♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 24]
Your Majesty,
since I returned from Sheng Kingdom,
Xiao Lin and I have already
broken off our relationship completely.
Bingchang, you…
But
your husband has deep feelings for you.
Xiao Lin risked his life
to come and assassinate me tonight,
luring all the guards to me
in order to help you escape.
Even I couldn't help
but be moved by such loyalty.
I wonder, Mrs. Xuancheng,
what are your thoughts on this?
No matter what Xiao Lin does,
I have nothing to do with it.
My heart is only
devoted to you, Your Majesty,
and will remain unchanged
throughout my life.
Really?
I swear on my life.
Haven't you been well with Bingchang?
Why did she say such words?
Alright, you may stand up.
You are the hero today,
and I should reward you.
What's General Ye doing here?
To give a hand?
Qingyu,
go ahead.
When I was at the Vermilion Bird Gate,
I saw Bingchang and Pian Ran
and heard them arguing.
I stopped Pian Ran
before she hit Bingchang.
Arguing for what?
About love threads.
Pian Ran, what are love threads?
Anyone with spiritual intelligence
would have love threads.
It is through love threads
that we are able to love others.
But I lost my love threads.
How did you lose them?
Why should I tell you?
Fine.
Then you tell me.
I…
I don't know what they are talking about.
Is that so?
Baiyu,
I heard
recently, the Moonshadow Guards
have developed a new demonic poison.
It can cause a person to
die a painful death within ten days,
but it also makes
them unable to keep any secrets.
I heard that it is quite effective.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Mrs. Xuancheng,
if you don't want to tell the truth,
you shall try the new poison for me.
Your Majesty,
you just gave me credit
and wanted to reward me.
They are not the same thing.
You can use the credit
to offset your mistakes.
After you try the poison,
I can consider keeping you alive.
Are you going to spit the truth,
or do you want to take the poison first?
I will tell the truth.
It happened seven years ago.
At that time, I had just turned 16
and was proud and arrogant.
Jiahui,
am I similar to this wildflower?
So weak and invisible…
In the Great General's
flourishing mansion,
who would notice
such an unremarkable wildflower?
Miss, don't say that.
You are beautiful and talented,
and you will surely marry
the perfect man someday.
How could someone like me
ever deserve a perfect husband?
Jiahui,
go to the temple
and ask for a safety charm on my behalf.
Hand it over to Grandma for me.
How about you, Miss?
It's not far from the city gate here.
I will walk back,
considering it an excursion.
Miss,
please hold on for a second.
Are you okay?
I'm going to die soon.
Miss,
could you do me a favor?
Are you from the capital of Sheng?
The girl I love is also in the capital.
I want to see her one last time.
Thanks.
[I wanna return what belongs to her.]
[Sadly…]
[She lives in the innermost house]
[of Orchid Alley in the city.]
[Please tell Pian Ran]
that I, Jiang Rao,
am just an ordinary man.
I'm not lucky enough
to spend my life with her.
[Receiving her love threads]
[was already a great fortune in my life.]
[I now return them]
[and hope that she will find happiness
and a wonderful relationship.]
[I wish her a life
full of joy and happiness.]
I'm sorry that I couldn't keep my promise.
[She looks so gorgeous]
[and has a lover
who was so devoted to her,]
[yet I have nothing.]
[At that time,]
[something wonderful shrouded me,]
[and it felt amazing,]
[making me forget myself.]
Who is it? Who's out there?
Jiang Rao,
was that you?
[I didn't know if
it was because of the love threads,]
[but later on,
my looks became more and more beautiful.]
[Men of all ages in the capital]
[are all captivated by me.]
I only knew that those things
were called love threads,
but I didn't know what they were.
Back then, I was greedy and foolish
and accidentally kept them for myself.
You didn't even know what they were,
and you kept them out of selfishness.
You knew that Jiang Rao
died with a heart full of regret,
but you didn't even want to
tell Pian Ran about his death.
I never thought that
Bingchang was such a person.
[It wasn't an illusion.]
[What grew in my heart were love threads.]
Even wanting to take
someone else's love threads for yourself,
You're truly despicable, Ye Bingchang.
Tantai Jin, don't kill her!
Xiwu,
Xiwu.
She stole these,
so she should give them back.
[So these are love threads.]
Women's misfortunes
often come from their loved ones.
I did possess this
demonic woman's love threads,
but I only received a little bit of
attention and admiration from others.
The promises of eternal love
and devotion that you gave me
were just because of the love threads.
Ye Qingyu,
Ye Xiwu,
you were born with everything you wanted.
What did I own?
Now you are even taking these from me.
I have nothing left.
Are you satisfied?
[If it wasn't for Ye Xiwu
enabling me to have love threads]
[and know the feeling of love,]
[I'm afraid I would never
have been able to experience it.]
Keep what belongs to you.
Take Xiao Lin to the prison,
strip Ye Bingchang of her title
as Mrs. Xuancheng,
and from tomorrow,
make her a slave in the inner court.
Yes.
[Chenming Hall]
Are you here to persuade me
or pity me?
When I was sad that day,
you could have dinner with me,
and today, when you are sad,
I can accompany you for a drink.
The river your sister mentioned,
back then,
I met Jiang Rao there.
He was watering his horse by the river,
but I thought
he was a creep spying on me taking a bath.
Without allowing him to explain,
I slapped him many times,
and he was stunned.
That river is very close to
the capital of Sheng.
It's so close that
the slowest person
can even walk home,
although 30 minutes late.
He was so close,
just a little bit,
and he could go home.
I've waited for him for so long.
Every day at home,
I counted the days on my fingers.
I waited for him
for more than a thousand days.
I know.
You must have waited for a long time.
♪Head to a short rendezvous♪
♪All dreams fall gracefully♪
I've been to the Jia Pass
to look for his corpse.
I looked for him for years,
but I heard nothing.
I had no idea
that he just died like that,
outside the city, with no one knowing.
♪May I never disappoint the moment we met♪
How ironic.
♪Loved and suffered
don't laugh at my infatuation♪
♪Crying and laughing
living for someone else♪
♪If my heart cannot entrust
without regret in this life♪
♪I'll stay amidst the crowd
unable to depart♪
♪Thankful to the heavens
for not overlooking me♪
♪Grateful for your constant presence
day and night, you see♪
♪For your memories, happiness
and sadness all bestowed♪
♪Even if no return date exists
I am content♪
Stop moving, alright?
Or the bed will fall apart.
I thought you wanted to comfort me,
but why are you
having a hard time going to sleep?
Tantai Jin,
do you think if Bingchang
wasn't a daughter of a concubine
and was treated with
more love and care at home,
would she have ended up differently?
Why aren't you thinking about sleeping
but her this late at night?
Why are you asking me?
Aren't you the same?
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking
perhaps the reason why
I used to be emotionless and heartless
was that I didn't have any love threads.
[Little Devil God guessed right.]
Ye Xiwu.
What would it feel like
to have love threads?
It's probably this feeling.
Go to sleep.
[Fu Yu,]
[How many more days
until this formation is completed?]
[Your Highness, three days will do.]
[In three days,]
[there will be no living creature left
within the southern border.]
How is the preparation
for the Puppet Soldiers going?
Your Highness,
the warlocks have been
working day and night to refine them,
and now there are more than ten thousand
Nether Puppet Soldiers for you to command.
Too few.
From today on,
ask them to accelerate
the refining of the demon soldiers.
I can't wait too long.
I will think of some solutions.
[Chenming Hall]
That's all. It's all done.
Right,
I want to go out to relax
one of these days.
Approved.
Tantai Jin,
you've got a conscience now.
If you keep babbling, no more days off.
Alright, alright.
What is it?
Your Majesty, I want to take a day off.
General Ye,
since you became a court official,
you have never rested for a day.
You can take a break.
It is right and proper
that officials have a day off
every five days.
Thanks.
You can put the food there.
Miss Xiwu, what are you doing here?
Take this.
I'm not short of food and clothing here.
Tantai Jin did not mistreat me.
Dad and Grandma asked me
to bring you this.
They care about you,
so just take it.
Thanks.
Does Tantai Jin know that you are here?
I will leave quickly after visiting you,
so I don't need to tell him.
I have nothing to do here all day,
and it's even more comfortable
than being in the barracks.
Go back quickly.
What are you planning to do?
What do you mean?
Where is Pang Yizhi?
Where are the Sheng's remaining troops?
I knew something was up with you.
Xiao Lin, you can trust me.
What do you really want to do?
I can definitely help you.
You don't need to help.
At this point, I can only
resign myself to my fate and await death.
Tantai Jin won't kill you.
I know he won't.
But he will never release me
from Jing's prison, either.
What on earth do you want?
Pang Yizhi will take at least six days
to return to the remaining troops.
If I could escape after the assassination,
I would lead the remaining troops
to recapture Jing's prisoners of war
and take them
south across the sea in six days.
If I couldn't escape,
Pang Yizhi would lead the remnant troops
and refugees to leave.
No need to wait for me.
What about you?
Sheng Kingdom can have
generals who die in battles
but not a crown prince who defects.
When the Sheng was breached,
I should have been buried
with the kingdom.
Come back here!
How can you be so stubborn?
Miss Xiwu, as long as I'm alive,
this last elite army
will fight to the death for me.
But now,
the Sheng is nearing its end.
Tantai Jin is a powerful leader.
With him,
the people of Sheng can still enjoy peace.
Only when I am dead,
and the hope of
Sheng Kingdom's revival is shattered,
can this war truly end
and the bloodshed stop.
So this time, you came
with the intention to die.
Yeah. We all have our aspirations.
Don't feel sad for me, Miss Xiwu.
Just wait here.
Within six days, I'll figure out a way
to let you leave with the Sheng army.
This is too risky.
Please don't take any chances.
Wait for my news.
Miss Xiwu.
Actually,
you're not Ye Xiwu, right?
Why did you say that?
I've known Ye Xiwu since little.
She wouldn't fight for others
or go on a mission alone.
Not to mention
risking her life to save me.
After Bo're Life,
when we're parting by the Mohe River,
I was already certain of it.
Prince Lin, I…
No need to explain.
This must be a most mysterious thing
not to be told to others.
Rest assured.
I won't mention it to anyone,
whether I live or die this time.
Just go.
Wait for me to save you.
For how long?
A quarter of an hour at most.
What did they talk about?
I was too far away to hear clearly.
At least you could see clearly.
They…
What?
Was it so hard to describe?
First,
Xiao Lin put his hand on Miss Ye's face.
Miss Ye dragged his clothes vigorously.
And then Miss Ye left.
That's all.
Nian Baiyu,
next time something like this happens,
send someone more articulate to watch.
You're dismissed.
Yes.
Ye Xiwu,
you cunt.
Who's Ye Bingchang?
I am.
Your family is here. Come with me.
[Palace Prison]
Grandma?
Grandma.
Bingchang, you've suffered.
Grandma, how can you get here to see me?
I asked Xiwu for help.
She is quite favored
by His Majesty.
That's why I can come to see you.
We've all heard about what you did.
It's fair to be punished
for your mistakes.
But blood is thicker than water.
You're one of our family, after all.
We won't abandon you.
Don't worry.
Grandma.
Actually,
I shouldn't have got greedy
for the love threads.
These days in Palace Prison,
I've finally come around.
To correct a mistake is the greatest good.
Alright, enough of these.
Come, look.
Take the food and clothes.
Thanks, Grandma.
Oh… I almost forgot.
Come, take this.
It's the hand ointment.
Xiwu told me to
bring it to you.
She said that it's cold in Jing Kingdom.
So Tantai Jin told the imperial doctors
to make up this ointment
for treating chilblains.
You can't buy this anywhere else.
She specially spared some
and told me to bring it to you.
Remember to apply it often every day.
After all,
Xiwu still cares about her elder sister.
Yeah.
That's why they all say
she's got a kind heart.
The palace gate is about to be closed.
We gotta head home.
Grandma,
I just remembered that
it's my mother's death anniversary
in a few days.
Although I've failed
to be a good daughter,
I still wish to go home
to pay respects to her.
Grandma,
could you discuss this with Xiwu?
See if she can
beg for mercy from His Majesty.
Begging for mercy?
Miss Xiwu can't help you with everything.
Grandma, I really regret what I did.
Bingchang,
I'll talk to Xiwu about it.
We'll see what we can do.
Thanks, Grandma.
[Chenming Hall]
Ye Qingyu asked for leave again.
He went outside behind my back
quite frequently these days.
And he tried to hide it from me.
Was he secretly doing something
unspeakable?
This is the road to Sheng Kingdom.
Ye Qingyu,
what exactly are you up to?
Although we were born in the same kingdom,
and we're both soldiers,
we didn't have the chance
to see each other.
[Tomb of Jiang Rao]
You're a good son of the Sheng.
You died here,
but you died for your kingdom.
This cup is me paying my respect.
The second cup
is me envying you.
Though you're killed in the war,
your soul lives on.
Not just in your homeland
but also in people's hearts.
In her heart,
she will always love you,
think of you, and miss you.
She'll be sad and happy for you.
Whatever happens in the future,
she'll never be able
to forget you in her life.
That's why I admire her too.
Although she's a spirit
with a very long life,
she's willing to love a plain mortal
and won't change her feelings
for him ever.
Sometimes I'd think,
if someday I also died in battle,
I could be like you.
I'd always have a place in her heart.
But
that was just a thought.
I wouldn't want her to be alone.
I want to be alive
and stay by her side
to love her and protect her.
I wanna spend this short life with her.
If your soul's down there,
please don't worry.
I'll take good care of her.
I, Ye Qingyu, will only
love this woman in my entire life.
I will never fail her.
♪Go for a short appointment♪
♪All dreams fall off like petals♪
Why didn't you
give me this sweet talk in my face?
Pian Ran.
♪I won't lay it bare or cling on♪
Thank you
for finding him.
I've also tried to look for it
in the outskirts,
but I missed the right spot.
I thought after so many years,
his bones were long gone.
I'm familiar with Sheng's warfare.
When soldiers came back from the front,
they always took these few paths.
That's why I…
That's why
you kept coming back
to see him behind my back?
♪If I can't entrust myself
to you without regrets♪
♪No matter how much I love you
we won't walk far♪
[Tomb of Jiang Rao]
Jiang Rao,
this man wasn't lying to you.
I live pretty well now.
And I'm happy.
♪Thank heaven for not blessing me♪
I found the one to spend a lifetime with.
♪Thanks for giving me
all your emotions and memories♪
♪It's enough even if there's no return♪
♪You're my first love♪
♪And my last love, too♪
What?
Got something on your mind?
Nothing.
By the way,
you told me that
Ye Bingchang wanted to be free
for two days
to go home and pay respects to her mother.
I've approved that.
But you must watch her closely.
She's now a slave in Palace Prison.
Don't let her escape again.
Understood.
You…
Don't you have anything to say to me?
No.
Then I'm leaving.
Go ahead.
[Today is the sixth day for Xiao Lin.]
[I can't wait any longer.]
Safe journey, Miss Xiwu.
What are you waiting for? Move!
Who'd have thought
a slave from Palace Prison
could still go home?
Move it.
[Ye Mansion]
Miss,
Miss Bingchang just came back.
Don't you wanna see her?
Wasn't I just back from the palace too?
I don't have time to chat with her today.
Miss,
what exactly are you doing?
Chuntao,
do me a favor.
I wanna cook sweet porridge
for Tantai Jin.
Porridge is supposed to be a simple one.
I guess I won't mess it up, right?
It's hard to tell.
[What a perfect chance.]
[This is pure dumb luck.]
This time,
it literally tastes good.
Miss Bingchang!
These crude drugs are for Her Ladyship!
Miss Bingchang, these crude drugs
are for Her Ladyship!
Miss Bingchang.
What's going on?
Miss Xiwu,
I need these crude drugs to brew medicine
for Her Ladyship later.
But Miss Bingchang just knocked them over.
What should I do later?
Let go of my sister. Don't be rude.
But these drugs…
Let go.
We must not ruin grandma's drugs.
I'll help you clean this mess.
Bingchang,
you must be tired as you got up early.
Go back to rest.
Miss Xiwu,
why do you always tolerate her?
Think about the things she did.
Besides, she's a slave
in Palace Prison now.
Shame on her!
That's enough. Let's get to work.
Come on, eat more of this.
[What a coincidence.]
[Ye Xiwu,]
[I thought you loved Tantai Jin deeply.]
[But you actually have evil plans, huh?]
[Tantai Jin,]
[I'm sorry.]
[You'll only be sleeping for a few hours]
[after drinking the knockout drops.]
[I'll apologize to you when I'm back.]
[You can punish me however you like.]
Why are you still up?
I'm waiting for you.
What have you cooked today?
Sweet porridge.
I guess I didn't mess up this time.
You can have a taste.
You eat first.
I'll eat it
after reading these reports.
I'm not hungry.
I'm gonna lie down for a while.
Remember to eat it when finishing reading.
Okay.
[What trick is she playing again?]
Bingchang,
why are you still up?
I'm here to deliver a night snack for you.
Did you cook this?
I'm not so dutiful as to
do such a good thing.
It's cooked by
your good granddaughter Ye Xiwu.
Bingchang,
why are you talking like this?
She told me to let you finish it all,
so don't waste her efforts.
Alright.
[Reported by official historian Zhou Liwei]
[I'm not hungry.]
I'm gonna lie down for a while.
Remember to eat it
when you finish reading.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪