The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 32]
Ye Xiwu,
is it you?
[Has Chief Qu heard about a lady]
[named Ye Xuwu?]
[Seems we haven't heard about her]
[in our immortal world.]
[Is she the disciple of our Hengyang Sect?]
[Jiwu has no parents.]
[He is not even a normal person.]
[Are you the real Ye Xiwu]
[or another fake Xiao Lin?]
Hello,
you've got the wrong person.
I don't know you.
Sorry.
My mistake.
I'm Cang Jiumin,
the disciple of the Xiaoyao Sect.
May I
know your name, please?
You're Sect Brother Cang.
I'm Li Susu from Hengyang Sect.
If there is nothing else,
I'm gonna go.
Wait.
I hear of you from Jiwu very often,
but haven't visited you.
So it's very lucky
to meet you today.
Sect Sister,
why not be with Jiwu?
He has something important to do,
so he doesn't come with me.
How about we go find him together?
Maybe we can pick up
some Immortal Tree Fruits.
Ok.
I can take the chance to just walk around.
It's my first time
to come to the Shangqing realm.
The palaces, painted pillars
and carved beams
are magnificent
So we can enjoy it on the way.
If you are interested in the realm,
I heard a story about it.
Ten thousand years ago,
there was a God of War.
His name was Ming Ye.
He married
a smart and lovely Clam Tribe princess.
♪I still bet my life on you♪
Her name is Sang Jiu.
♪We share this long, long dream♪
♪Love threads twine around the remaining heat♪
♪Our love has taken root long ago♪
Though Ming Ye
disliked the marriage at first,
he was drawn
into her step-by-step later.
Yet he didn't have time
to respond to her love.
She mistakenly thought
that he didn't love her.
So she left the Shangqing realm.
Since he regretted,
why didn't he go after her?
How do you know he didn't do that?
There was a battle
between gods and evils back then.
Even the Heavenly Pillar was sacked.
Ming Ye was the God of War in the realm.
He was afraid that he'd his life
in the battle
and Sang Jiu would be sad about this.
That's why
he bit the bullet not go looking for her.
But Ming Ye felt
he'd be okay
if only she was happy and safe.
All right.
That's the story.
Let's go find Xiao Lin.
Sure.
♪Do you know a wise man♪
♪Does not fall in love?♪
Ye Xiwu.
♪I won't fly away♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
I don't get what you're talking about.
I said
you've mistaken me for the other one.
[Why do you have to show up
at this particular time?]
[I can't tell you I'm Sang Jiu right now.]
[Sorry.]
[Tantai Jin.]
♪O, how I suffered inside♪
♪The delusion of having a dream being with you♪
♪A day is like a thousand years♪
At there.
Unexpectedly, over ten thousand years,
the Water Mirror has dried up.
And the Bone-refining Seal
has been revealed.
Without it,
it couldn't be found
for another ten years.
Just do it.
Wait.
It's a disadvantage for us to fight
in the Shangqing realm.
We need to use the diversion tactic.
You go distract them
so as not to ruin our plan.
Ye Mei and Feng Shi have been
awaiting orders down the mountain.
I'm gonna meet them
and go to Hengyang Sect for a big fight.
That's also great.
I'm Yue Fuya from Hengyang Sect.
I've finally got a chance
to meet you, the demons, today.
I'm gonna destroy you even at the cost of life.
Be careful.
Have you come to rescue me?
What's your name?
Where are you going?
Can I go with you?
It is horrible here.
Go.
Finally, it arrives.
Quick to open the Mountain Protecting Form.
Enjoy the power of my sword.
I bet you will never go back home.
Xiaoyao Sword Form!
Ten Views of Cloud Mountain!
Stop!
Your spirit seems great to devour.
Demon, stop.
Hurry to surrender.
Subduing Devil Form.
So much for your trap!
We've been waiting for you so long.
Start the form.
I thought you were capable.
But it's just so-so.
When I served the Devil God,
Only Ji Ze, Chu Huang
were the ones worthy of me fighting with.
Jing Mie,
don't talk wildly.
You are bound to die here today.
Where is Si Ying?
Why is only Jing Mie here today?
[So much noise there?]
[I'm afraid Jing Mie can't resist for too long.]
[I need to hurry up.]
[I remember, in Bo're Life,]
[Ming Ye has sealed]
[the Bone-refining Seal in the Divine Platform.]
[The Bone-refining Seal connects
to the Devil God's energy]
[and is very powerful.]
[Since it couldn't be destroyed,]
[the only solution is to seal it]
[under the Water Mirror.]
[and subdue it here forever
with the help of divine power.]
Terrible.
Divine Platform has something wrong.
Qu, stand still.
Disciples above all have been back.
Perhaps they are making a deke.
Let's kill this devil first
and not be duped.
Stop, devil.
As long as I'm here,
you are not allowed
to take the Bone-refining Seal away.
[It's her.]
[Then I'm gonna take your life.]
[You can't act wildly]
[at the former divine residence.]
[Just you alone to stop me?]
[Even the twelve gods risk their life,]
[they can't stop His Lordship.]
[What do you count?]
[The Bone-refining Seal
and the Heart of the Devil God]
[will be returned to His Lordship finally.]
[You are born with the evil bone]
[and doom to be the Devil God.]
[You're the Devil God.]
[You're the biggest curse]
[in the world.]
[This is your destiny.]
[To be a devil or a divine]
[is up to a moment's thought of you.]
[Ming Ye.]
Why do you choose me
to step into your Bo're Life?
You find no chance
to take the Bone-refining Seal today.
A common disciple of the immortal
could actually seal the Bone-refining Seal.
Xiaoyao Sword-play,
Shatter!
No.
Something is wrong with Divine Platform.
Cang Jiumin.
[This is for…]
[Your Lordship.]
Cang Jiumin,
Don't be seduced by devil energy.
Wake up.
It's been five hundred years.
The demonic fetus has been found by me
in the end.
[It looks like they have found it.]
[The charm has been made in.]
[Devil God,]
[I guess you didn't expect that, right?]
[The ones unsealed me]
[are two of your most loyal men.]
[I have regained the freedom]
[that deprived by you.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[you are originally a demonic fetus.]
[How can you defy my will?]
[When the seal merges into your heart,]
[I…]
[am gonna wake up.]
Cang Jiumin.
Wake up!
No.
No way!
[It's His Lordship's power.]
Cang Jiumin.
Concentrate.
Don't get carried away.
[His Lordship's plan is abstruse.]
[Today the situation is uncertain.]
[Better not get involved in it here.]
[I can come to pick His Lordship up
to go back to Barren Abyss]
[when the demonia fetus is wakened up.]
Ok, your Lordship.
The Bone-refining Seal originally is yours.
I'm leaving now.
[The devil energy is due to
the seal integrated with the heart.]
Cang Jiumin, Cang Jiumin.
Don't be bewitched by the demon artifact.
Wake up.
The Bone-refining Seal has connected
to your heart.
Do you wanna die?
Cang Jiumin,
Wake up.
Cang Jiumin.
Si Ying?
You come just at the right moment.
Let's kill all of them together today.
[Jing Mie,]
[No need to fight more.]
[Let's go.]
I didn't expect
they have fled.
[Could it be that someone leaked our plan?]
The immortal contest
has actually leaked out information.
The two demons took advantage of it.
It's my mistake.
To my surprise,
they came to Shangqing realm
to steal the devil artifact.
All right.
Qu, it's not your fault.
It's dark under the light.
Nobody expected the Bone-refining Seal
would hide in the Divine Platform.
Luckily, Jiumin and Susu
fought desperately
to have got back the demon seal.
Otherwise,
the consequences would be unimaginable.
Supposedly, the two devils
will come up with new tricks
as they couldn't snatch the seal.
Master,
Something happens at the barrier
outside the gate of the realm.
Seems the devil tribe is invading us.
Who are you?
How dare you intrude on our immortal realm!
You all may leave.
Buddy,
long time no see.
Di Mian, you have been imprisoned by Demond God
for ten-thousand years.
Finally, you return today.
Congratulations!
The ten thousand years
all are just fleeting time.
I think your immortal dress
is perfect for you.
Why not stay here for a while?
Then you two can get together.
What do you ask
to see me for?
If you wanna know how Cang Jiumin's injury is,
I have handed him to Uncle Zhaoyou
as your instruction
for a good recuperate.
My dear.
[Susu.]
Who are you?
Come to me.
How come you know my name?
It's you.
Susu,
you two know each other.
I had been to Barren Abyss
and talked with him.
You fell in rashly at that time.
If I hadn't noticed you in time,
you would have been smashed to pieces.
I'm very grateful
for you saving my life.
It looks like you two
knew each other by fate.
Susu,
come here.
Get down on your knees
and kowtow to your father.
To repay him for giving you life.
No.
I'm her biological father.
But,
I haven't raised her for one day.
God has been nice to me
for us to reunite here.
Father?
Dad,
what's going on?
It's a long story.
During the devil slaying battle
ten thousand years ago,
Lord of Evil defected and badly hurt Devil God,
but was sealed in Barren Abyss by Devil God.
[Decades ago, I had an arduous struggle
with the evil cultivator.]
[I seriously hurt
and fell into Barren Abyss]
[and was almost devoured by devils.]
[Fortunately, I fell outside the gate
of Di Mian's cave.]
[He tried his best to cover me
with his devil power]
[and dispelled the devils.]
[That's how I got away with it.]
[In return for his saving my life,]
[I promised him to find]
[the spirit egg he had with his late wife, Chu Huang.]
I haven't seen it.
No.
I haven't heard of it.
Thanks.
[Fortunately, heaven will pay you off
for your persistence.]
[I found the spirit egg eventually.]
[It was hard to be hatched.]
[Then I put it on the Magic Well
of Sumeru Base]
[It was nourished
by the pure spirit of heaven and earth.]
[Later, there was life movement in the egg.]
[Then I cast its spirit into the world.]
It went through life cycles
and suffered constantly.
I hoped one day
it could find a chance to break the shell
and come out.
[She was born on the Magic well
of the Heaven Lake.]
and generated from the spirit
of heaven and earth.
So I named her Princess of Elegance.
When Chu Huang died back then,
her body became Chongyu Harp,
a precious treasure of the Hengyang Sect.
I gave Chongyu Harp to that baby
and hoped she could be protected
by her mother somehow.
Now I see that the one I met
is my mother.
Dad sent my spirit into the world
to suffer constantly.
That's why there was Ye Xiwu five years ago.
and she looks just like me.
Maybe
she is my lifelong evil soul.
My spirit should have been restored
after the trials of a lifetime,
but it was damaged
by the Lightning Punishment.
As a result,
after five hundred years,
my physical body would spontaneously
combust without any external flames
and rest for ten years on the Sumeru Base.
Only when the cataclysm ends
can I truly wake up.
That's what happened.
Susu,
I hid the truth from you for so long,
and you won't blame me, will you?
I...
Susu,
you don't have to force yourself.
It's understandable if you don't want to
accept me as your father
or even hate me.
I don't hate you.
I just don't know what to do.
That's fine.
No matter whether you accept me or not,
Chief Qu will always be your father.
The grace of upbringing
cannot be severed by anyone.
Alright,
no matter whether you are
willing to call me father or not,
we will
take care of you together.
Father.
Get up.
It's really strange to think about it.
My mother is from the Phoenix Clan,
but I was born afraid of
birds and chickens.
It seems that destiny is predetermined.
It turns out that I'm afraid of myself.
This is great.
Today, you two reunited,
and a major issue in my heart is resolved.
Right, Di Mian,
your identity is special,
so please temporarily reside in our sect.
When I find a suitable opportunity,
I will invite all sects
to explain this matter
and let you
reestablish yourself in the world
with honor and dignity.
Thank you.
Have you heard?
Today, who trespassed into our sect
is the Lord of Evil, Di Mian,
who commands thousands of demons.
Actually, you may not know,
but his wife is the Goddess of Space, Chu Huang.
He risked his life
to work for the Devil God
in order to search for the Devil's weakness.
Yes, it is said in the legend
that he is the one who
defeated and killed Devil God.
Yes, it seems that
he has been through a lot
and endured many hardships.
Finally, he was able to
restore his reputation and identity.
All factions of the immortal sect
should treat him kindly and with respect.
For sure.
He is the hero who killed Devil God!
When His Lordship's
Bone-refining Seal was broken,
Mo Nv's spirit was unexpectedly
gathered together.
Sister!
You're finally awake!
His Lordship saved you again!
Sister!
I am Si Ying!
Si Ying?
Your spirit was damaged
ten thousand years ago,
and that's why His Lordship
sent you to reincarnate in the mortal realm.
Now that your spirit has been restored
and you have returned,
we can finally reunite.
Si Ying, my sister!
Sister!
Susu,
since you now know your true identity,
it is natural that you have answers
to the changes you have undergone
since emerging from seclusion.
The Phoenix Clan
has a natural affinity
for practicing the Heartless Way,
which is considered a shortcut to godhood.
However, it is ultimately up to you
to decide whether or not to pursue this path.
Dad,
knowing my origins
has strengthened my resolve
to pursue my destination.
My mother was slain by the Devil God,
and my father was imprisoned
by him as well.
Whether for personal or public reasons,
it is my mission to
fight against the Devil God.
If the Devil God were to
truly return to this world,
then only a true god would be able to
resist and oppose him
in the Four Continents and Three Realms.
It is quite a heavy burden
to place solely upon your shoulders.
It's...
Dad, rest assured.
I promise,
the day of the Devil God's return
will never come.
Although Tantai Jin's evil bone
has been extracted,
the identity of the demonic fetus
is still highly unusual.
It would be best
to inform them only after
I have truly destroyed the evil bone.
It's just that
my practice of the Heartless Way is too...
Cang, I wonder
what are you here for?
Indeed, I have come
to make a request of you today.
I'm all ears.
Actually,
I was born in Jing five hundred years ago.
When I was little,
I was loathed by my father
and bullied by others.
I had never felt the warmth of this world
until one day
someone came into my life.
At first,
she kept saying that she wanted to kill me,
but she saved me several times.
It was her who showed me
the joys
and warmth of life,
as well as the pains
and sorrows,
and all the beauty that comes with it.
Later,
she told me that she liked me.
I was so happy at that time.
If only time could freeze
at that moment forever,
it would be so perfect.
Who is that person?
Her name is Ye Xiwu.
Sadly,
I made an irreparable mistake
and she died.
The dead cannot be brought back to life.
Please accept my condolences.
I originally wanted to
join her in death,
but someone told me
that there is a Nether River in this world
that converges the spirits
of the three realms.
In order to see her again,
I found the Nether River
and searched for her in it
for five hundred years.
Every day,
my bones were burned by the Ruo Water,
and the pain was unbearable.
Later on,
I couldn't feel the pain anymore
and didn't even feel like I was alive.
But I still could not find her spirit.
What happened then?
Until one day,
I felt like I was about to die.
Fortunately,
Immortal Zhaoyou saved me
and I became a disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.
This is all of my experiences
over the past five hundred years.
Jiumin, why are you
telling me all these?
The Nether River
didn't help me find Ye Xiwu,
but I read about a Soul Gathering Array
which can help me find Ye Xiwu's spirit.
However, this array requires
the blood of a pure spirit body as a trigger.
Miss Li,
can you help me
find the one I love?
If I can really find her,
I am willing to give everything I have
to compensate her,
even if
she wants my life,
I will give it to her.
I can't help you.
Let the past be passed.
Since you've changed your name
and started over,
why not forget about her completely?
The Ye Xiwu in your heart
no longer exists.
No longer exists?
What do you mean by that?
You have the same face
and the same temperament.
Yuling,
you are Ye Xiwu,
why don't you admit it?
Do you know that
you don't even dare to look at me?
Have you heard of
Zhuangzi's Dream of the Butterfly?
What?
You can think of Ye Xiwu as that butterfly,
everything is like a dream
and when you wake up,
it should all be dispersed.
Dispersed...
How?
Five hundred years have passed,
and I have never forgotten her.
I have seen her smile,
seen her cry.
She has hugged me,
protected me.
She loved me,
and hated me.
Even if this is really just a dream,
if you abandon me in the dream,
how can I easily wake up?
I don't understand what you are saying.
I have woken up from my dream.
It has nothing to do with me
whether you wake up or not.
Tantai Jin,
if you really want to make amends,
then forget about the past
and be Cang Jiumin.
♪Thousands of words have,♪
♪in my throat
been stewing again and again♪
♪As the snowy foam floating in the cup
sinks deep within♪
As for me,
I am Li Susu, daughter of Chief Qu.
Now that the Devil God is about to descend
upon the Four Continents and Three Realms,
it's like facing an abyss.
I have decided to
cultivate the Heartless Way
for the rest of my life
and eradicate evil
in order to uphold justice.
♪My keenest quest for your company♪
♪all my life never fades♪
Our past is over
and we are now strangers.
This is the path you and I
must take.
♪Who can be spared from the pains?♪
♪The surging torrent of love♪
♪Keeps the sound of its murmurs faint♪
♪I allow no word to escape
But a trickle, flowing deep,♪
♪Ripples in my eyes to explain♪
♪I recall the fragrant rains♪
I am tired,
so please leave.
♪may as well be the staffage♪
♪Beyond the deepest depths of our hearts♪
♪Before we go gray
our romance has ended in vain♪
It turns out,
when you said that we will never
meet each other again
in this life and the next,
you meant it.
♪Keep the wine of dreams flowing endlessly♪
♪Until we are drunk with abandon♪
♪Whispering in each other's ears,
Caressing soft palm prints tenderly♪
♪How lucky we are♪
♪Since we can meet♪
♪A kiss is more worth than everything♪
♪Already involved in the chess game♪
♪who can be spared from the pains?♪
♪The surging torrent of love♪
♪Keeps the sound of its murmurs faint♪
♪Even when I know a hug will hurt each other♪
♪I still bet my life on you♪
♪I recall the fragrant rains♪
♪which melt into my eyes' waves♪
♪The peach blossoms,
fallen on the delicate arch of your brows,♪
♪may as well be the staffage♪
She loved me, and hated me.
Even if this is really just a dream,
if you abandon me in the dream,
how can I easily wake up?
♪who can be spared from the pains?♪
♪The surging torrent of love♪
♪Keeps the sound of its murmurs faint♪
It turns out,
when you said that we will never
meet each other again
in this life and the next,
you meant it.
♪We share this long, long dream♪
♪Love threads twine around the remaining heat♪
♪Our love has taken root long ago♪
♪The seeds of love are hard to let go
and hard to part with♪
♪Beyond the deepest depths of our hearts♪
♪I'll miss you one life after another♪
In this Immortal Sect Competition,
I gave you so many artifacts
to help you come out on top
and bring glory to our Glorious Glow Sect.
But you didn't seem
interested in winning,
and instead, why did you flirt with a girl?
You're really disappointing.
I'm injured too!
Dad,
you are not even helping me retaliate!
Helping you?
I am too ashamed to see anyone now.
When can you bring us glory
like Cang Jiumin
and Gongye Jiwu did?
I would like to be like them,
but I simply do not have
the same natural talents.
You always tell me to work hard,
but if you have the ability,
why don't you work hard
and create another kid like them?
Nonsense!
You!
Kneel here and reflect
for a full 24 hours!
Cang Jiumin,
just you wait!
Sooner or later
I will make you fall from grace.
So, you and Cang Jiumin
knew each other 500 years ago
and were a couple in the past life.
The reasons behind it are complicated,
and forgive me that I can't explain them.
In short,
Cang Jiumin was a part of the tribulation
in my past life 500 years ago.
No wonder you have been melancholic
ever since you came out of seclusion,
as if you have changed.
Jiwu,
I don't want to deceive you.
What happened between Tantai Jin and I
is now in the past.
But after reuniting with him,
I realized that
even if we can't continue our past relationship,
there is no room
in my heart for anyone else.
Susu,
you are telling me these just to...
Because if I continue to be indecisive,
it will only make me
feel more sorry towards you.
I understand now.
Susu,
you don't have to feel guilty.
It is because I was not thoughtful enough
and failed to realize it earlier,
that caused you
to suffer alone for a long time.
Although I am reluctant,
no matter what,
I hope you can find happiness
according to your own wishes.
Moving on from someone is indeed not easy.
Give me some time.
In the next few days,
I will ask my master for permission
to leave the sect to catch demons.
I hope that when I see you again,
I will be able to face you
with an open and calm heart,
and just be your elder sect brother.
Jiwu...
Have a good rest.
I should leave now.
I'm sorry, Jiwu.
Quick pain is better than long-suffering.
This is the best choice
for you and me.
if you really want to make amends,
then forget about the past
and be Cang Jiumin.
As for me,
I am Li Susu, daughter of Chief Qu.
Now that the Devil God is about to descend...
I have decided to
cultivate the Heartless Way
for the rest of my life and eradicate evil
in order to uphold justice.
The Devil God again...
Once the demonic fetus
is born into this world
and the devil weapon recognizes its owner,
the Devil God will be resurrected
and the three realms
will face an disastrous destruction.
I heard that the recent battle of Barren Abyss
was because Si Ying and Jing Mie,
the two remnants of the Devil God,
lost the demonic fetus.
That's why they have been
causing trouble everywhere,
trying to find the demonic fetus
through the devil weapon.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪