♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of the Moon]
[Episode 23]
Ye Qingyu.
You're awake.
You were drunk last night.
Do you have a headache?
I was being impulsive
after drinking last night.
Please don't take it to heart.
I can tell the difference.
That's good then.
Ye Qingyu, I…
You're here to ask me
about the antidote, right?
You can be frank with me.
I can't stay here any longer.
Give me the antidote.
And I'll leave the capital by myself.
Why? Is it because of me?
I really don't know
if I should feel honored
or unfortunate.
Ye Qingyu, it's impossible between us.
What do I have to do
for you to give me the antidote?
There is no antidote.
What?
His Majesty told me
that the pill he forced you to swallow
was just a regular tonic pill.
Tantai Jin!
So, you're free.
Tantai Jin said
he gave the antidote to you.
I can never leave your side
as long as you use
that excuse to keep me around.
Why did you tell me the truth?
You're a woman of your word.
And I enjoyed momentary pleasure with you.
I dare not expect God
to favor me again.
Pian Ran, encountering you
was the most fortunate event
that had happened to me.
What if I feel like
staying in the capital again?
It's okay. You can go wherever you want.
If you don't wish to see me,
I can write to His Majesty
and leave the capital myself.
Ye Qingyu,
are you truly a fool?
Or are you pretending to be one?
Forget it.
I can't bother to explain it to you.
Anyway, I'm free now.
I can go wherever I want.
Now, I feel like
staying in the capital again.
Pian Ran.
So,
we can spend time with each other again,
right?
I guess. It depends on your performance.
Xiwu,
have you two reconciled with each other?
There's nothing to reconcile about.
There are no overnight grudges
between husband and wife.
Buttercup,
you must tell me if you feel troubled.
Don't hold it in and suffer alone.
I'm perfectly fine.
How can that be?
Tantai Jin is the emperor now.
And our family has fallen from grace.
You may inevitably be subjected
to humiliation in front of him.
What humiliation?
I made him sleep on the floor last night.
Xiwu,
you're excellent at taming your husband.
Speaking of which,
Bingchang hasn't returned home yet
after she arrived in the capital.
Now, Bingchang is
the noble Madam Xuancheng.
Tantai Jin lets her live in the palace.
I think he's afraid that Xiao Lin
may snatch her away.
It's always safer to hide in the palace.
When she's in the Palace of Jing,
Xiao Lin will have to hold back.
They won't ignore her.
Has Bingchang
suffered any grievances then?
Don't worry, Grandma.
Tantai Jin isn't that kind of person.
If you're still worried,
I'll visit her after dinner
and ask her if she's willing to move back.
Good.
Come on, eat up.
That's the gist of it.
Bingchang, you must have suffered
for the past few days.
I'll apologize to you
on Tantai Jin's behalf.
There's no need to say that.
How could I make
the emperor apologize to me?
I'm happy for you
that you two have
reconciled with each other.
That's typical of Tantai Jin.
He's so capricious.
Just don't take it to heart.
If you can't get used to
living in the palace,
I can speak with Tantai Jin
and tell him to let you leave.
You can go home and
live with Grandma and Dad.
No need.
I mean, His Majesty must have his reasons
to let me stay in the palace.
Besides, I've already gotten used to it.
I shouldn't go home
and disturb Grandma and Dad.
But…
Xiwu, we are both married women.
How can we keep
living in our parents' home?
It's good for you that
you can stay by His Majesty's side.
But me?
Prince Lin is still missing.
If I live at home,
I'll look like a divorced woman instead.
Our neighbors will criticize us.
It's better if I live in the palace.
All right.
But Grandma and Dad do miss you very much.
Please visit them when you're free.
All right. Thanks for your concern.
Then I'll head back first.
[Tantai Jin still loved her deeply]
[despite how Xiwu treated him.]
[If I stay in the palace,]
[I might still have a chance.]
[If I move home,]
[it'll be difficult
to see Tantai Jin again.]
[I didn't expect that
he had no desires for me.]
[If I want to live off him,]
[I must be of use to him.]
Your Majesty.
You may speak over there.
I don't know what I have done wrong
to make you dislike me.
You have done nothing wrong.
Once I capture Xiao Lin,
I'll let you two reunite.
Your Majesty, do you have to
capture Prince Xuancheng?
Why did you think I allowed you
to stay here in the first place?
Your Majesty,
I have something to discuss with you.
The rations I borrowed two days ago
will run out in another two days.
We're out of medicine and bandages too.
What should we do?
Is there any nearby county which
we haven't borrowed rations from?
There's none.
Try again then.
Your Highness, you're now a rebel.
We're all wanted criminals.
Forget about borrowing rations.
They have already done us one last favor
by not reporting us
to the local authorities.
Junior Martial Uncle,
what are our odds of winning
if we keep this up?
Well, you see…
We have no chance of winning, right?
There's nothing we can do about it.
Do you still remember you, me, and Qingyu
used to discuss
state affairs in the capital?
Common folks always suffer
no matter how the state does.
It's always been like this.
I've engaged the people of Jing in battle
on numerous occasions.
Although Jing Kingdom is our enemy,
their soldiers and people
are made of flesh and blood too.
Qingyu was right.
To common folks, war is detrimental
no matter if it's won or lost.
Now, Tantai Jin fights for peace.
People want him to unite the world.
Maybe I should lead
our remaining people southward
and leave this place.
How could you harbor such thoughts?
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
The spy we planted in the Capital of Jing
sent us a secret letter.
It's for you.
It's Bingchang's handwriting.
No wonder Tantai Jin
allowed her to write to you.
The content of the letter
praises his benevolence.
Looks like Tantai Jin
is still bent on making you surrender.
Something's not right.
What do you mean?
[Help]
[Jingyao Gate]
Court dismissed.
General Ye.
Your Majesty.
Disaster relief involves many aspects.
You're from Sheng Kingdom.
I feel most reassured to let you
help the refugees to settle down.
I shall not fail you, Your Majesty.
Now, the world is united.
I desire for
the people of Sheng Kingdom to settle down
and recoup their losses
more than anyone else.
And I appreciate your kindness
Today's the Qixi Festival.
I heard that the night of Qixi
in the Capital of Jing is the liveliest.
Why don't you
go for a stroll with Pian Ran?
Go ahead.
Ye Xiwu.
Bravo!
Let's go.
Now, Sheng and Jing are united.
The state is in peace.
We can finally have a proper festival.
That's right.
You accomplished a good deed.
I just did what a ruler should do.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
It's crowded here.
Today's the last day of
the Water Festival.
And it's also the Qixi Festival.
The townsfolk are all out on the streets.
The liveliest day of the year
is today.
Tantai Jin,
why are they all wearing masks?
It's for the seven-day-long deity parade
during the Water Festival.
It is said that it would
help exorcise demons.
You'll understand
if we run into one later.
Masks for sale!
Sir, pick one.
Let's get one and follow the customs.
Okay.
Don't just agree verbally. Pay up.
Come. This one suits you.
I want this one.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you.
Let's go.
Masks for sale!
Sir, take a look.
So, we're inside
the Capital of Jing already?
Keep your guard up. Stay cautious.
This is enemy territory after all.
Yes, sir.
All right.
Let's go.
You scared me.
Please feel free to try.
Try this one. It's freshly made.
Thanks.
Okay.
Does it taste good?
Yes.
Take a look at this.
Exquisite craft for sale.
It brings you good luck.
Take a look!
It's so pretty.
It's a white jade scepter.
[Ward off evil and diseases]
Excuse me.
Bravo!
Pick me!
Me?
Tantai Jin, what is this?
This is a custom of Jing.
When you're picked by the arch wizard,
you'll be the goddess
of this year's Water Festival.
Go now. You'll be blessed with good luck.
Why did he pick you then?
Are you a goddess too?
Are you a god then?
Miss, what's with the question?
Have you not celebrated
the Water Festival before?
I'm from Sheng Kingdom.
No wonder.
Since the wizard pointed at him,
that meant he had been chosen
as the Devil God.
You heard of the War of the Titans
that happened 10,000 years ago, right?
He has been chosen as the Devil God
to join the parade with you.
Go now. You were picked by the wizard
to pray for the world.
You'll be blessed with
peace and happiness too.
You need to finish the sword dance rite
with the Devil God.
After that, you have to
kill the Devil God.
♪We go separate ways♪
♪Right or wrong, success or failure♪
♪Past or present♪
♪Broken, rebuilt,♪
♪Destroy, reconstruct♪
♪I don't care about my tears of sadness♪
♪I won't follow the destined path of my life♪
♪When the mystic bird returns
who will it be then?♪
[Ward off evil and diseases]
♪I've searched endlessly
in hopes of meeting you in this life♪
♪I've become the light traveling in the dark♪
♪A drop of tear, a pinch of dust♪
♪A journey ends in an instant♪
♪Life is short, but a dream lasts forever♪
♪I've searched endlessly
in hopes of meeting you in this life♪
♪I've become the light traveling in the dark♪
[Are you the Devil God?
Or are you Ming Ye?]
[Are you my enemy]
[or my lover?]
♪Life is short, but a dream lasts forever♪
♪I longed for it for three lifetimes♪
Bravo!
His Majesty?
His Majesty!
Why is His Majesty here?
Your Majesty!
It's His Majesty!
Bravo!
Your Majesty!
It's His Majesty himself!
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
♪Do you know a wise man♪
♪Does not fall in love?♪
♪Even when my heart is torn in two♪
♪I won't fly away♪
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
♪Like blessing, like suffering, it never ends♪
♪I miss you like the sands miss the desert♪
♪O, how I suffered inside♪
[You are no one else.]
[You are Tantai Jin.]
♪I always remember that before the flowers fall♪
♪A young man tried to persuade me with a kiss♪
♪Let's freeze love before it turns to dust♪
It's such a beautiful night.
Wouldn't it be a waste
if we were to get drunk?
How about…
What were you thinking?
I…
The moon is clear and bright tonight.
It's perfect for fox spirits
to cultivate their powers.
I actually forgot about it.
If I don't absorb enough moon essence
in time,
even spirits like us will grow old.
By then, you'll be scared to death
when my hair turns gray,
and my face is full of wrinkles.
Even so,
you're still the cutest to me.
But I'm a mortal.
At most, I can live a hundred years.
I'm afraid I have no chance
to witness that moment.
Actually, there's a simple solution to it.
There's a legend among fox spirits.
Legend has it that if you're married
to your true love,
with a bite on the arm and
a drop of blood as a vow,
even if one of them dies,
their soul will not
head to the underworld.
This way, they can be together forever.
Really?
I haven't tried it before.
How would I know?
Even if that day does come,
I won't give it a try.
I'll drink a lot of wine,
find another man,
and forget about you completely.
If so, I can rest at ease.
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
♪Do you know a wise man♪
♪Does not fall in love?♪
♪Even when my heart is torn in two♪
♪I won't fly away♪
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
Your Majesty!
Miss.
Do you guys want to buy some candy?
Little girl,
were you separated from your parents?
You're so young.
Why are you selling things alone here?
Stop right there.
What are you doing?
I'll buy the whole basket.
Where are your parents?
They're dead.
Come.
Take this pouch
and go to the new orphanage
located at the East Palace Gate.
Find the manager there.
He'll find you a new place to live.
Thank you, mister.
Go now.
Why did you buy so much candy?
To eat.
Your Majesty!
Let's go.
Your Highness,
Tantai Jin hasn't returned
to the palace yet.
Okay. Let's split up and execute the plan.
Your Majesty!
Over there!
They almost found us.
Why were they chasing you?
I guess they want to see me.
See you for what?
I heard that Tantai Wuji
was deserted by his people.
Tantai Minglang was tyrannical
and was killed by a swarm of mice.
The day I entered the capital,
countless mice fled, and the tyrant died.
The news spread and people regarded it
as an auspicious sign.
Later, they even said
that I was a god sent from above.
See, everyone does love you.
They're just following the herd.
Now, they see me as a god.
But they might see me as a devil later.
Why are you belittling yourself like this?
You deserve to be liked by people
after accomplishing a good deed.
I think you just lack compliments.
You'll get used to it
after being praised by us
for a few more years.
[No, I'm afraid
his time is running short.]
[I must destroy the evil bone]
[within one year.]
I don't care
whether people like me or not.
It's enough as long as you like me.
You should have this.
I don't like it.
If so, why did you buy so many of them?
Do you still remember
the previous New Year's Eve?
That was my first time
hanging out on the street.
You bought me a new coat.
It was snowing that day.
And it got dark pretty soon.
On our way home,
we met a woman selling firecrackers.
Ma'am,
please sell all your firecrackers to me.
Miss,
my firecrackers are homemade.
They're not very nice.
It's fine. I like such firecrackers.
Miss, well…
And this. Take it.
Happy Chinese New Year, ma'am.
But Miss…
Back then, I couldn't understand
why you did so.
But now, I can understand why.
Understand what?
♪Rather than wake from this slumber
I'd prefer the dream to last forever♪
I understand how tough it is for the sick.
I understand how miserable it is
for the poor.
I understand sympathy.
And I understand the desire to do good.
I can feel their pain and hardships.
Now,
I just want to do everything I can
to help more people.
For some reason,
ever since I came back from Mohe River
and had you by my side,
it seemed like
I was able to feel more and more emotions.
Suddenly, I was able to appreciate
how beautiful this world was.
[What will happen if I tell him]
[about the evil bone?]
[Maybe]
[he won't turn into the Devil God
on his initiative]
[once he knows the truth.]
[And, I'll be able to be with him forever]
[and protect him.]
[I won't need to turn my
Soul-slaying Teardrop into spikes]
[and stab his heart with them.]
What's wrong?
Tantai Jin,
I think
there's something
you have to know.
What is it?
-Your Majesty!
-I…
Your Majesty!
There you are!
How could you leave the palace
without telling me?
Even if you forbade me from following you,
at least you should notify me.
Miss Xiwu, you're also here.
I guess I'll make a move.
Never mind.
It's getting late.
I'll return with you.
[Forget it.]
[I'll find another chance to tell him.]
Your Majesty.
I have something to discuss with you.
Will you let me stay by your side
if I assist you in capturing
Prince Xuancheng?
[The city gates are open
on the night of the Water Festival.]
[Tonight's the only night
Xiao Lin can enter the city.]
[If he succeeds,
my safety will be guaranteed.]
[If he fails,]
[this will be my gift to Tantai Jin.]
[Either way, it's my win.]
[Seems like the show's about to begin.]
No need to hide. Show yourself.
Miss Bingchang, hush. It's me.
Scholar Pang?
We're running out of time. Let's go!
[If Pang Yizhi is here,]
[that means the plan worked.]
[Xiao Lin is definitely here.]
Xiao Lin.
Now, you're the only survivor
of Sheng Kingdom.
You should cherish your life.
My life means nothing compared to
the calamity our kingdom is facing.
The calamity your kingdom is facing?
Seems more like personal affairs to me.
Miss Bingchang, what's wrong?
[The final winner is still unknown.]
[I can't leave yet.]
Scholar Pang, I can't walk.
You guys can go on without me.
His Highness entrusted you to me.
How could I leave you behind?
Zhong Tai!
Scholar Pang.
Escort Miss Bingchang out of here.
Yes, sir.
Someone! Help!
Stop!
What happened?
There are assassins in the palace!
You must be careful!
Someone's trying to
assassinate Tantai Jin?
Let them go.
Are you going to kill me?
Xiao Lin.
The conflict between the two kingdoms
just ended not long ago.
The world is gradually regaining peace.
If you kill me today,
the two kingdoms will
descend into chaos again.
Countless people will die.
You know that
better than anyone.
That's why you won't kill me.
Why are you here today?
I want you to pull back your troops
and end the war.
A fair request.
But it's a shame.
Today,
you don't get to bargain with me.
You knew I was going to
assassinate you tonight?
Every inch of land is my territory now.
Now, my eyes and ears are everywhere.
My informant will tell me everything,
including when you made your plan
and when you will set off.
Today, Prince Xuancheng,
you came here uninvited.
It would be rude of me
not to give you a warm welcome.
I admit defeat.
Kneel.
Xiao Lin.
Is this all that's left of
the Dragon Guards?
Where are your two trusted followers?
Madam Xuancheng,
where are you going
in the middle of the night?
[Seems like Xiao Lin failed.]
How dare you kidnap me?
Chief Pian, they wanted to kidnap me.
Save me!
You guys heard that, right?
What a bunch of foolish men.
You all can't even figure this out?
Tantai Jin!
Why are you here at such a late hour?
Are you okay? Were you hurt?
Don't worry. I'm fine.
I was terrified.
Look at you. Your hands are freezing.
Do you feel better now?
Xiao Lin?
[Xiao Lin actually
tried to assassinate him?]
[What should I do?]
It's been a long time, Miss Xiwu.
Well…
You'd better not ask me
to show him mercy at this moment.
Thank you for your kindness, Miss Xiwu.
I was aware of the consequences.
Reporting in!
Chief Pian Ran
has intercepted the rebels
who kidnapped Madam Xuancheng.
Your Majesty, don't worry.
Madam Xuancheng is fine.
Good. Tell Pian Ran to bring her here.
I need to ask her something.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Run!
What?
Don't tell me you want me to help you up?
I wasn't on their side.
Please clarify the truth
in front of His Majesty on my behalf.
Is that so?
Why do you possess it?
What do you mean?
Speak!
Why do you possess this love thread?
I don't know!
Let go of me!
I'm a distinguished guest of His Majesty.
I'm going to ask you one last time.
Where did you get that love thread?
Do you really think I'm as stupid as them?
You think
I can't do anything to you
if you don't talk?
Let go.
Pian Ran, calm down.
Don't do anything silly.
Qingyu, she's trying to kill me.
Qingyu.
No matter what my sister has done,
I'll apologize to you on her behalf.
Let's straighten things out first.
I've got nothing
to straighten out with you.
Out of my way!
Get lost.
Get lost!
Pian Ran.
You mentioned something
about a love thread just now.
What exactly is going on?
It's none of your business.
How could that be?
Chief, His Majesty has ordered you
to bring Madam Xuancheng to the main hall.
Sir, I failed to complete my mission.
How come?
Miss Bingchang claimed that
we kidnapped her.
She was unwilling to leave with us.
Why would Xiao Lin
fall for someone like her?
Scholar Pang,
what should we do now?
Leave the capital in small groups
as per His Highness's instruction.
After that, join up with
Chen Xian's main force.
Yes, sir.
Let's go.
Prince Xuancheng,
it might be too sentimental for you
to meet your wife in a foreign land.
Why don't you wait behind the hall
for a while?
Please.
What's the matter?
I'll keep an eye on him for you.
Were you hurt?
Out of all the things to do,
why did you put your neck into the noose?
Reporting in!
Chief Pian Ran, General Ye,
and Madam Xuancheng are here
to seek an audience.
Let them in.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[In the end, Bingchang still
couldn't make it out.]
Madam Xuancheng contributed the most
to the assassins' capture tonight.
She deserves the highest award.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I'm honored to resolve
your troubles for you.
I…
dare not take credit for it.
What does that mean?
What has Bingchang
got to do with this operation?
You sent Xiao Lin a letter
with encrypted messages
to make him believe that
your life was in danger.
You asked for his help urgently
with the letter you wrote.
A chivalrous man like Xiao Lin
would definitely
come to your rescue personally.
This is a devious scheme that
takes advantage of human nature.
You have outdone most of my advisers.
I'm flattered, Your Majesty.
But I'm curious about something.
What if Xiao Lin succeeded
in assassinating me tonight?
Would you swim with the current
and leave together with him?
Your Majesty, please give us
your wise judgment.
I had cut off all ties with Xiao Lin
ever since I came back from Sheng Kingdom.
Bingchang, you…
[Till The End of the Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪