♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 5]
[As long as they can't kill you,]
[you can use their power.]
Power.
So,
this is
what power feels like.
[Since those demons can give me power,]
[why don't I]
[live a different life?]
[Little Devil God almost]
[killed himself in his nightmare.]
[Could it be
he still doesn't want to live now?]
Tantai Jin.
What are you doing?
[Perfect timing.]
[I'll test my power with you.]
Miss Xiwu,
what do you think I'm doing?
Miss!
Someone, please help!
Mr. Tantai killed Miss Xiwu!
Tantai Jin?
Miss Xiwu?
What do you think I'm doing?
You're not doing needlework, are you?
I need to use your scissors.
I gotta trim my nails.
Miss,
I trimmed your nails just a few days ago.
You didn't trim them well.
Ye Xiwu,
it's you who took away
my dagger in my dream.
Of course.
Who else do you think it was?
Miss,
the doctor said
you almost injured your tendons.
You need to rest properly.
Don't trim your nails carelessly.
[How am I supposed to convince him?]
[Tantai Jin, you can't die.]
[Forget it.]
[From now on,]
[let's find a way to watch him closely.]
[And convince him
with emotions and reason.]
Tantai Jin,
I heard my sister
had also come to herself.
Do you wanna go see her?
No.
Taking a walk in the garden
will liven your mood.
Let's go.
Come on.
She'll be fine.
From what I see, Miss Ye
has the fate of
"ivy twining around tree trunk".
With you, the tall tree, as her shield,
she will be blessed
and survive the crisis.
Since you care for her so much,
why don't you ask
His Highness to grant your wish?
I do have my concerns
about not giving my word to Bingchang.
In people's eyes,
I'm the luckiest man alive.
I can have everything
without moving my hands.
But everything
isn't as simple as it seems.
You're worried that being the Prince Lin,
if you marry a Ye who controls the army,
there will only be more suspicion.
You read my mind.
But this is indeed difficult.
But,
you've already decided, haven't you?
Prince Lin.
Prince Lin, Miss has awakened.
Your Highness,
when I was taken by that demon,
I was so scared of
not being able to see you again.
Bingchang.
Since I first saw you at that banquet,
I had something I wanted to say to you.
How I regret
that I didn't say it earlier.
What did you want to say?
I'm willing to die if we can be together.
Together, we'll have the sweetest life.
Don't cry.
I'm also in love with you.
You're a distinguished prince,
but I'm just a concubine's daughter.
When I gave my heart to you,
I'll never love anyone else in this life.
Rest assured,
I won't fail your love.
I'll have a proper arrangement for you.
We're both each other's love.
You deserve
a justifiable status.
Bingchang,
have good rest and get better.
I'll be back for you.
Okay.
I'll be waiting for you.
[He might feel happier]
[when he meets his loved one.]
[Oh no.]
[How come Prince Lin is here too?]
[Wouldn't the love rivals
make things worse?]
[I'd better take
Little Devil God out of here.]
Prince Tantai.
Miss Xiwu.
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
I'm okay.
Nothing serious now.
Thank you and Dragon Guard
for sending us back.
Bye.
Miss Xiwu,
there's something
I need to talk about with you alone.
Prince Tantai, would you excuse us?
Okay.
Don't go too far.
Please go ahead, Your Highness.
The succubus crisis
helped me see clearly
my love for Bingchang.
After I return to the palace today,
I'll report this to His Majesty
and ask him to grant our marriage.
I'm flattered that you're fond of me,
but I hope that in the future, you will…
Accept this reality
and stop badgering you?
Actually I…
Never mind, it's too complicated.
Anyway, you may rest assured.
We won't disturb each other's lives.
We'll go our separate ways.
There'll be nothing shady.
I hope you can keep your word.
Got it.
[This Ye Xiwu]
[really seems to be a different person.]
[She's not obsessed with Xiao Lin.]
[She even specially cares about my life.]
[Don't freeze to death]
[There's another thing.]
[It's about Prince Tantai.]
Tantai Jin?
What's up with him?
It's really lucky for Prince Tantai
to be able to return unharmed.
If something happened to him
not only the Ye family,
but the whole world
could be in trouble.
Why are you saying so?
Looks like Miss Xiwu
knows little about state affairs.
Tantai Jin is a hostage from Jing Kingdom.
As a Tantai,
his life is bonded
with the fate of his nation.
If anything happens to him,
it'll give Jing Kingdom
an excuse to attack us.
Sheng has been losing
military talents these years.
It's definitely not a good time for war.
By then, despite His Majesty would punish
the Ye family for dereliction of duty,
once the war breaks out,
all males of Ye family
must go to the frontline,
which is a disaster for your own family.
Once the fire of war ravaged the field,
causing severe deaths to normal people,
and will be a catastrophe for everyone.
I'm gonna keep an eye on him.
So that's how it is.
[Prince Tantai left his homeland]
[to be a guest in our Sheng Kingdom.]
[He did it for the peace of two kingdoms.]
[And also for keeping the civilians
away from the agony of war.]
[We should treat him politely.]
[How can you bully him without scruples?]
Turns out, Xiao Lin cared about me
so that his kingdom can be safe.
Ye Xiwu cares about me
so that her family could be safe.
In their eyes,
I'm just a jinx who only brings disasters.
Do you mean anything more
when you say, "keep an eye on him"?
Prince Lin,
I don't wanna lie to you.
But I can't explain it to you further.
Honestly,
I hate Tantai Jin
more than anyone else.
[I wanna kill him even in my dreams.]
[I even wished]
[he never existed in this world.]
But rest assured,
I won't let him die.
But if you want me
to truly care about him,
it's impossible.
Ye Xiwu,
you finally told the truth.
All your performance in front of me
was just for your own benefit.
Turns out
you're no different from them.
[I actually thought]
[someone would really care about me.]
Father,
the eldest daughter
of General Ye and I have been in love.
Would you grant my wish
to marry her?
Do you really love her?
For a lifetime.
Lin,
don't say it too soon.
What exactly do you love about her?
Her looks,
or her mind?
Looks will eventually fade away,
and people's minds will also change.
Nothing in this world
can let love last.
Father,
I don't know exactly why I love Bingchang.
Since childhood,
everything I did had a proper reason,
except falling in love with her.
I am following my heart
for no reason at all.
What a surprise.
There's actually someone in this world
who can break you out of your norm.
Alright,
let me think about it.
Thanks, Father.
Miss.
Miss,
I got some news.
What is it?
There's an edict from the palace
asking Mrs. Ye to see His Majesty.
Miss,
could it be anything about your marriage?
After Prince Lin went back,
he must have asked His Majesty
to grant marriage to you two.
But Her Ladyship favors Miss Xiwu,
if she says something
in front of His Majesty…
Jiahui, don't say it like that.
Xiwu has already been married.
It's a done deal.
No matter how much Grandma favors her,
there's no reason for her
to stop my marriage.
Miss,
you haven't realized how complex it is.
Think about it,
ever since you were a child,
be it clothes, jewelry,
food or things to enjoy,
when Miss Xiwu gets something,
you don't necessarily have it.
But if it's something even she can't have,
have you ever had it?
Miss…
[Ye's Residence]
You Great General Ye Xiao's eldest daughter
who's known for her graceful appearance,
gentle character,
kind heart,
and etiquette-conforming behaviors,
therefore I grant her the title of
Side Concubine of Prince Xuancheng.
The end.
I accept and thank
His Majesty's graciousness.
General Ye, Grand Princess Royal,
please rise now.
Mr. Attendant,
I wonder who this Prince Xuancheng is.
His Majesty issued two edicts today.
The other one
is to grant Prince Lin the title of
Prince Xuancheng.
Blessings come in pairs, right?
I see.
Mom, look.
Our Bingchang is such a lucky girl.
Even His Majesty cares about her.
Thanks for coming.
Please come in and have some tea.
Please.
Ye Bingchang is truly gentle and virtuous.
No wonder Lin likes her so much.
Isn't this a good thing?
Why did you sigh, Your Majesty?
Good thing?
Ye Xiao enjoys
a high reputation in the army.
His second son, Ye Qingyu,
who guards Jia Pass,
is not to be underestimated.
How can I not be worried?
It's rare for Lin
to ask something from me.
If this Ye woman becomes his first wife,
she's probably
gonna be the Queen of Sheng.
He doesn't want to fail his woman,
but I must consider the future of Sheng.
This is the dilemma of being a king.
I'm telling you Ye Bingchang,
no matter what you do
you're always the daughter of a concubine.
I just need to have a word with Grandma,
and you will
only deserve to be a concubine.
[Miss,]
[ever since you're a child,]
[when Miss Xiwu has something,]
[you don't necessarily have it.]
[But if it's something
even she can't have,]
[have you ever had it?]
Miss,
don't be upset.
Jiahui,
I really don't understand.
I've studied hard for years.
I'm good at needlework.
Every word I say, every movement I make,
I can't be more cautious about them.
I'm as obedient as I can possibly be.
But what exactly have I done wrong?
Why?
Why would it end up like today?
Miss,
you haven't done anything wrong.
You can only blame
the foul difference
between a wife and a concubine.
I don't understand.
We're both daughters of the Ye family.
Why do this to me?
[So I must be Xiao Lin's legal wife.]
[I must.]
Your Highness,
please allow me to inform her.
Your Highness, you can't…
Your Highness, how come…
Bingchang,
I obviously requested
to marry you as my wife.
But I didn't expect…
Your Highness,
Bingchang knows her place.
Actually, being able to marry you,
is already enough for me.
Bingchang,
you really don't have to force a smile.
You can just tell me
you're disappointed
that you can't be my wife.
Bingchang,
although you never cried
or complained to me,
I always knew
how you'd been treated in Ye's Residence
and how you concealed your grievances.
Now seeing an edict like this,
you must be so sad.
Don't you think that
I'm asking for things that are not mine?
That I desire too much?
So what if you do?
Isn't love
a kind of desire?
No woman in this world
doesn't want to
be the wife of their loved one.
Besides, you never harmed anyone else.
I want to be the husband of you,
instead of the husband of a saint.
All your depression and disappointment
are your true feelings,
which I can't cherish enough.
Why would I blame you for that?
♪No more talk of leaving or staying♪
♪Silence is the best cure♪
♪One who wants to
Get drunk needs no alcohol♪
Your Highness.
Bingchang.
Actually I'm not worth you doing this.
No more thoughts like that.
You're the kindest
and most beautiful girl in the world.
The position of my legal wife
will always be reserved for you.
I will give you a wedding
just as grand as marrying my wife.
From now on, be it happiness or hardships,
we're in this together.
[The grand wedding.]
[Ye Xiwu, Xiao Liang, Ye Zeyu,
Gao Jie, Qiu Yu, Cheng Peng]
[Enemies don't live under the same sky.]
[Time to settle the scores.]
[Xuancheng Palace]
Congrats!
[Emperor's Son-in-law, Gao Jie.]
[Gao Jie]
[Marquis of Jinling, Qiu Yu.]
[Qiu Yu]
[Princess Yongxing's son, Cheng Peng.]
[Cheng Peng]
Pillar of the State Great General is here!
Lord Ye, you're here.
Greetings.
Thank you for your congratulation.
You've learned
to play rogue with your masters.
Believe it or not I'm gonna beat you now!
[Pillar of the State Great General's son,
Ye Zeyu.]
[Ye Zeyu]
Tantai Jin!
I finally found you.
Where have you been?
I haven't seen you for quite a while.
[I hate Tantai Jin more than anyone else.]
[I wanna kill him even in my dreams.]
Why are you looking at me like this?
Is there anything on my face?
[Pillar of the State Great General's
daughter, Ye Xiwu.]
[Ye Xiwu]
What a lively day today.
All the high officials and nobles
in the capital are here.
There's one less.
Which one?
[He's coming.]
Whose little brat is this?
How dare you block my way?
Get lost.
My Lord,
she's still a child.
Sorry for getting in your way.
Please have mercy
and let us go.
Alright.
I won't mind being offended by her.
I'll kowtow to you.
But,
today's the big day for my sixth brother.
And there's someone crying out loud
in front of his gate.
This is so unlucky.
It's our fault.
Guards, do something!
My Lord, please spare my life!
Dad!
Please spare my dad!
[Prince Wuning, Xiao Liang.]
[Xiao Liang.]
Dad!
He's bleeding!
That's lucky!
Dad!
Terrific. Let's go.
Greetings, Prince Liang.
Prince Wuning is here!
Save it.
[He's the Prince Liang]
[who has been bullying Tantai Jin.]
Did I come late
or did you guys come early?
Of course, it's us who came early.
Well well, hostage Tantai is also here!
And Miss Xiwu, too!
Ever since you
and the hostage got married,
you look prettier than before, Miss Xiwu!
Greetings, Prince Wuning.
Save the etiquette.
Hostage,
Jing Kingdom regards
black as the noble color.
You're all dressed up today.
Are you here
on behalf of the wife's family?
Today seems like a fun day!
Where is the fun?
I've seen how you
desperately pursued Ye Bingchang.
How does it feel?
Seeing the woman you love
becoming someone else's bride?
You must feel terrible, huh?
Xiao Lin is a prince.
You are also a prince.
He gets both power and beauty.
But your life is worse than a dog's.
I'm sure at this moment
you must feel like hell in there, right?
[Is Little Devil God gonna lose it?]
Prince Wuning,
did you eat pickles for breakfast?
Why is your mouth so foul?
Ye Xiwu!
You!
How dare you talk to me like this?
Prince Liang.
You asked how I felt just now.
I feel happy for them of course.
Coward.
Even a dog from Jing Kingdom
has more guts than you!
Farewell.
What did you say?
I said, Prince Liang,
farewell.
You do know the rules better than before.
Go.
Tantai Jin,
don't take his words to heart.
He's just a despicable person.
Miss Xiwu,
there you are.
Scholar Pang.
What good stuff are you holding?
It's a wedding gift from the sect leader
of Xiaoyao Sect, who
told me to send to Prince Lin.
Heart-guarding Scale?
Miss Xiwu,
do you even know about this?
It's a chest scale from the dragon race.
It's super tough.
It can protect you from all evil.
This is a secret treasure of our sect.
I wonder why the old man
is so generous this time.
Tan…
The auspicious time has come.
Please welcome Prince Xuancheng,
and Side Concubine of Prince Xuancheng!
First bow to heaven and earth!
Second bow to thank His Majesty!
Husband and wife bow to each other!
The ritual is finished!
Good!
What a perfect couple!
So wonderful!
Where does this crow come from?
Why is there a crow here?
Miserable people of a dying kingdom,
how long will your good days last?
The crows are about to land.
Whose roof will they land on?
What does this mean?
I don't know.
How can it talk?
Did it just talk?
Prince Liang, are you alright?
Crows everywhere! Run!
Quickly!
[Ye Xiwu, Xiao Liang, Ye Zeyu,
Gao Jie, Qiu Yu, Cheng Peng]
[Xiao Liang]
Dad!
Watch out!
Your Highness,
take the Heart-guarding Scale!
Escort Side Concubine out first!
Leave here to me. Now!
Thanks, Junior Sect Uncle!
Go, Bingchang.
[Gao Jie, Qiu Yu, Cheng Peng]
Wait here for a while in this side hall.
I'll come back for you
when I save the guests.
Please don't go! I'm scared!
But the people outside…
I don't care.
I just want you by my side.
Bingchang, listen to me.
The people outside
are either guests attending our wedding
or my guards and servants.
I can't just leave them to danger.
Are they more important than me?
I'm your newly-married wife!
How can you
leave me behind to save others?
Bingchang, trust me.
You're going to be fine.
Wait for me.
[Ye Xiwu]
My face!
Help me!
Zeyu!
[You actually know how to use charms.]
Go!
[Ye Xiwu,]
[you really surprise me.]
[Xuancheng Palace]
It's fine.
-Come on.
-My legs!
Go now, Zeyu!
Faster!
Zeyu!
What happened to you?
It hurts!
[Where's Little Devil God? Still inside?]
Dad, I'm disfigured!
You'll be fine. Let's go!
[If anything happens to Little Devil God,]
Come on!
[we'll be doomed.]
Listen to me!
Come on!
My legs hurt. I can't walk, Dad!
What? What's wrong with your legs?
Xiwu, you can't…
Dad!
-I can't let Xiwu go in there!
-I'm already dying!
Dad!
So this is the taste of vengeance, huh?
Doesn't feel like too much fun.
Tantai Jin!
You did this!
This is the Heart-guarding Scale.
Miss Bingchang,
keep your wedding gift.
I wish you
a merry wedding.
Okay.
[Oh no.]
[I've used up all my charms.]
[Even if I had the power to kill anyone,]
[I didn't feel
any fluctuation in my heart.]
[Except at that moment,]
[Ye Xiwu]
[in which I felt something different.]
Tantai Jin!
[Ye Xiwu?]
[I've let you go.]
[But you won't let me go?]
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
♪That's about to fall
From the edge of the sky♪
♪I wanna hang a glittering butterfly there
Till the snow falls♪
♪I wanna hang it in a wrong time
To forget my everything♪
♪I wanna hang a dream there
And trade you with a drop of tear♪
♪Hearts burn like flames♪
♪Why don't we just be like this
For ten thousand years?♪
♪Let's freeze time before we say goodbye♪
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
This is great!
Tantai Jin,
you're not dead, and I'm not dead.
We both survived!
♪My heart won't fly away♪
♪Do you know that look you gave me♪
[Ye Xiwu, didn't you hate me?]
[How could you sacrifice your life]
[in order to save me?]
This is such a serious incident,
but the culprit is still unknown!
Your Majesty,
this thing is quite weird.
The crows were conjured by some demon.
They were quite fierce,
but none of the guests were killed.
Most of them fainted
or got pecked on their faces.
These creatures
must be secretly manipulated by someone.
This culprit harbors evil designs.
I shall never tolerate him!
Investigate!
Keep investigating!
The culprit must be found!
Yes!
[So, the power I devoured from the demons]
[will eventually run out.]
[If I know how to cultivate]
[like Xiao Lin does,]
[I'll be able to sustain my power]
[without devouring demons.]
[I wonder if that sect…]
Tantai Jin!
Did you get injured somewhere?
Let me check.
We've been through life and death.
Don't be shy.
I'm not injured.
Even Xiao Lin,
who got excellent swordsmanship,
has multiple injuries.
While you remain unharmed?
Are you suspecting me?
No.
I was just saying
you're lucky.
Because I know
if you want to live, you gotta hide.
Unlike someone who ran around
like a headless fly.
I did that to save you!
You little ingrate!
If I didn't run faster,
you'd be killed by the birds.
Why did you come back for me?
Because I'm kind, duh.
I'd do the same for anyone else.
Back then everyone was
running out of the mansion.
Did you especially come back
just to save me?
I…
Because I love you, alright?
A couple should look out for each other.
Saving you is what
I'm supposed to do, huh?
You love me?
Just like in the novels,
in the beginning we didn't see eye to eye,
but eventually we grew fond of each other.
You saved me because of love?
What is love exactly?
Love is…
Love is you don't want him to die.
You wanna stay with him.
You'll be worried if you don't see him.
You'll be happy if you do.
[I'm sorry, Little Devil God.]
[I didn't mean to lie to you.]
[Love,]
[compared with power,]
[is truly something not worth mentioning.]
Alright.
If you love me,
why don't you teach me how to draw charms?
This way, we can spend more time together.
Why do you wanna learn that?
Because I want to be like you,
capable of protecting my loved one.
[Little Devil God actually has
someone he wants to protect now.]
Okay.
I'll teach you how to draw charms,
and you promise me to live on.
I don't wanna save you with my life again.
Okay.
[Ye Xiwu]
What are you doing here?
My words count.
I'm here to fulfill my promise of course.
Teach me.
What should I teach you…
The one you used to repel the crows
at Xiao Lin's that day.
Not that one.
That spell is too dangerous.
You're just an amateur,
and if you mess the charm up,
you might blow up the house.
[It's always wise to play safe.]
[Because you are Tantai Jin,]
[I will never teach you spells
that can kill.]
Then what are you going to teach me?
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I’ve seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel,
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪