The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 27]
You've been standing here all night.
Your Majesty.
Your injuries haven't healed yet.
Would she have died
if Pian Ran and Ye Qingyu
had been there a little late.
The doctor said
she had been so close to death.
I ask her to live well,
she should do as she's told.
Her life belongs to me.
Without my permission,
she mustn't die.
Your Majesty.
Someone asks to see you.
Ask him to go.
It's Pang Yizhi.
He said he had to see you.
Scholar Pang, what did you come for?
Your Majesty, you've addressed me wrongly.
Sheng Kingdom has been conquered,
so I'm not Senior Chamberlain Pang
of the Sheng
but a disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.
I came to make divination for you
to exchange for one thing.
What's the thing?
Don't you want to know
what the divination is about?
No.
Emperor Jin.
I can't hold anything back,
so I have to say it
whether it's good or ill luck,
or I'm gonna explode.
From the divination image,
you'll suddenly lose your love
and regret in your entire life.
Cannot reclaim your love
and be trapped in the underworld.
It seems you don't want
your tongue anymore.
Emperor Jin.
Be patient.
I haven't finished my words.
There are two chances showed
in the divination image.
One is about thunder.
The other is about water.
What do you mean?
You know,
I'm not proficient.
Sorry I can't explain it.
What do you want to exchange it for?
I want a bottle of your heart blood.
Scholar Pang.
What makes you
think I would give it
to you
after hearing your nonsense?
You have the whole world under you.
Of course, I'm not fully confident
that you would give it.
However, I have a thunder-series artifact.
If you give me your heart blood,
I'll repay you with it.
What's it?
This is Yin-Yang Twin Bracelets,
made from thunder iron.
It's an artifact of Xiaoyao Sect.
When two people wear one of the bracelets,
the owner of Ying bracelet won't die
if the owner of Yang bracelet is alive.
The reason is
that the lifespan
of the owner of Yang bracelet
has offset the disasters
of the owner of Ying bracelet.
Yet, once you put on the bracelet,
you won't take it off.
[Offset the disasters.]
I want to offer the artifact
in return for your heart blood.
Pang Yizhi.
What do you want the blood for?
It has nothing to do with you, your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
We don't know his purpose.
Besides, your heart is injured.
I beg you to think well.
Nian Baiyu.
Dagger.
Thanks.
[Xiao Lin.]
[I've been practicing
martial arts]
[and learning divination for many years.]
[What is it for?]
[I can't change what has happened]
[or save my friends.]
[You're my friend.]
[Now I'll make divination]
[for you.]
Xiao Lin.
If you were still alive,
you would certainly admonish me
when I want to do this.
Now that you're in the underworld,
you can't stop me.
Just let me do what I want to.
[From now on, our fates have become one.]
Are you fine, your Majesty?
Take her pulse again.
Your Majesty.
Her pulse is recovering quickly.
She'll wake up in a few hours.
You can leave.
Yes.
Your Majesty, are you okay?
When Ye Xiwu wakes up,
lock her up in Chilly Ward.
No one is allowed to visit.
She's now my weakness.
If she's killed,
my life span will be deducted.
Yes.
Remember,
don't talk about the bracelets to anyone,
including Ye Xiwu.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
And what do you want to do
with Ye Bingchang?
Have you found
why she tried to kill Ye Xiwu?
She said Ye Xiwu caused Xiao Lin's death.
As Xiao Lin's widow,
she wanted to avenge his death.
The person who killed Xiao Lin
was not Ye Xiwu，
but me.
Don't kill her.
Put her in the dungeon.
Don't let her go unless she dies.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Why does Pang Yizhi want your heart blood?
I think he's up to no good.
And I'm afraid this thing
will be bad to you.
Your Majesty.
I beg you.
Please take care of your health.
I don't care about it.
[What did you put in it?]
Dry mylabris.
[If someone eats it,]
he would surly die.
[You made this porridge for me?]
[No, Tantai Jin.]
[I didn't want to kill you.]
[It's wrong...]
[Li Susu.]
[Are you giving up?]
[This is]
[Barren Abyss.]
[Li Susu.]
[Ji Ze.]
[I failed to kill Devil God.]
[I've let down your trust.]
[Sorry.]
You not only feel guilty to me,
but also feel guilty to Tantai Jin.
Right?
[Guilty?]
I'm surprised
that he was convinced
that I wanted to poison him
but he still wanted to marry me
and be with me forever.
Ji Ze.
Whether he is a demon or a god,
since he loves me deeply,
how can I not be guilty?
[Silly...]
[I tell you,]
[even if so many people]
[hadn't died because of]
[you and Tantai Jin,]
[this would be how you and Tantai Jin end.]
Li Susu.
In your lifetime,
the fate of you two has already been doomed.
Whatever you do, you won't change it.
If you don't want to owe him,
you have to owe the world.
In Barren Abyss,
I mentioned
a dream, a drop of tear
and a strand of silk.
Have you understood them?
The tear is Soul-slaying Teardrop.
The silk is the affection silk
of Tantai Jin.
The dream...
Is it Bo're Life?
Since you've guessed right,
why haven't you woken up yet?
What do you mean?
What are you doing?
Sang Jiu.
I'll take the punishment for you.
When my immortal body vanishes,
my divine essence
will replace your demon bone.
Ming Ye.
Let go of me!
The divine essence
will replace the demon bone.
Everything happens for a reason.
Don't indulge in foolishness.
Seize the chance.
[The divine essence
will replace the demon bone.]
[If he loses the evil bone,]
[Devil God won't return to life.]
[With the power of the thunder,]
[Ming Ye replaced my demon bone
with his divine essence.]
[So similarly, I can replace evil bone
with divine essence.]
[But now my body has no power,]
[let alone divine essence.]
[What should I do?]
[That hurts.]
[With my weak body,]
[how can I build divine essence]
[to trigger thundering?]
It's a gem
that I forged with the divine essence
of the entire Flying Serpent clan.
This tiny piece
contains the powers of immortals.
It's capable
of overturning heaven and earth.
Why don't I call it
World-overturning Jade?
[World-overturning Jade.]
[That explains it.]
[That's the succession
of cause and effect.]
[What's this place?]
[This place looks so familiar.]
[I feel I've been here.]
[This is where Tantai Jin lived
when he was little.]
[This is Chilly Ward.]
[Have you ever seen your mom?]
[I haven't either.]
[They say I don't have mom.]
[Yue Ruanruan.]
You're awake.
How are you feeling?
Here.
Eat the medicine.
What's the bracelet for?
Why can't I take it off?
I don't know it.
It looks like a divine weapon or artifact.
Did Tantai Jin put it on you
to stop you from escaping?
I won't escape.
Then eat the medicine
and get well.
Being alive is the most important thing.
They said you didn't eat or drink.
I thought you didn't want medicine
but want to die.
How can it be?
Good.
I've lived for so long
and have known
that where there is life,
there is hope.
Cheer up.
[If I go all out to absorb power
from World-overturning Jade,]
[I'll definitely be retaliated heavily.]
[Even if I die,]
[I mustn't die]
[before completing these thing.]
[Ji Ze's barrier won't last long.]
[I have to speed up.]
[Your Majesty.]
[This is the elixir refined
by the warlocks today.]
Your life is reduced for Ye Xiwu.
I'll make the warlocks refine elixirs
day and night
to extend your life.
This is a drop in the bucket.
But it's might be good.
If I'm still alive,
Ye Xiwu won't die.
She mustn't die.
I'm not done with her.
Your Majesty.
It seems Ye Xiwu
doesn't want to suicide anymore.
She ate the meals we sent today.
Did she?
Yes, your Majesty.
Why don't you go see her?
Ask her about the origin of the spikes,
so that we can find out
how to pull them out.
Nian Baiyu.
As long as she's alive,
I don't want to know if she has meals
or anything like that.
I'm not interested.
Yes.
[What a pity.]
[When I'm retaliated by World-overturning Jade,]
[I won't see the stars clearly.]
[Will I]
[not be able to see his face clearly?]
[Tantai Jin.]
[I've owed you in the lifetime.]
[But now my life]
[doesn't belong only to me anymore.]
[I will]
[repay you with my life.]
[As expected,]
[with World-overturning Jade,]
[my cultivation has advanced considerably.]
[If I speed it up,]
[the divine essence
should be completed soon.]
[It was almost there.]
His Majesty has been
working diligently lately.
Old guys like us can't keep up with him, huh?
But isn't His Majesty too harsh with
regulating us officials lately?
[Chenming Hall]
My heart already belongs to you.
It's more than a bad mood.
His Majesty seems
to have health issues these days.
Could the rumor be true that His Majesty's
meridians are badly injured and will die soon?
Don't say that.
Stop talking nonsense. Let's go.
This puppetry spell
is recorded in Yiyue Tribe's ancient books.
But it usually can only control one person.
After I improve it with Chixiao Sect's
instrument forging methods,
you will be able to control thousands.
Mighty Ruo Water,
control the souls.
Wake up.
These civilians King Sheng sent us
will be your soldiers to fight for you
and listen to your commands.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
With the ten thousand Nether Soldiers,
our great plan will definitely succeed.
Your Majesty,
recently in the southern borders,
suspicious people have been seen again.
They turn civilians into puppet demonic soldiers
and wreak havoc everywhere.
They are large in number
and no longer small groups like before.
Did you find out who's behind this?
According to the scouts,
the southern borders are covered by miasma.
The source of these demonic soldiers
seems to be deep in the poisonous miasma.
They can't probe deeper.
Since only Sheng civilians are involved,
most ministers think this can be ignored.
Although they are remnants of Sheng,
they're people of Jing now.
Go investigate immediately.
Yes.
Your Majesty,
there's another thing.
What is it?
Ye Xiwu was found unconscious
on the ground this morning.
Now she has come to herself.
We couldn't find out the cause.
We can only presume it's due to her weak body.
Also,
her hearing seems to have declined.
And she has poor eyesight.
Could be due to long time of living indoors.
Your Majesty, please send a doctor to treat her.
No need to report
as long as she's not dead.
Why is the water filled?
When did this happen?
Congratulations, your spell is completed.
Now with the Ruo Water Puppets to fight for you,
you can devour the demonic energy without limit.
You can definitely kill Tantai Jin
and get back to the throne.
You don't need to comfort me.
I'm perfectly aware.
Swallowing the demonic elixir
and devouring the demonic energy
is the cause of me looking like this now.
My days are numbered.
I'll die soon.
All this is because I don't accept my fate.
I'll do anything
to fulfill my ambition.
But you...
You've been following me since I was young.
I must thank you.
I've been following you
since you were young
and weren't made crown prince.
I'm willing to follow you till the end.
Spread the news that I'm on the southern borders.
When Tantai Jin knows,
he'll definitely come personally.
I'll drag him into hell with me.
This fight of me and him
won't stop till death.
It can never be reconciled.
Since you have such resolution,
you'll definitely make it.
I'm willing to assist you with my life.
My men, listen!
Let's go to war!
Your Majesty,
we've found that the mastermind behind the
demonic soldiers is indeed Tantai Minglang.
Now he's hiding on the southern borders
and control civilians with demonic spells.
He gathered ten thousand puppets
and has a demonic woman cultivator with him.
According to the chamberlains of Sheng palace,
it was this woman who advised King Sheng
to hold rituals with your mother's bones.
I shall
personally
fight this war.
Wise decision!
With the World-overturning Jade's side effects,
my body can't last for too long.
I'm about to forge the immortal essence.
With it, I'll be able to trigger
the lightning punishment.
Hope there's still time.
Your Majesty,
according to the refugees who got out,
thick fog has started to appear a few days ago.
And the people in it
will lose contact with the outside world.
This should be
Tantai Minglang's place of demonic cultivation.
Your Majesty,
there should be a lot of trapped civilians inside.
I've sent men go probe in there first.
The troops will pass after safety is confirmed.
What is going on?
What's that?
Let them out now.
Something's not right.
This fog is poisonous.
I'll go rescue them.
The poisonous miasma is too dangerous to go in.
Oh my third brother,
you're so wary.
But the entire southern borders
have been turned into a poisonous fortress.
I guarantee that anyone comes shall not return.
Your abilities to control little animals
won't be of use in here.
Let this place be your
burial ground.
This terrain is quite dangerous.
I'm afraid Tantai Minglang has troops in ambush.
I must first clear the poisonous miasma
to reduce our casualties.
What? What's going on?
What happened?
Look! What's that?
It's the miasma.
It has dispersed!
Your Majesty.
Looks like the rumor is true.
His heart and meridians are truly injured.
Let me see
how long your injured heart can last.
Spread my order.
Whoever kills Tantai Jin
shall be a marquis.
Kill Tantai Jin!
We mustn't fight a protracted war.
The southern borders are full of dangers.
We have to keep our morale up
by fighting a quick battle.
Baiyu,
follow me closely.
Yes.
Protect His Majesty.
Charge!
Tantai Jin is eager to save his people.
He's forcing out his power.
Let's just let him show off for now.
When his power runs out,
my preparations will about to be finished.
Fu Yu,
I'll go first.
You come later.
Tantai Jin,
let's see how many people you can save.
You'll regret it
after you occupied the poisonous fortress.
Why isn't General Ye at the battle ground?
His Majesty already secured multiple victories.
But you're here wielding your weapon.
Does His Majesty not trust you?
That's not true.
His Majesty told me to guard the capital
in case the rebels launch a sneak attack.
Tantai Minglang is a treacherous one.
His Majesty gives this important mission to me.
It means he trusts me.
Then you're literally sleeping with your weapon.
Well, I'm different.
I just wanna stay in the capital to slack.
Chief Pian Ran, don't you know
if I'm sleeping with my weapon or not?
Ye Qingyu,
you've become good at smooth-talking.
Focus on your practice.
I'll go check at the city gates.
Look at those dark clouds.
How unusual.
There's thunder.
The lightning punishment is coming.
Ye Xiwu, you must hang on.
The sky looks weird.
No, it's not.
This seems like an ominous sign.
Is His Majesty suffering a defeat in the war?
We've only lived a few peaceful days.
Don't tell me...
News of victory!
With His Majesty taking the lead,
our troops smashed into enemy territory.
We will conquer the poisonous fortress soon.
We've captured more than 3,000 rebels
and saved over 10,000 civilians.
Is today some kind of festival?
Why's everybody so excited?
Don't you know it yet?
The rebel Tantai Minglang has been defeated.
Your Highness,
I've found a side door to the old town
at the northwest corner of the Jing capital.
Since it's being retrofitted lately,
few people go through it
and there aren't many guards there.
What's your business?
Material delivery.
Stop for a routine inspection.
You don't look familiar.
Are you carrying any prohibited goods?
Enemy attack!
Tantai Jin,
I didn't expect there's someone
you actually care for in this world.
I'm surprised.
It's the thunder.
I'm about to break through.
What happened?
Run!
Tantai Jin,
I'm coming.
Your Highness,
the gate to the Jing capital is open.
You'll achieve your ambition very soon.
Well done.
Where do these burglars come from?
How dare you trespass my territory?
A fox spirit wants to guard Tantai Jin's city?
I like eating black-hearted demons the most.
A mixture of human and demon like you
perfectly suits my taste.
Your Highness,
the Ruo Water Puppets are ready.
Mighty Ruo Water, control her soul.
Please enter the palace first.
Leave this fox spirit to me.
Try your best.
Yes.
Go.
Slay our way in!
Attack!
Don't hurt the innocent civilians!
Are you being serious with me?
Demon-hunting Crossbow!
Fu Yu!
Ye Qingyu!
Pian Ran, look at me.
I got something to say to you.
I've failed my kingdom and family.
Now I die for protecting the civilians
and protecting my loved one.
This death is worth it.
What are you talking about?
You won't die.
I won't let you die.
Ye Qingyu.
I thought
I would never be as good as Jiang Rao.
Because he's already dead.
He'll live in your heart forever.
I didn't expect that now I'm also...
Ye Qingyu,
you're not Jiang Rao.
You don't need to be Jiang Rao.
You are Ye Qingyu.
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
♪True love is rare though♪
Pian Ran,
if only I could meet you
earlier.
♪While the fireworks of life
are short-lived and easily enjoyed♪
♪But this time, who will come and go♪
So I can fall in love with you earlier.
To dote on you.
Pian Ran,
spirits live much longer than humans.
Will you still remember me
after a few hundred years?
You jerk!
If you dare to die,
I'll forget everything about you!
Just forget about me.
Don't feel sad for me.
After living the best days of my life with you,
there's nothing I regret when I leave the world.
What a shame.
We
can't leave the world together.
♪Watching the nebulae cycle by
I've long let go♪
♪But I never forget your words of "No Regrets"♪
Ye Qingyu!
You fool.
You think I'd make the same mistake twice
on the same thing?
Losing Jiang Rao made me suffer so much.
I can't lose you again.
Please forgive my selfishness.
If fate has a plan for us,
we will meet again some day.
Let me,
let your Pian Ran,
leave the world first.
Qingyu.
In the past, I couldn't see my heart
because I lost my love thread.
Now,
my heart belongs to you.
It only belongs to you.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪