♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 7]
You missed. My turn.
Wait and see my card.
Nobody moves.
Check it out.
Cheers.
Cheers, Mr. Qingyu.
What's on your mind?
Everyone's celebrating the new year.
You seem spaced out.
Dad, cheers.
How is it?
Mrs. Ye,
you can't beat this one.
I play this one.
Come on.
Again!
Are you playing or not?
Told you not to play it.
Check it out.
Look at mine.
Mrs. Ye, I can't follow.
Red packages are here!
Come here.
Be patient. Everyone will get one.
OK. Here.
No rush.
Yours.
Grandma,
-Do I get one?
-This is yours.
Thank you, Grandma.
Take it.
Thank you.
Yours.
Thank you, Grandma.
Thank you.
This is yours.
Here.
Grandma,
do I get a red package?
Take it.
It's enough
for your whole year's expenses.
Thanks, Grandma.
You clung to me since childhood,
playing and jumping in front of me,
and making noises.
In a second,
my granddaughter has grown up.
Grandma.
[Father, Lin,]
[your spirits in heaven]
[don't need to worry about me.]
[Now I have a grandmother, father,]
[and brothers and sisters.]
[They are all nice to me.]
[And I think I can still save Tantai Jin.]
[I'm living a good life here.]
What?
Someone secretly helped Tantai Jin?
I didn't perform my duties well.
None of the sent assassins returned.
How the hell did this happen?
Those people
are very meticulous in their work,
and I…
I have no evidence.
Please punish me, Your Majesty.
You…
You may rise.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
I didn't expect this guy
to be so deeply concealed,
with such a mysterious force
hiding behind him.
For so many years,
I didn't even notice a hint.
I can't let him live for sure.
Your Majesty, do you mean…
Wait for a chance.
He can't leave this Sheng Kingdom anyway.
Find out the people behind him,
and then pull them up by the roots.
Get rid of all of them.
Come out.
You can transmit sounds with birds,
so are you from the Yiyue tribe?
[Your Highness,]
[you must take care of yourself.]
[Wait for Lan'an to come back.]
Your Highness,
I'm finally back at your side.
Auntie Lan'an.
I failed the Princess's trust.
Your Highness, I failed you.
But I didn't lie to you.
I promised you,
and now I'm back.
Why did you leave back then?
And why are you back today?
Back then, Emperor Jing
left us alone in the palace.
But without anyone to rely on
in the dangerous palace,
it was hard to survive.
I had to take the chance
when they dismissed the maids
to escape from the palace.
I wanted to return to the Yiyue tribe
and have the tribe's help to rescue you.
But there was an accident in the tribe,
and the old Chief was dead.
The current Chief didn't want to
offend Jing Kingdom,
so he didn't want to interfere.
And you stayed there.
Your Highness,
I don't dare to disappoint the Princess.
I lived in disgrace,
trying to gain a foothold.
I even had to marry the Chief.
It took me 20 years
to become the High Priestess.
Now the whole tribe follows my orders.
Finally, I could bring Moonshadow Guards
from thousands of miles away
to find you, Your Highness.
I'm back to save you, Your Highness.
Stand up to talk.
Thank you.
Your Highness,
you've grown up.
Auntie,
Auntie, I don't remember
you having Yiyue's talents.
Who sent the nightingale?
Nian Baiyu,
come out.
Your Highness,
he is the head of the Moonshadow Guards.
The old Chief once saved his father,
so the Nians
will absolutely be loyal to you.
You have that talent?
Yes.
People from the Yiyue tribe
can not only control birds
but also mentally engage
with their exclusive birds.
This nightingale is my exclusive bird.
Your Highness,
after what happened in Xuancheng Palace,
I'm afraid that Emperor Sheng
has been suspecting you.
These days, Mr. Nian and I
have dealt with a few waves of assassins
sent from the palace.
Surely they will not give up easily.
I've brought a team of Moonshadow Guards
and got a big boat ready at the ferry.
They are enough to escort you
and send you back to
the Yiyue tribe safely.
I never said I wanted to go back.
Are you willing to stay
in the Sheng Kingdom,
and be the hostage prince?
I can't understand.
Is there anything here
that is worth you lingering over?
The Yiyue tribe is your home.
Only your tribe people care
if you have enough food
or warm clothes;
if you are happy.
We can shield you from danger,
guarding you and protecting your life.
Don't you want to have a life
where you are respected
and your commands
are followed by everyone?
Auntie Lan'an,
tell me,
shouldn't everyone have
the feeling of homesickness?
Homesickness…
It is human nature.
Then I will return to the Jing
to relieve my homesickness.
No matter where you want to go,
I will follow you, Your Highness.
When can your boat set sail?
It's anchored off the ferry.
We can get going tomorrow morning.
OK.
Wait for me at the ferry tomorrow.
I have one more thing to deal with.
Yes.
[Your Highness.]
[Surely they will not give up easily.]
[I've brought a team of Moonshadow Guards]
[and got a big boat ready at the ferry.]
[They are enough to escort you]
[and send you back to
the Yiyue tribe safely.]
[I never said I wanted to go back.]
[Now Emperor Sheng and Emperor Jing]
[both want me killed.]
[In this case,]
[even if I return to the Yiyue tribe,]
[I will only
bring disaster to my mother tribe.]
[Only by returning to Jing Kingdom]
[can I take back everything
that should've belonged to me,]
[and have the strength
to protect myself.]
[He is not my son.]
[He's a monster!]
[Prince Minglang said]
[a hostage prince
should never leave the palace.]
[This journey is perilous,]
[I cannot leave with Jing Lan'an]
[with empty hands.]
[The demon woman
hanging out with Ye Qingyu]
[is a perfect supplement for my power.]
[I'm really going to leave]
[this place which is like]
[a prison to me.]
[But why am I feeling a bit strange?]
[I'm here to see if you have died,]
[in case I have to bury your body for you.]
[Nice day today.]
[Your smile earlier was quite nice.]
[There are so many people in this mansion.]
[There will always be
someone who likes you]
[and wants to talk to you.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
Ye Xiwu!
[-What…]
[-Be good.]
[Let's study tomorrow.]
[Ye Xiwu, let go of me.]
[Be quiet.]
[Ye Xiwu,]
[after today,]
[we won't see each other anymore.]
Are you silly?
It's so cold.
Why are you standing outside?
Nothing.
Tantai Jin,
if you feel bored,
you can chat with me.
Why are you standing out here
without telling anyone?
Don't do this anymore. You hear me?
Luckily, I brought these.
We've bought them, so let's set them off.
I'm not doing it.
Come on, try one.
No so good.
I think they are okay.
Let me show you a prettier one.
A Sketch Charm?
It's New Year. It's worth wasting one.
Go!
So pretty. I'm awesome.
Ye Xiwu.
Do you have so much fun
every Spring Festival Eve?
This year is not quite the same.
But it's still fun.
Don't worry,
I will be by your side from now on,
and no one dares to harm you anymore.
We can be this happy every year.
[As long as I can watch over you,]
[and you don't turn into the Devil God.]
[There's no more "from now on".]
Tantai Jin,
let's have a snowball fight!
Chuntao says they do this every winter.
♪Your gaze, a little closer♪
♪Heart beats faster
taking root in the void♪
♪The stars scattered in the sky♪
♪Quietly fall on your brow♪
Don't you sneak-attack me!
♪As my heart sets its direction
time passes and deepens♪
Ye Xiwu,
I've put up with you for a long time!
♪I want to enter your dreams♪
♪To explore the spring in your eyes♪
♪We are devout, turning the gears of fate♪
♪Spending a lifetime
just to see one person♪
♪From the first glance
to being immersed in passion♪
♪I carefully trace the lines of your palm♪
♪We are devout
opening the door of our hearts♪
♪Wishing to see only one person
in this lifetime♪
♪Only hoping to be moved♪
♪Not to be afraid♪
♪The mark on my heart
don't ask whether it's worth it♪
♪Just believe that it's the right time♪
[Jiang Rao,]
[where are you?]
Who is it?
Miss Pian Ran.
Are you drunk?
Jiang Rao,
you are back.
You are back!
Where is Qingyu?
This is the first day of the New Year,
but he missed breakfast and now lunch.
What are you waiting for? Go get him here.
Mr. Qingyu went out last night.
What made him leave in such a hurry?
I think he might have gone to meet a girl.
How pretty can she be
to make Qingyu so obsessed?
Oh, she must be gorgeous.
Even a prude like my brother fell for her.
I heard from Mr. Qingyu's servant
that he went somewhere near Orchid Alley.
Should we ask Mr. Qingyu back?
Leave him alone.
Qingyu has always been focused on
studying and martial arts since young.
He is smart and talented,
but never good when it comes to romance.
This time,
he's finally showing some interest.
Let alone a pretty girl.
Even if she's a widow or demon,
I still accept her as my daughter-in-law.
Father just said,
Qingyu didn't come home
all night last night.
[This demon has some good tricks.]
Did you smell anything strange?
I can't tell what it is.
I see.
I think Qingyu encountered a demon.
That's why
he has that strange smell on him.
[When did Ye Xiwu become so smart?]
It's not good.
I need to go to Pang Yizhi,
and have him check Qingyu out.
I'll go too.
I've been learning to draw charms
for a while,
so maybe I can help too.
[Little Devil God is willing to open up
and return to good.]
[He is asking to help others.]
[Li Susu,]
[you are achieving remarkable results.]
OK, let's go together.
Miss Pian Ran.
Why are you here?
When did you come?
Last night.
Who allowed you
to stay the night at my home?
Last night, I wanted to
visit you and then leave.
But you got too drunk,
and wouldn't let me leave whatsoever.
So did you sit all night on the ground?
Don't worry.
I've been sitting here all night.
I never had any…
Why didn't you come to bed?
Are you that one-track-minded?
Since you are here,
have lunch before you leave.
OK.
Look at your hesitant face,
as if I'm going to devour you alive.
You're joking.
I'm not joking.
Alright,
since I owe you my life,
you can do whatever you want to me.
What did you say?
Three months ago,
after the Jia Pass battle,
in Mount Mituo.
We met there.
Am I right?
So similar.
It's you.
I recognized you yesterday at first sight.
But I didn't mention the past,
not wanting to startle you.
Please forgive me.
Startle me?
Yes.
Ye Qingyu,
do you know what I am?
I do.
I was once a disciple
of the Xiaoyao Sect in Mount Buzhao.
I can tell demonic energy.
So you knew I was a demon
the moment we met.
Yet you pretended to be nice
and walked me home.
I couldn't help myself.
Sorry.
What if I don't forgive you?
I'm at your mercy.
That's what you said.
Regretting won't change anything.
To save you that day,
it consumed a lot of my cultivation.
I want it back with interest today.
Miss Xiwu,
let's just forget about it.
It's New Year's Day
and I've done the divination.
Today is not a good day to catch demons.
Not a good day.
Then what is good to do today?
Weddings, funerals and family visits.
Even sleeping at home by the fireplace
and petting cats
would be better
than going out to catch demons.
That's ignorant of me.
Scholar Pang,
so this is how your Xiaoyao Sect
teaches your disciples?
Do you have to tell your fortune
before you catch demons to save people,
and see if it's a good time?
We should hurry up and go.
If we delay any longer,
Ye Qingyu's would be swallowed
by the demon and nothing's gonna be left.
Exactly.
Just cut the crap and go.
Wait.
Take this.
Miss Xiwu,
you have to come back unscathed,
or General Ye
will rip my head off.
I got you. Let's go.
See no evil.
[Is Little Devil God learning how to…]
What's that?
The spirit of a human.
Hurry up.
Is Ye Qingyu going to be drained?
Not so serious.
He will only lose some energy.
Easy for you to say.
Wait here.
Ye Xiwu.
Miss Xiwu,
she's just teasing Ye Qingyu.
In fact, she's not hurting him at all.
Qingyu…
Lady,
please calm down and listen to me.
Let my brother go.
Are you his sister?
Lady,
I have heard some about
demons cultivating.
But sucking people's energy
is not the righteous way.
You should cultivate on your own,
and that is the right way.
Shut up!
I know there is a sect.
They never discriminate
against the disciples,
whether they are humans or demons.
If you trust me,
I can write you a reference letter.
Heptatail Fox!
[Little Devil God
is trying to save others.]
[This conciliation approach works.]
Go after her!
Hurry up.
[Ye Qingyu should be fine.]
[Hanxuan Restaurant]
I'll set up the tactics outside.
Miss Xiwu, please go in and look for her.
[Hanxuan Restaurant]
Let's cooperate from inside and outside.
Miss Xiwu,
I can't move a step,
so I have to guard the gate.
I'll hand you the job of catching her
in this sealed building.
It's called the Thousand Thunder Tactic.
Once you touch it, your cultivation
of a hundred years will be wasted.
You won't escape this.
What the hell?
Sorry.
I can tell,
you have a tender heart for women.
You won't do such an unromantic thing.
I can spare your life,
but how are you going to repay me?
Sir, you are asking
while knowing the answer.
Who-who on earth are you?
[Your blood can counter
all demons in the world.]
[Go, devour them.]
Please spare me.
Tantai Jin!
When did you learn these demonic arts?
Are you really responsible
for Xuancheng Palace's incident
and Chief Wu's death?
You came at a bad time.
You've been lying to me this whole time.
Imperial order of the three divine gods,
reveal evil spirits!
Bind!
Ye Xiwu,
you have no mercy toward me!
I merely wanted to enhance my power.
What's wrong with that?
I can't believe you were
attacking me for a demon.
Escaping?
What do you want?
My dear husband,
don't leave!
Don't forget we are a married couple.
If you leave,
I'll feel sad.
[It's a demonic hex from that fox.]
Ye Xiwu,
your life
is in my hands this time.
Unexpectedly, things went so smoothly.
His Highness wants to go back
to Jing Kingdom to claim the throne.
Tantai Minglang has always
hated the Yiyue tribe.
If he had the throne,
the Yiyue tribe would be in danger.
We came all the way to find Tantai Jin.
Luckily, he is willing to join us.
Our hard work paid off.
High Priestess,
why didn't you tell His Highness
our actual purpose?
You don't know Tantai Jin well.
He is cold and aloof by nature,
yet he desires care and attention.
The less we display selfishness,
the smoother things will go.
It's good for both him and us.
But wouldn't that be using him?
He has the bloodline of the Princess,
so I think we should be loyal to him.
It's always been hard
for the Yiyue tribe to survive.
Now we are doing our best
to help him return to his home.
How is that using him?
You are still young.
Things in this world
are not all black and white.
Even if you want to be loyal,
you don't have to be
candid about everything.
As long as we don't hurt him,
What's wrong with achieving our goal?
But…
Enough.
The agreed time is up.
He is still not here.
Go check it out.
OK.
It's him.
Nian Baiyu, leading Moonshadow Guards,
welcome Your Highness.
You may rise.
Your Highness,
who is this?
Ye Xiwu.
Are you taking her with us?
Auntie Lan'an, do you think
I shouldn't take her?
I don't dare to disobey you.
It's just… I heard
Miss Xiwu throws
her weight about everywhere.
She has been disrespectful toward you
for a long time.
Your Highness, you are returning
to claim the throne
and unify the world.
Why don't you kill this woman
to boost our courage?
Ye Xiwu is utterly stupid,
but her father holds
the military power of Sheng Kingdom.
It won't be late to kill her
after I make use of her.
It's wise of you, Your Highness.
Xiwu is your biological sister.
She is now missing
because of that demon.
You are killing me!
I'm willing to take
any punishment for my misdeeds.
But the most important thing
right now is Xiwu's safety.
That's right, Grandma.
Stop scolding Qingyu.
It's urgent to find her.
How do you expect me to live
if something happens to Xiwu?
Mother,
don't be agitated.
General Ye!
Scholar Pang had met Ye Xiwu.
General Ye,
Today, Miss Xiwu took me to catch a demon.
It was my fault that
I only guarded outside the gate.
What did that demon do to Xiwu?
That Heptatail Fox only escaped.
When I realized it,
I barged into the building
to search for her.
Then I found out
Tantai Jin took Miss Xiwu away.
That's strange.
What did Tantai Jin take Xiwu away for?
Zhong Tai!
Here!
Go to Chen Xian.
Send Dragon Guards to seal the city gates
and search the whole city.
The ferry on the east of the city
leads to Jing Kingdom directly.
Take a team over there now
and stop all the boats.
OK.
Your Highness,
do you mean…
Tantai Jin may escape Sheng Kingdom…
Currently, Jing Kingdom is
in an unstable situation.
Now the hostage prince runs away
from Ye family.
My father will be suspicious of you.
Seal the ferry.
Search the boats one by one.
Yes, sir.
Have more eyes on the river.
OK.
Check over there.
High Priestess,
everything has been arranged.
Miss Ye is locked in the cabin,
and I tied her with Ruo-River ropes,
so she won't get away.
You've grown up in a flash.
Mr. Nian,
why are you loyal to the Yiyue tribe?
The old Chief has saved the Nians…
That's the last generation's business.
I'm asking you.
I want to know your own thoughts.
As long as His Highness takes the throne
and protects the Yiyue tribe,
he will be my new master.
The Yiyue tribe is my home.
I was born there and brought up there.
My family is there.
Family…
High Priestess,
I'm sorry.
I was absent without leave back then,
and lost Miss Fuya.
I told you, that's the past.
Don't mention the past anymore.
I can't blame that on you.
Luckily, we got His Highness back.
You and your Moonshadow Guards
can take a break for now,
but don't let your guard down.
If the Sheng people find out
they've lost the hostage prince,
they will take action.
Yes.
Go.
[Fuya,]
[my girl,
I promise I will bring you home.]
[So cold.]
[What's this place…]
Stop struggling.
We took your charms away.
Also, this rope is made by the Yiyue tribe
with Ruo River water.
You can't untie it even with your spells.
So, what are you doing here?
To laugh at me
that I can't untie the rope?
Or are you here to kill me?
The journey is long and boring,
so I'm here to chat with you.
Didn't you say that
I can come to you
when I want to chat with someone?
I was stupid to trust you.
Doesn't matter.
Whether you want to or not,
willing or not,
you can only sit here and listen.
You must be wondering
how come the weak me
can devour the demonic elixir,
why there would be a team of guards,
and where and when all this started.
Does that matter?
I should have known earlier
that you were born this way.
You are an ungrateful man.
Ye Xiwu,
I don't think you are innocent.
You are stupid.
You don't even know
why you married me.
What do you mean?
Have you ever wondered the reason?
You clearly sent people
to poison Ye Bingchang's dessert
with Love Fury,
but why did you
finally fall victim to it?
[The night before
the Qixi Festival banquet, in the palace,]
[I noticed a servant]
[tampering with
the desserts of the banquet.]
Well done.
After they both take Love Fury,
they will surely have some fun together.
But she is your sister after all.
Are you going too far by doing this?
What's so good about Ye Bingchang?
She has been pretending
to be pitiful and weak
all day.
I want her to lose her virginity,
particularly to that
fat and greasy Prince Wuning.
I want everyone to laugh at her.
I want Xiao Lin to
think of her as a nasty woman,
and lose interest in her.
You can go back.
Wait and see tomorrow night's big show.
Yes.
[I had a difficult life in the palace,]
[cornered to a desperate state.]
[Because of your plot,]
[I could have a great chance]
to leave the Palace of Sheng.
It was you who swapped
Ye Bingchang's and my desserts.
You also set up a scheme
to eat Xiao Liang's dessert.
[I was planning on
knocking over his snack,]
[but he took the initiative to
give me a hard time.]
[It took me no effort
to make my plan work.]
[Why didn't you choose my sister?]
The Love Fury was originally for her.
This was your evil plan.
So of course, you were the perfect choice
to fulfill my plan.
Also, you are
General Ye's favorite daughter.
If I want to escape
from the palace to save my life,
marrying you is a correct option.
You have schemed so much,
yet you still pretend
to be innocent
and victimized in front of me,
making me feel pity and guilt toward you.
Ye Xiwu,
as a hostage prince,
I was living in degradation
in the Sheng Kingdom
and my life and death
were not in my own hands.
What else could I do
but endure and make concessions?
Let me tell you one more thing.
That night,
we were only lying next to each other.
Nothing happened between us.
[You are evil and stupid.]
[I would rather endure]
[the heart-wrenching pain from Love Fury,]
than be intimate with you
for even a second.
That's great.
Thank you very much, Tantai Jin.
In the future,
we will have nothing
to do with each other.
Future?
Do you still think you have a future,
the forthcoming?
Dream on.
I won't keep anyone
who knows too many of my secrets alive.
The people who know your secrets…
[This is Nanny Yingxin.]
They want to harm His Highness.
You will harm His Highness.
You will harm him!
Are you talking about Tantai Jin?
Who wanted to harm him?
It wasn't me.
Why did Yingxin go crazy?
You made her go mad.
She colluded with Tantai Minglang
and tried to kill me.
Can't I fight back?
The food today
is unexpectedly substantial.
Your Highness,
you are about to wed Miss Xiwu,
so the royal kitchen
sent the dishes to show kindness.
[Prince Minglang said]
the hostage prince
should never leave the palace.
Tantai Minglang wants me to kill him?
If you are willing to
help us with this favor,
we will find a way to help you
leave the Palace of Sheng
and go back to your hometown.
For real?
Yingxin.
Do you remember
a bottle of imperial wine was buried
under the tree outside the gate?
It was given to us by Emperor Sheng
on his birthday one year,
but you wanted to preserve it.
You said that if there was ever a day
we could leave this damned place,
we would open it to celebrate.
Now we can leave the Palace of Sheng.
How about digging it up?
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪