♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 4]
Princess Yue Ruanruan,
known for her gentleness and virtues,
is hereby granted
the title of Concubine Rou.
She will be welcomed and greeted
with a grand wedding ceremony.
A nationwide celebration.
May Your Majesty and Her Highness
love each other forever,
and may your descendants thrive on and on!
♪I've searched endlessly
in hopes of meeting you in this life♪
♪I've become the light traveling in the dark♪
♪A drop of tear, a pinch of dust♪
♪A journey ends in an instant♪
♪Life is short, but a dream lasts forever♪
[Till death do us part]
Congrats, Your Majesty!
Concubine Rou is pregnant!
Aunty.
[Can you sew?]
[Of course.]
[These are our child's clothes.]
[I must sew them by my own hands.]
[You were born with high hopes.]
[They loved each other so much.]
[How could King Jing agree]
[to let him be a hostage
in Sheng Kingdom?]
[Your Majesty,]
[Concubine Rou has been
in torturous labor for three days.]
[The imperial doctor
has tried all methods.]
[I'm afraid you can
only save one of them.]
[Your Majesty, please decide soon.]
[What's there to decide?]
[Of course, I should save Concubine Rou.]
[I just want her to live.]
[Everything else doesn't matter.]
[Go now!]
[-Yes.]
-Princess.
Princess, hang in there.
His Majesty's order:
keeping Concubine Rou alive
is the top priority.
Princess.
[Lan'an,]
[you must save this child.]
[Don't let him die because of me.]
[He will be a kind-hearted kid.]
[Please.]
Monster!
Princess!
-Someone!
-Princess!
Someone please help!
[He shouldn't have been
born into this world.]
[He's responsible
for Concubine Rou's death.]
[He killed the woman I loved the most.]
Please have mercy.
Your Majesty,
the little prince hasn't even
been suckled since he was born.
If you throw him into the cold palace,
he won't be able to survive.
Your Majesty!
Please have mercy!
He's not my son!
He's a monster!
Your Majesty!
Little prince is
Her Highness's only bloodline.
Your Majesty!
If the little prince dies,
Her Highness will really
be gone for good, Your Majesty!
Please have mercy!
If you insist on protecting him,
you shall be his guardian.
You shall fend
for yourselves in the palace.
Thanks, Your Majesty!
Let's go!
Your Majesty,
these are all lucky names
provided by the Ministry of Rites.
Please decide which one it shall be.
I understand.
[The names of all children]
[Jin (cinder)]
[bears the expectations of parents.]
[But Tantai Jin's name]
[was but a curse.]
[Why is someone awake?]
Watch out!
Tantai Jin?
I only left for a short while,
and you two broke free.
You're quite something.
I was wondering
why you didn't have nightmares.
Turns out you don't have any love lines.
What don't I have?
You were born without love lines.
That's why you can't feel emotions.
You won't feel happy or sad.
You won't feel scared, either.
How can a loveless one have nightmares?
What a waste
of all your miserable memories.
However,
I finally found your weakness just now.
Something you do care about in this world.
Even if it's only a little.
But that will suffice.
Enjoy your nightmares!
Where is this place?
How can a baby live here?
He'll freeze to death!
Go find him now.
Come on!
[Seems like Tantai Jin and I]
[entered different timelines.]
[No.]
[I must find Little Devil God soon.]
O' divine mirror,
see through all illusions.
Shatter!
[There's no Chongyu Harp.]
[My power isn't enough
to break the barrier.]
[Seems like only after
Yingxin's memories end,]
[can I get out.]
Your Highness.
[Hope Little Devil God is fine.]
Your Highness!
No!
What should we do, Sister Lan'an?
He's not breathing.
Don't jinx it!
Your Highness! Your Highness!
Why would he wake up after sucking blood?
He's a monster!
Why is he born with teeth?
Don't say anything like this again.
We can't let others know this.
[As expected from Little Devil God.]
[But the war of God and Devil
happened ten thousand years ago,]
[why would he be born
at this very time and place?]
Here it is.
Your Highness, don't cry.
Don't cry. Here comes the yummy food.
Don't cry.
Come on.
[Although he led a hard life,]
[at least some tried their best
to take care of him.]
[But how long could they]
[keep living like this?]
Here you are.
It's edible.
See?
Stop crying.
There.
Don't cry.
Kneel!
Just kneel!
Today I'm gonna let him
be our puppy dog. How about that?
Yeah!
-Bark!
-Come on.
Do it!
Bark!
Come on and bark!
-Bark!
-Come on!
Puppy!
These little brats!
Come on!
Give it to him.
You can't kneel to those servants.
Let alone bark like a dog, understand?
They said if I barked,
they wouldn't beat me.
And even give me food.
Don't you know what dignity is?
Are you born without a sense of shame?
[As a prince, you're bullied by servants.]
[Do you have no sense of shame at all?]
[Sense of shame?]
[That means nothing to me.]
[Food is clearly more important.]
They keep bullying you like this.
Don't you feel sad?
What's sense of shame?
What's feeling sad?
They're making fun of you.
Did they not mean to give me food?
No.
I see.
Then can I kill them?
[So this is the nature of Devil God?]
I can't take this anymore.
His Highness isn't normal at all!
He's a monster!
What nonsense are you talking about?
He's only six. He's still a child.
You think he's abnormal
simply because
he has been living in the cold palace
and is constantly bullied.
Understand?
But…
We're running out of money and jewelry.
We can't sustain like this.
Here's an idea.
A few days from now
is the palace maids' off-day.
I'll try to slip out
and ask for help from Yiyue Tribe.
What about me?
Yingxin,
I need you
to take care of him alone for a while.
His Highness inherited
the ability to communicate with animals.
He's the hope of Yiyue Tribe.
We must save him!
[Don't worry.]
[I'll be back soon.]
[I'll do my best
to bring you and His Highness]
[to Yiyue Tribe soon.]
[Trust me.]
Does it hurt?
Thanks for caring, Your Highness.
I'm used to it.
Where is Tantai Jin?
Come quickly to hear your edict!
It must be Lan'an coming to save us!
His Highness is here!
Edict from His Majesty:
Tantai Jin is to set off immediately
to be a hostage in Sheng.
What do you mean a hostage in Sheng?
You're asking that?
We lost the battle with Sheng Kingdom.
To make peace,
His Majesty ordered Tantai Jin
to be a hostage in Sheng Kingdom.
He shall set off today.
Understand?
You two help them pack things up.
-Yes.
Jing Lan'an, you liar!
You left me here to die!
Liar!
[We're at Sheng Kingdom now.]
Chief Wu.
You're called Yue Yingxin?
You're the maid who came along
with the hostage prince?
Are you sending snacks to him?
I'm not gonna eat you.
Get in there.
Yes.
[This old turtle is so disgusting!]
Your Highness!
Hold down this lowly maid, too!
What are you doing?
Let go of me!
Your Highness!
They say you're a freak.
You don't shed tears.
I don't believe there's someone
who doesn't shed tears.
Cry for me now.
And I'll let you go.
I really can't.
Your Highness!
How's that? Does it hurt?
The hostage prince still isn't crying.
Don't stop!
Go ahead and break his other arm off!
Yes.
Stop!
Greetings, Prince Lin.
You may all rise.
Brother,
Prince Tantai left his home country
to be a guest in our kingdom.
He did it for the peace
of the two kingdoms.
And also for keeping the civilians
free from the pains of war.
We should treat him politely.
How can you bully him without scruple?
Such a bummer.
Let's go!
Your Highness.
Thank you Prince Lin for saving us.
No need.
My fifth brother was being rude.
Prince Tantai looks pale.
Why don't you go back and have a rest?
I'll explain it to the teacher for you.
Come on. Thank you, Prince Lin!
Why would that Prince Lin
tell his brother to stop?
And how could he make them fear him?
I heard,
Prince Lin's mother is the queen.
She's also His Majesty's favorite.
People in the palace
are mostly superficial.
So naturally they dare not offend him.
Mother?
If he didn't have a mother anymore,
would he be the same as me?
Actually, what I said
isn't necessarily right.
Besides his mother
is important and favored,
Prince Lin is also gentle and intelligent.
Who wouldn't like him?
Really?
[If I behaved like him,]
[will others like me too]
[and stop bullying me?]
[Geography of Four Continents]
Geography of Four Continents?
Your Highness, why are you reading this?
It is said that Xiao Lin
just went to Mount Buzhao
where he'll cultivate for three years.
I don't know that place.
So I wanted to find it in books.
Someone can't even get out of the palace,
but is still dreaming about
some immortal mountain.
Trying to learn spells to fly out of here?
Prince Liang.
Take this!
Your Highness!
Are you alright?
Prince Liang,
why did you hit me?
Why?
Because your smile looks disgusting.
I tell you what,
I've had enough of a freak like you!
Now that Xiao Lin's not around,
let's see who will protect you!
Get him!
Your Highness!
Stop it!
Stop!
Your Highness!
I thought
they stopped bullying me all these years
because I acted like Xiao Lin
and learned to be a normal person
like Lan'an said before she left.
But I didn't know
they were just scared of Xiao Lin.
Prince Lin,
congrats for completing your training
and moving into your new mansion!
Good things come in pairs!
Congrats!
[Prince Tantai?]
We haven't met for three years.
Thank you for coming today.
Congratulations.
Look! Miss Ye Bingchang is here!
That is…
She's the daughter of General Ye.
Miss Ye.
Your Highness.
It's getting chilly.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Hos…
Prince Tantai, why are you here?
Miss Ye.
The weather is chilly.
Be careful not to catch a cold.
Your Highness, I don't feel cold.
Please keep the cloak for yourself.
[Could Tantai Jin like Ye Bingchang]
[because he was imitating Xiao Lin?]
Yingxin,
is it because my cloak is worn out?
Tantai Jin!
Who are you trying to disgust this time?
Prince Liang,
so many people pass by this corridor.
If you plan on beating me up here,
I'm afraid…
You haven't heard?
Now Sheng and Jing kingdoms are at war.
If I kicked your Jing ass,
who's gonna stop me?
Get him!
Your Highness!
Take that!
Stop it!
[He's been getting beaten so frequently.]
[When does this ever end?]
Yingxin,
how does it feel like to be liked?
You're not answering.
Is it because you don't like me either?
Please forgive me, Your Highness!
I never disliked you.
When I was little,
I couldn't understand what the looks
on people's faces meant.
But now,
I sort of understand a little.
Actually, you've always resented me.
It's because of me
that you're trapped in this
dark and remote palace.
Yingxin,
I don't blame you.
I resent myself too.
I know people out there don't like me.
Normally speaking,
I should feel sad inside.
If it were Xiao Lin,
he'd be ridden with such guilt
that he couldn't eat.
Later on, I started imitating Xiao Lin.
I imitated everything he did,
hoping that I could
gradually become him.
Be someone likable
just like Xiao Lin.
But Yingxin,
I still couldn't feel a thing.
I was faking it when I smiled like him.
I was faking it
when I was being magnanimous.
I was even
faking it when I cared about others.
Fake things
deserve to be detested.
To be loathed.
And to be abandoned.
[Doesn't matter.]
[For someone like me,]
[being alive is a blessing enough.]
Your Highness.
[Why should I want love?]
Your Highness!
[Born with an evil bone…]
[Having no emotions or love…]
[None of it was what he wanted.]
[Nor was it his fault.]
[But once he became the Devil God,]
[all those victims]
[were indeed slain by him.]
I was ordered to send
a verbal message from Jing.
Jing Kingdom?
The hostage prince will soon marry
and leave the Palace of Sheng.
But once he does,
he might return to Jing Kingdom.
Once he returns,
he'll probably grasp power,
and then he'll become untouchable.
That's why Prince Minglang said
the hostage prince should
better not leave forever.
[Tantai Minglang?]
[Little Devil God's elder brother.]
Tantai Minglang wants me to kill him?
Then what's in it for me?
Even displaced horses
and birds miss their home.
Prince Minglang knows
that you're getting older.
As long as you're willing to help us.
We'll think of a way
to help you get out of the palace,
and return to your hometown.
Really?
You've sacrificed your best years
and ruined most of your life
just for Tantai Jin.
Are you really willing
to follow this monster
until you die in a foreign land?
Yingxin,
don't get seduced!
You watched Tantai Jin grow up.
Although he's weird,
he never once hurt you.
Do you really have the heart to do this?
He has no family
or friends in Sheng Kingdom.
You're the only person he can trust.
You can't betray him!
Yingxin!
Okay. I'll do it.
Very well, then. I'll leave for now.
Even you betrayed him.
[In Tantai Jin's whole life,]
[if only there was someone
who truly loved him,]
[and held his reins,]
[maybe…]
[he wouldn't have
been forced to devilize.]
It's finally over.
We've finally found it.
The demon's den is protected by a barrier.
Bingchang's probably here.
I feel Tantai Jin and Miss Xiwu
are imprisoned here, too.
We have to rescue them fast.
Go check the borders of this barrier.
Have someone guard the roads.
Yes.
Hurry!
Move!
Now we must lure the demon out.
I'll do it.
Demon!
We've found your den!
Stop hiding!
Otherwise, I'll set your woods on fire!
Free delivery to my doorstep, eh?
[I wonder how Yingxin went crazy after.]
[Tantai Jin.]
Tantai Jin!
Tantai Jin, wake up!
You said you couldn't dream.
But why is there a nightmare blossom
sprouting from you?
Tantai Jin!
Tantai Jin, wake up!
[Tantai Jin!]
[Tantai Jin, wake up!]
I heard
among the outer disciples of Xiaoyao Sect
Jin is one of the best.
And his talents are extraordinary.
He's just doing it for fun.
What?
Do you really want Jin to be immortal?
Let me look at you, dear.
You've really gotten thinner
after you left the palace.
Mother.
Come.
I have something to tell you, Son.
While you were away cultivation,
I've been arranging you a marriage.
Thank you, Father.
The bride is the daughter of
Sheng Kingdom's General Ye Xiao.
Conflicts can never seem to cease
between Sheng and Jing.
After we make peace this time,
we will be more like friends than enemies.
I'll do what as you wish, Father, Mother.
Jin,
while you were cultivating
in Xiaoyao Sect,
did you meet any promising young talents?
The Prince Lin of Sheng Kingdom
got along well with me.
[What a coincidence.]
[Xiao Lin happens to be one
escorting the bride to Jing Kingdom.]
[You can spend time
getting to know him better.]
[Yes.]
Congratulations, Your Highness!
[I didn't want to]
[choose your wife so hastily.]
Congratulations, Your Highness!
[But now that you've
been throned Crown Prince.]
[Your marriage
concerns the kingdom's future.]
Congratulations, Your Highness.
[Miss Ye Bingchang is well-educated.]
[She's also a stunning beauty.]
[I think you'll like her, my son.]
Ye Xiwu?
It's you?
Who else
were you expecting?
Mother?
Mother!
Father.
You matricide bastard!
No.
Father.
I didn't kill mother!
Lan'an.
Don't go.
[You're a monster.]
In your beautiful dream,
you had such a perfect family.
How did it feel to be loved by everybody?
Xiao Lin,
help me!
But that's all fake.
Once you wake up from these dreams,
no one will care about you,
nor will anyone love you.
All this time,
you've been imitating me,
hoping you could be like me,
to be ackowledged by others.
But in your dream just now
you got everything you ever wanted.
Love from your parents.
Easily ascending to the throne.
Even I'd envy that kind of life.
But can you really feel happiness?
I can't.
I felt nothing.
If not for you,
your mother wouldn't have died.
Your father wouldn't suffer
the loss of his love.
Lan'an wouldn't waste away
in that dark palace.
Yingxin wouldn't be shamed
time and time again.
They were all your nearest and dearest.
But they all hate you.
I never intended to do them harm.
Never.
See?
All emotions, affections, and desires
mean nothing to you.
All you ever know is to protect yourself.
You don't understand
or care about other people's pain at all.
I understand.
I understand it all.
I just can't feel it.
Tantai Jin,
you really are pathetic.
You're alive,
but you can't feel
the slightest beauty of this mortal world.
You can't even feel the pain
of this mortal world.
The only point of your existence
is to bring torment to others.
No!
To be despised and hated by others.
Why…
are you even alive?
No! That's not true!
But at least,
your mother never hated you!
She loved you till the very end.
If you could see her
and hear her say
how much she loved you,
you could break free from this fate.
Do you want to see her?
The chance is right before your eyes.
What are you waiting for?
[You must experience
all pain in the world,]
[and draw endless hatred.]
[You're carrying the curse of your fate.]
[You're destined to have a bitter end.]
[When your pain reaches its peak,]
[when your life reaches the end,]
[I will come and accept your sacrifice.]
I'm done waiting.
I'm not waiting any longer.
Tantai Jin!
You can't die!
[Why is my power weakening?]
Xiao Lin!
Hurry, Junior Martial Uncle.
Ah, whatever. This will do!
We did it!
Where did she go?
So you ruined my vines.
I should've swallowed you
and let your soul disperse!
[Tantai Jin.]
[Why not have a taste of this demon?]
What are you talking about?
[Your blood deters
all demons in this world.]
[Your body can bear their demonic powers.]
[As long as they can't kill you,]
[you can use their power.]
[Do you feel it?]
[This power is what your body craves.]
[Isn't it more fun
than emotions and desires?]
Don't try to fool me again!
[With the whip of power in your hands,]
[you'll be the highest ruler
of this world.]
[This is the taste of power!]
[I promise you this,]
[once you've tasted it,]
[you'll never want to lose it again.]
Tantai Jin!
Your Highness,
Miss Bingchang is over here.
Bingchang!
Where's that demon?
Was she blasted to ashes
by the charm I used?
Let's save the people first.
Bingchang!
No…
Tantai Jin!
[Am I back again?]
Miss!
Miss, you're finally awake!
I was worried sick!
I thought you were going to die.
Where's Tantai Jin?
Is he dead?
Mr. Tantai was placed
in the east-wing chamber.
He hasn't woken up yet.
But he's probably not gonna die.
Chuntao,
how did we get back?
I can't remember.
It was Prince Lin who brought you back.
The imperial doctor said
you passed out just because
you were too weak.
Her Ladyship
and His Lordship sat by your bed
for a whole night and just left to rest.
What about my sister?
Is she alright?
Miss Bingchang is okay now.
Prince Lin is looking after her.
[The damages in the nightmares were real.]
[Thank god I stopped him
from slitting his throat.]
[Tantai Jin can't die.]
[But who can withstand]
[such a painful life?]
[If I can give him a hand,]
[would he be able to live normally]
[and not turn into Devil God?]
[Li Susu,]
[you're actually sympathizing with him.]
[He destroyed Hengyang Sect.]
[He killed so many people.]
[He plagued the three realms
and four continents.]
[He must pay for all these debts.]
[Even if he's suffering so terribly now,]
[it's his fate.]
[But it's now five hundred years ago.]
[He hasn't yet killed anyone,
nor is he capable of causing harm.]
[Being constantly bullied]
[is simply cruelty for doing no wrong.]
[Since I was little,
Father taught me to be upright]
[and be true to my heart.]
[Now that I know all this,]
[and if I'm secretly happy for it,]
[I'll be confusing right from wrong.]
Miss Xiwu,
please have some rest before you see her.
Even if you want to see Prince Lin…
-Wait till you can stand properly…
-I'm going to see Tantai Jin.
[As long as they can't kill you,]
[you can use their power.]
Power.
So,
this is
what power feels like.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I’ve seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪