The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 30]
[Now in the three realms,
the immortal sects are the leader,]
[the mortal realm comes second,]
[Barren Abyss]
[and us demons come last.]
[This is because the Devil God
was killed 10,000 years ago.]
[Us demons have lost our leader.]
Why are there more and more demons?
Barren Abyss is too big.
We are shorthanded.
We need help in the north!
[Leader of Xiaoyao Sect, Zhaoyou]
In the south…
A big swarm of demons rushed out in the south.
What should we do?
Master Zhaoyou?
The runes in the east have been installed.
Don't panic.
Sects in the east front
go help your left and right sides.
Move in the north direction as a whole.
The runes in this side have been installed.
Yes.
Come on.
Our goal is to deploy the Vigilant Bells.
Don't get distracted by the demons.
Hang on a little longer.
Our job with the bells is about to be finished.
[Victory is at hand in the Barren Abyss.]
[Old Qu,]
[I wonder what's going on with your side?]
[Hengyang Sect, Demon-sealing Cliff]
Oh no.
They're getting away.
It's master's sword!
Master is here!
Master!
[Leader of Hengyang Sect, Qu Xuan Zi]
Reinforce the seal with me.
Yes!
Master,
why are these demons
going on a rampage at the same time?
All demons of the four continents went crazy.
They must be agitated by something.
We're just living by our nature.
But they've been killing us
like we're rats on the streets.
They've sealed us in this dark place
for hundreds of years.
Can you accept this?
No!
As long as we retrieve the devil fetus
and revive His Highness,
we'll be able to revitalize Barren Abyss!
Although Yiyue Tribe lost the devil fetus
and we've searched for 500 years without results,
thankfully His Highness had plans beforehand.
He left three Demonic Artifacts
to guide us to find the devil fetus.
Our real target today
is actually this minor little sect
called Yunchang Sect.
The clues of Bone-refining Seal,
the heart of the Devil God, is there.
The devil fetus and the demonic artifact
interact with each other.
As long as we find the Bone-refining Seal,
it'll definitely lead us to the devil fetus.
Reviving His Highness will be a matter of time!
Revive His Highness!
Revive the Devil God!
Master,
in case you got distracted,
we dare not tell you earlier that
something unusual happened on Heaven Lake.
What?
Since a few hours ago,
[Hengyang Sect, Heaven Lake]
it's been thundering in the thunderclouds above Heaven Lake.
Senior Sect Brother.
Senior Sect Brother,
anomaly on Heaven Lake.
Master told us to be there quickly.
[Susu…]
[Kill Tantai Jin before he devilizes.]
[Stop the predestined arrival of the Devil God.]
[Raise your head.]
[Tantai Jin.]
[Is this really a person?]
[You won't die.]
[As long as you're alive,]
[more will be able to live.]
[You'll be happy when you see him.]
[The sky is blue.]
Susu!
♪Against the glowing of all stars♪
-Sect Sister!
Sect Sister is out!
Sect Sister!
You're finally out!
♪Tear open the wounds of destiny♪
I'm back.
I did it.
♪I'm not afraid to burn all my blood♪
♪This is a tribute to my past pride♪
♪Even if there's only a glimmer of hope♪
Susu,
[I thought…]
Dad.
♪I'm never forgotten by the winds♪
I did it.
I made it.
Yes.
You've survived
your punishment.
My punishment?
Yes.
Somehow your lightning punishment
didn't strike down.
But you've safely passed
this punishment in your life.
[Didn't the]
[lightning punishment already strike?]
Dad,
I wasn't talking about the lightning punishment.
You and Uncle Zhaoyou used the Mirror of Past…
Mirror of Past?
That's the ultimate treasure of Xiaoyao Sect.
When did we ever use it?
[This makes sense.]
[I've stopped the arrival of the Devil God.]
[They have no memory of]
[sending me back 500 years with the mirror.]
Susu,
have you confused things
after 10 years of meditation retreat?
I've been in a meditation retreat for 10 years?
You really don't remember?
Ten years ago your body suddenly caught fire.
You dropped into deep sleep
and didn't wake up until today.
So there's no Devil God in this world?
There's no All-in-Distress Way?
There's no catastrophe?
Right?
Right.
That's great.
That's right.
It's so good to see you safe and sound.
[Xiao Lin?]
I've been hoping that you would wake up.
[No.]
[Now that I'm back,]
[I should call him Sect Brother Gongye.]
Thank you, Senior Sect Brother.
Susu,
Jiwu,
let's go.
Let's go home.
[Susu,]
[why do you see me as a stranger now?]
Old Qu,
Susu is out of her meditation retreat.
You can finally be rest assured
after worrying for her for ten years.
Something doesn't seem right about her.
Her cultivation level actually dropped.
I wonder what exactly happened?
When you're free,
please check her fortune for me.
By the way, how're things going at Barren Abyss?
I'm here for this matter.
The Vigilant Bells have all been deployed.
Those demons
won't be able to cause trouble for now.
But then again,
this time I didn't see
the two arch demons Si Ying and Jing Mie.
I can't help but feel unsettled.
Their whereabouts
have been quite unpredictable lately.
I wonder if they have some other plans.
We must be careful.
Almost forgot.
The letter from my younger sect brother.
Zhao'en?
Didn't he go to Yunchang Sect?
Luckily,
he survived
because he was half a day late.
I suspect that
this is exactly why the two didn't show up.
This is a serious matter.
It's best if we gather all sects to discuss.
But I heard,
Leader Cen of Chixiao Sect is still traveling.
When is he going to be back?
Leader Cen is most keen on killing demons.
He'll return as soon as he gets the message.
Old Qu,
there's another thing I wanna ask you today.
Immortal Buxu told me to
go to the bank of Ruo Water,
saying that there's an auspicious sign
in the southeast direction.
He particularly said that I must go personally.
I went there like he asked,
and I saved a person from there!
Could you tell me
is this fortune or misfortune?
This isn't the Nether River.
Where is this place?
This is…
[That's right.]
[I sank into the depth of the Nether River.]
[Then,]
[it appeared.]
[I've seen]
[that black crossbow]
[in Bo're Life.]
Friend,
are you okay?
Come on, get up.
Are you alright?
When did you wake up?
Why didn't you tell us?
Why am I here?
My master found you and took you back.
My master is the leader of Xiaoyao Sect.
He's the famous
Immortal Zhaoyou in the immortal realm.
You are just so lucky.
I've cast a spell to rain divine raindrops.
With the protection of Heart-guarding Scale,
it won't take long
before this place becomes
a land abundant in immortal energy.
[This place is surrounded by mountains]
[and sunlight can't reach the valleys.]
[I shall name it Mount Buzhao.]
[This]
[is Mount Buzhao left by Ming Ye.]
Son,
you're awake.
Aren't you gonna say thanks to your savior?
[It's him.]
[Seems like Ye Xiwu could've been alive now.]
[But because of me…]
Thanks for saving me.
I still have something important to do.
I'll take my leave.
Don't leave just yet.
You're in such a hurry.
Are you returning to the Nether River?
Do you know the gate to the Ruo Water
only opens every five hundred years?
Even if you made it to the bank of Ruo Water,
how are you going to
open the gate of Ruo Water?
I can't stay.
I have to find her.
Are you trying to retrieve
her primordial spirit?
The dead can't back to life.
She's already dead.
What's the point of retrieving it anyway?
You're such a stubborn one.
Sect Uncle Buxu sent me a message
to tell me to save someone by the Ruo Water.
I thought I could find a treasure.
Instead I found someone as costly as you!
Do you know how many
valuable drugs and treasures from Xiaoyao Sect
I've used in order to save you?
I've tried so hard to get your life back,
but you just wanna walk away like this?
Then what do you want?
If I can't find her,
life and death have no difference to me.
Forget it.
I'll take it as a losing business.
I like doing things thoroughly.
If you really wanna kill yourself,
wait till you leave our sect property,
understand?
Master,
are you really letting him go like this?
Rest assured.
He can't leave this place.
He'll be back sooner or later.
Bravo!
[This should be an immortal sect
like Ye Xiwu said.]
[The gate to Ruo Water has closed.]
[I have to wait 500 years for it to open again.]
[It's easy to leave this place.]
[But where shall I go to find Ye Xiwu?]
Sect Brother.
You didn't try your best.
I'll challenge you again.
I'll defeat you and your Zhuokun Sword someday.
Go.
Let's go.
[Prince Tantai left his homeland]
[and became a guest in our Sheng Kingdom]
[for the peace of the two kingdoms.]
[We should treat him politely.]
[How can you bully him without scruple?]
[Back when we're in the Sheng palace,]
[I was a prince]
[and you were a hostage.]
[Our paths were nothing alike.]
[Another year later,
who'd have thought we will be at war]
[and become each other's archenemy.]
[I want you to pull your troops back]
[and stop the war.]
[Now what separates us will be]
[the boundary of life and death.]
[Brother Tantai]
[I know you don't wish to see me dead.]
[But death is my only way out.]
[Thank you for granting my wish.]
Xiao Lin?
Xiao Lin.
You look new here.
Are you a disciple of Xiaoyao Sect?
How may I address you?
Why are you here?
Me?
I'm afraid you mistook me for someone else.
I am Gongye Jiwu.
Eldest disciple of Leader of Hengyang Sect.
Gongye Jiwu?
I see.
Since you're not familiar with this place,
let me walk you out a bit further.
Honestly,
you look very much like one of my
old friends from many years ago.
I wonder where
you come from?
Maybe you two are related somehow.
I was…
Adopted by Immortal Buxu.
I know nothing of my origin, either.
[It's this Immortal Buxu again.]
May I see this Immortal Buxu?
He used to send me a message to save my life.
I'd like to thank him in person.
This is the place.
Since Immortal Buxu passed away,
he's been hiding in this golden flower.
Could you tell me
how he died?
It's said that he had traveled through
the mortal realm and seen every emotion.
He saw through everything
but couldn't acquire the method of immortality.
Till the year when he was ninety.
A new gambling house opened down the mountain.
He went there and won a fortune.
When he came back with his walking stick,
he got too excited and fell.
Then he died seven days later.
Then how should I thank him in person?
I just need to summon him with my spell.
Like this.
[Pang Yizhi?]
[I've come this time]
[to trade something with Your Majesty.]
[I want a bottle of your heart-tip blood.]
[Pang Yizhi,]
[why do you need this blood?]
[This doesn't concern you, Your Majesty.]
Is this his primordial spirit or an illusion?
Neither.
It's an interesting spell called Cloud.
It was created by Immortal Buxu.
He said that physical bodies will perish,
but consciousness lasts forever.
That's why he cast this spell before he died
to preserve his consciousness.
Brother Gongye,
I have some questions to ask Immortal Buxu.
Would you
leave us alone for a moment?
You may go ahead.
I happen to have other things to do.
I'll take my leave.
Immortal Buxu.
Pang Yizhi.
Do you know where
Ye Xiwu's primordial spirit is?
How should I find her?
[If you want to tell your fortune,]
[you need to use a spell from my sect.]
Pang Yizhi!
[What are the secrets of this immortal sect?]
[The long dead Xiao Lin]
[actually stands here alive.]
[Why would Pang Yizhi tell Zhaoyou to save me?]
Son,
weren't you in a hurry to leave?
Why are you still here
till now?
Is it because Xiaoyao Sect is too big
and you've got lost?
Do you need me to walk you out personally?
I heard that your sect has the Cloud spell.
I'm here for a divination.
You need the help from Immortal Buxu's Cloud?
But,
if you want him to answer your question,
you must enter our sect first.
Only after you've learned our way
can you summon him with your divine energy.
[Since Xiao Lin is here,]
[could Ye Xiwu also be…]
[I need to stay to get to the bottom of it.]
Please enlighten me, Sect Leader.
Although you've kneeled to me,
I didn't agree to take you in.
It's not so easy
to join the Xiaoyao Sect.
How about this?
Get up.
How about you
go do something for me?
If you completed,
you won't owe me any drug or treasure.
What do you say?
As for accepting you as my disciple…
Come my sword!
This sword is called South Branch.
Forged by my master himself,
it was transformed from plum blossoms.
It has the heart of spring and soul of frost.
It carries no intention of killing.
If you see the world with this kindness,
you'll have no obsession
and see the true freedom.
I'll give it to you as a witness.
When you can awaken it,
you will have understood it.
Only then can you learn the immortal arts
to cultivate yourself.
[Susu,]
[you've been in a retreat for 10 years.]
[Your fatal punishment has passed.]
[Don't overthink anything.]
[Just take a good rest.]
[I've extract the evil bone from Tantai Jin.]
[The line of fate is broken.]
[There will no longer be a Devil God.]
[But what if this is merely a punishment?]
[Tantai Jin,]
[are you really just a dream of mine?]
[When the dream ends,]
[everything will disappear.]
Who's there?
Come out.
Junior Sect Aunt.
Who are you?
I…
I'm not a bad guy.
I'm also a disciple of Hengyang Sect.
So,
you're a disciple of Sect Sister Yao Wei?
You've never seen me before?
Since I was admitted into the sect,
I've heard that Hengyang Sect has a
pure-bodied Junior Sect Aunt.
But you're in a meditation retreat all along.
I could only see that thundercloud.
I was so curious.
But when I saw you just now,
I didn't know why,
but you looked so familiar to me.
Sect Niece,
what's your name, please?
My name is Yue Ya.
You can just call me Yue Ya,
or
Little Moon.
You're called Yue Ya?
Yeah, Junior Sect Aunt.
What's the matter?
[My name is Yue Fuya.]
Sister,
you saved me,
right?
Your original name is Yue Fuya.
You're from the Yiyue Tribe.
Yue Ya is your new name.
Am I right?
You're so awesome.
How can you tell everything?
Fuya,
why would you come to Hengyang Sect?
A sister once saved me
and left a letter to my adoptive parents.
She told them to come here if they needed help.
Later, when I was 15 or so, I was sick.
No doctor could treat me.
When I was about to die,
my parents sent me here like the letter said.
Fuya,
come here.
do you still remember the look
of your savior sister?
Savior sister?
From now on you're called Yue Ya.
Don't tell anyone your original name.
Understand?
[Wish we could meet again someday.]
Are you
the helpful sister?
Sister.
[All of this is not a dream.]
[Some people can still reunite.]
Sister.
[Someone makes me unforgettable,]
[but I'll never see him again.]
[Here it is.]
[In a village ten miles east
of Mount Buzhao,]
[there's a blind old woman.]
Zhi'er.
[She has been waiting for someone
at the village gate]
[for the past fifteen years]
[from day to night, rain or shine.]
Mom.
Zhi'er is back home.
Zhi'er.
Did I hear that right?
Is that you?
Zhi'er.
You've come back!
[The old woman
just has seven days to live.]
My Zhi'er.
[She's a kind-hearted woman.]
[Immortal Sect wants to satisfy her wish.]
[Unfortunately, her son is dead.]
Yes, Mom.
I'm back.
Zhi'er.
Take a good rest.
I'll cook for you.
Be careful, Mom.
[Pang Yizhi may know something.]
[I have to stay at Xiaoyao Sect.]
[No matter where you are,]
[no matter how much time it takes,]
[I will find you.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
Yizhi.
Go.
Do you want to eat?
Yizhi, you know,
in the past 500 years,
Capital of Jing has changed a lot.
Why don't we often
go down the mount to take a walk?
Look, there's a storyteller.
A thousand years ago,
The Jing and the Sheng was one country.
Then it was separated into two by the river.
An emperor showed up
and reunited the two countries,
so that the flourishing age started.
As to what happened thereafter,
please come here next time.
Let's go.
All right.
Excuse me, sir.
[The Past And Present]
If you're not in a hurry,
please stay longer
to tell me another story.
What story do you want?
Tell me about
Tantai Jin of Jing Kingdom
500 years ago.
Okay.
Please sit down.
Yizhi.
Who's Tantai Jin?
He's
the emperor of Jing Kingdom.
Five centuries ago,
the Jing was a weak country,
and many people lived in poverty.
Since Tantai Jin succeeded to the throne,
he turned the tide,
made great achievements,
and has created peace for centuries.
But tonight,
I won't tell you his well-known stories,
but an unknown story.
It is said
Emperor Tantai Jin had his beloved girl.
There is no word about the woman
in the history book.
Even her name is unknown.
She was not given a title,
but received special favor from the emperor.
It's said
after Emperor Tantai Jin passed away,
he was buried with his beloved woman
at Tantai Mausoleums.
In the next 500 years,
The royal Tantai family
has a lot of descendants
and wise emperors.
[He had let go of the past]
[and moved forward.]
[It's true.]
[When we were together,]
[we enjoyed happiness,]
[but also bore hatred.]
[I was just an ephemeral mote]
[in his life road]
[of being an emperor.]
[It's not worth remembering.]
[I should get over it]
[and go on my own road.]
Mom.
Why are you standing here
early in the morning?
What time it is?
It's five o'clock.
Not right…
It's Spring Equinox today.
There's a plum tree in the courtyard
that is very important to me.
You go see if it has bloomed.
[It…]
[It has already withered away.]
The tree has been there for ten years.
Every year I hope it will bloom.
But I never make my wish come true.
[The most painful thing about living]
[is that we can't get rid of memories,]
[Likewise, I'm trapped in the nether land,]
[being washed by Ruo Water]
[with my broken heart.]
[To satisfy the granny's wish,]
[I have to help her let go of the past.]
Pretty.
Mom.
Today
is the last day of nanny
living in the world.
By any means,
I have to satisfy her wish.
[Zhi'er.]
Good son.
Come here.
I have something to talk with you.
What's the matter?
Zhi'er.
What do you think human live for?
I don't know.
People live for the sake of others.
Others?
If not for waiting for my son,
I would have been dead.
If I had been dead,
who would remember or miss
my son?
Mom.
I…
But I'm here.
I'm blind in the eyes,
but in my heart,
I know
you're not Zhi'er.
It's kind of you
to accompany me at the end of my life.
I don't have any regrets anymore.
What about you? Kid.
Where is your home?
Is anyone thinking about you?
No.
I lost my mom since I was young.
My father hated me.
Although some people
around me,
I've never been missed.
But
I had a wife.
She protected me
and saved me.
She tried to
help me to be a good person.
Have you become a good person?
I…I don't know.
She taught me to be kind,
to be merciful,
and to love others.
However, I caused her death.
Now no one can tell me
what kind of person I'm anymore.
If you can find your wife back
when you turn into a bad person,
would you do that?
[She's right.]
[If I have the power of Devil God,]
[I'll find a way to find Ye Xiwu.]
No.
She would not be happy
to see me do that.
That's right.
If you miss your wife indeed,
you shall satisfy her wish.
Do you understand?
What do you mean?
Kid, look.
Look at the plum tree.
Has it blossomed?
Zhi'er had planted the tree before he left.
He said
he would be back
when the plum tree bloomed.
I often water the tree,
because I hope
it's still alive
when Zhi'er comes back.
So he won't feel so sorry
for my old age.
That's the way it is.
I think…
I think I've figured it out.
[Nanny's son is the past
that she has been trapped in.]
[And this plum tree is the key
to unlocking this.]
[As long as nanny thinks
the plum tree is blooming]
[so that her son won't feel sorry
when he's back,]
[nanny will be satisfied.]
[The sword is named Nanzhi.]
[With spring heart and frosty soul,]
[it drives away chillness.]
[Taking Nanzhi Sword as the branch]
[and nurturing it with spiritual power,]
[one can drop his obsession]
[and be free.]
[Plants wither, flourish, and return.]
[All lives live in contentment.]
[Shatter.]
Mom.
Look.
It has blossomed.
I picked up one for you.
Thank you.
You're a nice person.
Mom.
[Nanny.]
[You have live a complete life.]
[You'll be blissful in your next lifetime.]
Immortal Zhaoyou.
Could you be my master?
I want to be your disciple
and stay here for cultivation.
Good.
Kid.
I think you have a bond
with immortal sects.
I knew you will come back.
You got out of Nether Water
and survived.
Before you join in our sect,
I'm going to give you a new name.
I used to be surnamed Cang.
I'll give the surname to you.
You're surnamed Cang.
Your first name is Jiumin.
How's it?
What does Jiumin mean?
It's not the time
to tell the secret.
Do you like
the name of Jiumin?
Thank you, Immortal Zhaoyou.
Immortal Zhaoyou?
Thank you, Master.
Good.
My disciple.
The nanny's wish
has been fulfilled.
I give the sword
back to you.
I'm a beginner
and don't need good weapons.
Jiumin.
What are you worried about?
You
awakened the sword.
In that case,
it has belonged to you.
Keep it.
Come.
I'll show you around Xiaoyao Sect.
Jiumin.
There are six peaks in Buzhao Mount.
The middle peak is named
Xianglu Peak
which is the tallest one.
When the devil weapon was born,
mountains and the earth break.
Buzhao Mount emerged at that time.
Mountains merged into one.
The six peaks stand out.
The sky is like a dome.
All of this form a natural formation.
Our Xiaoyao Sect
is in the middle.
We take the sky and ground as the furnace
to refine all things.
How time flies.
The place that had been soaked
in devil energy
now
has become an immortal sect.
Feel free,
do what you want to,
and go where you want to go,
which is called Xiaoyao.
Therefore,
Xiaoyao Sect created a unique technique
which is called
Xiaoyao Sword-play.
Sword following your heart
and making numerous changes.
Since you've unsealed Nanzhi Sword,
now I'll
teach you to use Xiaoyao Sword.
But you must remember
sword-play follows your heart.
Before practicing the sword-play,
you need to practice it.
[Bone-refining Seal
is the heart of Devil God.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
[Is it pretty?]
[Only when I forget about Tantai Jin,]
[I can gain stronger power.]
[Li Susu.]
[Focus.]
[I can't go on like this.]
[The person I like is you,]
[not anyone else.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
[Are you giving up on me?]
[When I tried to forget about Tantai Jin,]
[for a moment,]
[my power became stronger.]
[I should let go of the past]
[and go on my own road.]
[Is this Heartless Way?]
[If I don't move with it]
[ang practice Heartless Way,]
[I'm afraid when my attainment
is exhausted,]
[the power of Heaven Lake
won't seal the evil bone.]
[Tantai Jin had lived his lifetime]
[as a wise king.]
[I shouldn't]
[let myself be trapped in the memory]
[and be tortured.]
[So this is the life in immortal sect.]
[This is the place]
[where Ye Xiwu used to live.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
[If only I can]
[feel the life 500 years ago.]
Brother.
You left in a hurry that day.
We haven't introduced to each other.
I'm Zang Hai.
If you need any help,
you can come to me.
Thank you.
He's Zang Feng.
Brother.
You're new here.
Let me give you some advice.
Among the disciples of our master,
Zang Hai ranks second.
I rank the third.
What about you?
Every new disciple
would have a new name.
What's your first name?
Cang Jiumin.
You don't have the same surname as us.
Cang is the master's previous surname.
Are you his relative?
I didn't know the master before.
The master must
have given him the name for a reason.
Stop speculating.
Jiumin.
Let me tell you about our senior brother.
Let me tell you.
His name is Zang Lin.
He's a crazy martial artist.
He has a problem in here.
A problem?
Zang Lin.
Zang Lin is just
obsessed with practicing martial arts
and is more hardworking than others.
Yeah…
You're the new disciple?
Why don't we compete?
You must have something special.
Show it to me.
-All right.
-Jiumin.
You're injured. Take a rest.
We're leaving.
Go, Zang Lin.
Have a competition next time.
Have a competition with me.
Junior brother,
the immortal contest counts for much.
Don't forget to practice your sword skills.
The divine is doing me a favor
in cultivation.
Ye Xiwu.
Uncle Zhaoyou,
what's wrong with you?
You know,
I'm gonna need a drink
at the sight of someone with a cold face,
playing a profound thinker.
Or I will be uncomfortable head-to-toe
and with eye twitching.
Where is your wine gourd?
I'll get you a pot of it.
No.
Trifles like getting wine in the future
will be left to my new dear disciple.
But you're such good as I see,
how about I get you something?
Soothsaying your marriage.
Please!
Susu has made up her mind
to practice the Heartless Way.
Susu,
the Heartless Way's no joke.
Have you carefully weighed
pros and cons of it?
Susu has been in suffering for a decade.
But it's more like experiencing nirvana.
In her body,
everything has been reshaped.
A lot of weird stuff goes on
in Hengyang Sect.
Susu is still young
and hasn't been in love.
How has she ever been in love suffering?
And why does she change
to practice the Heartless Way?
It seems
Tantai Jin is my love suffering.
Dad and Uncle Zhaoyou
need not worry about me.
Now that I've shown my resolution to Dad,
there is no need to hesitate here.
Susu,
You may go back.
It's surprising to me.
What Susu said just now
isn't like words a common ignorant girl
would speak.
Susu.
Gongye.
Susu,
I have something to tell you.
Instead,
she is like having been
through storms and stress.
Okay.
Susu,
we've known each other since childhood.
Over the past decade,
my love for you has been rock-solid
every day.
Senior brother,
unexpectedly there is one day
that I'm afraid to look at your face.
Senior brother,
I'm about to say thank you.
I was so young and immature before
and fatheaded in doing things.
But you didn't mind about this.
You often help me
and instruct me.
I'm grateful for it.
I haven't found a way to repay you.
Susu,
have you got nothing else to say
in addition to gratitude?
What about our engagement…
You are close
to me
and I respect you.
That's it.
As for my marriage,
I'll find a way to tell my dad
that I shall decide by myself.
You're really a different person
than you used to be.
I get it.
Susu,
I'll prove it to you.
My love for you hasn't changed
whether it's in the past or now
and what you've been through.
I wonder
if you'll think of me as your marriage partner
in the future.
There's still time.
Senior brother,
I'm unsure what will happen
between you and me.
Now,
I'll just let it be.
I see.
I'll wait for you.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪