♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 14]
It hurts.
It's not right.
If my injury is healed,
will the demonic energy come back?
Forget it, I can't hold back Ming Ye.
But will Ming Ye care about
my sincerity?
The two gods wanted to
test the king's sincerity.
One transformed into a small white dove
and the other transformed into a hawk.
The hawk chased the white dove
and the dove
pounced into the arms of the king.
The white dove pleaded with the king,
"Please save me, save me quickly."
The king, being a sincere person,
said to the hawk,
"You can eat my flesh."
The hawk said, "I can eat your flesh,
but I want to eat the amount of flesh
that is the same weight as the dove.
Otherwise, won't I be at a loss?"
The king agreed,
so he had someone bring a scale.
He put the dove on one end of the scale
and cut a piece of flesh
from his leg
and placed it on the other end.
Guess what happened?
The weight of the flesh was not enough.
So the king cut
another piece of flesh from his leg
and placed it on the scale,
but it still wasn't enough.
He cut all the flesh from both legs,
but it was still not enough.
Why?
I have seen doves before.
Doves are much smaller
than the fishes in our river.
That's because these two gods
wanted to test the king's sincerity.
However, what they didn't expect was that
the king stood up with difficulty
and threw his entire body onto the scale
to exchange the dove's life.
As a result, it was the king's sincerity
that moved the gods.
The king's body was completely restored,
and he ascended to become a god.
However, I still don't understand
why someone's sincerity needs to be tested
by cutting their flesh and blood.
So many people pray to the gods,
claiming that they are sincere.
If he is not faced with
unbearable suffering,
how can we know if he is truly sincere?
I can't give in.
I can't have Ming Ye worry about me.
I haven't seen Sang Jiu these days.
Where is she?
Could it be true, as Tian Huan said?
No. I have to go and ask her.
Ming Ye,
I'm going back to
the Mohe River for a few days.
No need to worry about me.
Is she avoiding me?
Wars have been frequent recently.
I wonder if Sang Jiu
has returned from The Mohe River.
Why can't I meet her?
I miss Ming Ye so much,
but I can't go to him.
Ming Ye,
I heard that you went to battle again.
I pray for your safety.
I have had feelings for you
for a very long time.
Ming Ye,
when can you see my sincerity?
Before, my nanny always said
when she couldn't sleep at night,
she had to gather
demonic energy to make pearls
so as to pass the time.
She actually accumulated
a full bag of pearls.
I once made fun of her,
but I didn't expect that
I am doing the same so soon.
When my shift is over,
I must go back and find Sang Jiu.
Even if she is really avoiding me,
I must see her.
Report!
The traces of a demon group
have been found 300 miles away,
but they don't have any intention to attack.
They are gathering towards the Demon Realm.
Towards the Demon Realm?
Yes.
Follow me.
Let's go spy on them.
Yes.
All gods arrive.
Ming Ye,
Did you find any information
during your search in the Demon Realm?
The Devil God did take action
and has sinister intentions.
Therefore, I have summoned everyone
to discuss a solution.
This time, I sneaked into Barren Abyss
and discovered that the Devil God
is practicing a formation
called All-in-Distress Way.
It seems that this formation can devour
all positive energy in the world,
causing all living beings to die
and demons to thrive.
If he succeeds,
wouldn't this world become the purgatory?
We mustn't allow him
to open the All-in-Distress Way!
But now, it seems that
the Devil God is like an arrow on the bow,
ready to be released.
How can we stop him?
Is there no way to kill the Devil God?
Ming Ye,
since you called us here,
do you have any good ideas?
Yes.
When the Devil God practices the formation,
he will extract the evil bone
and personally guide the negative energy
of heaven and earth.
As long as the evil bone
is not destroyed, the Devil God won't die.
So,
when the evil bone leaves his body,
the Devil God can be killed.
This will be the only chance.
But the evil bone connects
the Devil God and the All-in-Distress Way.
How can we get it?
That's right, Ming Ye.
How should we assist you?
And what do you plan to do?
We can set up an ambush
near the Devil Palace.
When the formation is activated,
the Devil God has to
defend the formation's center.
At that time, I will do my best
to force him away from the center
and stop the formation.
Then I will go with you.
There are many
demon soldiers in the palace,
but I can use the power of
the God of Cosmos to freeze time
and separate the demon soldiers
with the Time Freeze.
This way, you only need to deal with
the Devil God alone.
I'm the God of Universe.
I can be anywhere in the universe,
so I can take advantage
of the Devil God's unpreparedness
to take the evil bone
away from the Devil Palace
and seal it in the Heavenly Pillar.
The Heavenly Pillar is
the supreme place in the universe,
where the spiritual veins of heaven and earth converge.
It is indeed capable
of sealing the evil bone.
The God of the Sun,
Please grant the Nine Palaces
and Eight Trigrams Heavenly Formation.
It seems that it's time
to use this formation.
Indeed.
To trap the Devil God,
we can only use this formation.
The Nine Palaces and Eight Trigrams
Heavenly Formation is granted by the Heavens.
This formation was created
to imprison demons,
but once activated,
both gods and demons will be trapped
and unable to escape, except for Chu Huang
who can control space.
Ming Ye,
are you sure about this?
The Devil God is born from
the negative energy of heaven and earth.
What nurtures him
is the endless pain,
sadness and hatred in this world.
As long as there is
pain and sorrow in this world,
the Devil God will be immortal.
Even as gods,
we cannot match him.
Now we can only gamble on this last chance.
When Ji Ze and Chu Huang leave,
I will use my true form
to hold the Devil God,
trapping myself with him in the formation.
I won't give up until death.
You don't have to worry about me,
even if I'm trapped in the formation,
it's nothing.
I can just risk my divine body
to fight until death.
It's not a big deal to me.
Since you are so brave
and risking your lives,
why should we save our divine power?
If necessary,
we can burn up all of our divine power.
When the Nine Stars are in alignment,
I will move the stars
and rain down celestial punishment
to assist you in killing the Devil God.
Under the punishment,
everything will be destroyed
and the Devil God
will not be able to escape.
Even if we exhaust all gods' divine power,
we can only activate
the Celestial Punishment once,
so we must aim carefully.
I might not come back
from this journey.
I bid my farewell.
From now on,
the survival of all living beings
in the Three Realms will depend on you.
Little Ming Ye, you can go.
Don't worry,
we will take this responsibility.
I, Ji Ze, is honored
to know you all.
I have lived a fulfilling life in the
Shangqing realm for thousands of years.
Now I have no regrets.
After seeing you off this time,
I don't know how many of you will return.
Maybe after this battle,
there will be no more gods in the world.
It will be a new start.
Everyone,
hopefully, we will meet again.
I heard that someone is assisting her
in co-cultivation outside.
So,
she probably doesn't need you anymore.
I might not come back
from this journey.
I bid my farewell.
From now on,
the survival of all living beings
in the Three Realms will depend on you.
So be it.
I will die and my soul
will be destroyed on this journey.
If Sang Jiu has found the person she loves
and to stay with,
it's better than being alone
in Yuqing Palace for the rest of her life.
Sang Jiu,
I'll let you go.
After I kill the Devil God,
and then you can live happily ever after
with the one you love.
Did Ming Ye ask you to give it to me?
Yes, Lady.
Lady!
Ruby.
Goddess.
Send it to Lady Sang now.
Yes.
Ming Ye.
Ming Ye!
What's the point of
sending a piece of paper?
If you really don't want to see me again,
just tell me face-to-face.
Ming Ye.
Ming Ye!
Ming Ye, say something!
Sang Jiu,
You have 24 hours
to pack up and leave Yuqing Palace.
Leave Shangqing realm.
What are you talking about? Are you crazy?
What did I do to piss you off?
For so many days,
I dare not say
or do anything.
I am even afraid to look at you
and talk to you for a few moments.
And now you don't even want to look at me,
are you planning to
use a piece of paper to drive me away?
From the beginning,
it was your father who forced me.
I didn't have any affection for you.
The safety and stability of
Four Continents and Three Realms rely on me,
but you wouldn't stop pestering me.
You asked me to teach you swordsmanship
and clear your negative energy,
but I'm already tired of these things.
Now I can only abandon you.
Because I bothered you?
Yes.
Unbelievable.
I tried to avoid you
and not to bother you,
but
things still ended up like this.
My dad once told me a story
about a king saving a white dove.
He told me that
the king cut off his flesh to feed the hawk
in order to save the dove.
But it was still not enough.
The gods are so unreasonable.
Why someone's sincerity needs to be tested
by cutting their flesh and blood.
That's because these two gods
wanted to test the king's sincerity.
However, what they didn't expect was that
the king stood up with difficulty
and threw his entire body onto the scale
to exchange the dove's life.
As long as you have sincerity,
the gods
will definitely be moved.
I thought I had enough sincerity,
but the god never turned his head for me.
Ming Ye,
I will go back to pack my luggage.
And I will leave
before the sun is out.
Sang…
Ming Ye.
Ming Ye,
I want to ask you one thing.
Have you ever,
even a little bit,
for even one second,
had any feelings for me?
Sang Jiu,
From the moment you and I arrived
in the Shangqing realm
on our wedding carriage,
Why don't you have one too?
Why are you eating everything you see?
to the moment you ate
the untouched divine fruit,
and to your each and every move
when we were together…
never,
I've never loved you.
Sang Jiu,
you must forget me.
I wish you happiness.
Sang Jiu. It's you.
I'm leaving.
I'm here to say goodbye to you.
Alright.
I didn't know you could drink.
Okay,
it's just what I want.
Sang Jiu,
you got something you want to say to me?
No.
Before I go,
I just want to get
what's owed to me.
What?
You owe me
wedding night sex.
Relax.
I created this toxic orb myself.
It weakens a target physically.
It's nonlethal.
Jiu…
Oh,
it also takes away the target's voice.
After tonight,
we'll call it even.
And I hope our paths never cross again.
Jiu,
I know it wasn't the best way to say goodbye.
I'm sorry that I let you down.
Today,
this very day…
After everything that has cost us,
all that preparation,
it's all…
for this fight.
The Devil's Army has gathered near Devil Palace.
The Devil God is planning to cast
All-in-Distress Way over all three realms.
If his plan works,
it means the destruction of all lives.
A complete annihilation.
I must condemn him. Who will join me?
We will gladly join the fight!
Lord of Evil! Lord of Evil! Lord of Evil!
Lord of Evil,
you have control over 100,000 evil cultivators.
That's a crazy number of followers.
No need for formality.
After all, we are all at the Devil God's disposal.
Please, call me Di Mian.
Oh, you truly care about
your own kind, don't you?
Now I see why you fell out with your wife
to cross over to the Devil God.
I can't imagine what it would be
if you ran into her in front of the formation.
Right now we've got bigger fish to fry.
We need to think of a way to
strip our opponents of their powers.
My Lord.
Today, all three realms shall be mine.
The formation of All-in-Distress Way will suck
all the positive energy out of the universe
and fill the space with negative one.
Before long,
all living things will turn evil.
We will come together to share pain.
Si Ying, Jing Mie, Di Mian,
offer your devil energy.
Use the devil artifact as a medium
to combine our powers to create the formation.
So that's the Devil God's
ultimate weapon of mass destruction, huh?
It is my great honor
to be part of this.
Let's all dive into sadness.
Huang,
I'll leave it to you.
Ye, how are you holding up?
Where are you now?
What have you been up to since we parted ways?
The war must still be occupying your time, I guess?
I still think about you sometimes. Can't help it.
I'm worried about you.
I just hope you'll live a long life.
Ming Ye.
You're still alive.
I can't die just yet.
The Devil God is still in one piece.
Let's get him!
We have to stop the Devil God
before the formation is successfully cast.
Time is of the essence.
I'll be off to the Demon Realm first.
The Devil God isn't our only problem there.
There are also three other Devils
and tens of millions of soldiers.
You're hopelessly outnumbered.
You can stop the Devil God all by yourself.
That's all the more reason for me to go first.
I can lure away those three sidekicks of his,
leaving him all alone.
This is outrageous.
Jing Mie, step aside.
Ye did manage to
keep them off the offering altar.
Let's just hope everything goes as planned.
Ye,
I'm ready.
Devil God,
your turn.
How dare you disrespect His Lordship?
Kill him.
This is a Time Freezing spell.
If you want to go back in time
and lose your powers,
by all means, go ahead.
Attention, soldiers.
Yes.
Today, we will make the evils pay.
We will purge the Demon Realm.
Or die trying!
Devil God,
you actually created such evil magic.
If the formation is activated,
it will lead to
the annihilation of all three realms.
With everything gone,
so are all sins.
And I will return to nothingness.
Such a shame your followers
are under the wrong impression that
you'll be running the realms with them.
Turns out it's a suicide mission for them.
Jing Mie, ignore their soldiers
and break the Time Freeze spell.
The truth is, your hands are tied,
whatever my real intention is.
The God of Cosmos' Time Freezing spell
isn't strong enough to take on my evil soldiers.
Not to mention your divine power.
It can't harm me one bit.
Well,
not when our powers are combined.
A portal?
Well,
I hate to admit it,
but that blow was unexpected.
The God of the Universe.
You see, to me,
it doesn't make a difference
how many of them die for my cause.
The All-in-Distress Way formation has been broken.
And the negative energy has cleared.
Everyone, send in backup., now.
You broke the formation.
I see you people came prepared
You serpent,
what else do you want?
Oh, I didn't think the Devil God felt fear, too.
Aren't you full of surprise?
I'm not letting you get away with it this time.
I will kill you today.
I don't care how.
Oh yeah?
Well then, go ahead.
Show me what else you're capable of.
I knew it.
Removing the evil bone from his body
makes him vulnerable.
And once this bone is sealed,
we'll be able to take him out, once and for all.
Huang, it's almost time.
I got you.
No, I got you.
We're just getting to the best part.
It's time.
Nine Palaces
and Eight Trigrams Heavenly Formation,
initiate!
Initiate!
What's that?
It's Nine Palaces
and Eight Trigrams Heavenly formation.
As long as it stays intact,
no one,
not even the Lord,
can get out of here.
Huang, the evil bone's all yours!
Shit, my evil bone.
Catch up with His Lordship.
Kill all the soldiers of the God's Army.
The Devil God is trying to break through the barrier.
Hold on a little longer, guys.
No, he's trapped.
We did it.
Ye, are you okay?
I'm fine.
The barrier has been cast.
Nobody leaves the Demon Realm.
Together, you and I
can finish off the Devil God.
Stripping him of the evil bone
didn't seem to do enough damage to slow him down.
This is going to be one hell of a fight.
On the bright side,
with the barrier formed,
and that once the evil bone is sealed,
it's only a matter of time
before we eliminate the Devil God.
Damn it.
I'm stuck in here.
What am I going to do?
That's the sign of Huang's divine power.
Where'd Di Mian go?
I thought we couldn't get out of this thing.
Follow His Lordship.
What's going on?
Ze,
your divine power is drying up freezing time.
You have to stop
or you're going to run out of divine essence.
The Devil God is gone.
What are you waiting for?
But you…
Please,
Ye,
we both have a duty to follow.
If one of us has to stay,
it'll be me, all right?
Trust me.
Ze!
Ze…
I want you to have this phoenix feather.
It holds all my divine powers.
No matter where you are,
if you want to see me,
it will bring you to me at once.
Give me the evil bone.
I will give it to you
over my dead body.
Huang,
hand over the evil bone.
With it,
I will become a Devil God.
And when I become the King of all three realms,
we can run the whole universe together.
Mian,
I thought you were deceived by the Devil God,
making you untrue to yourself.
But now you're telling me
you want the evil bone
for your own benefit?
Our benefit.
You are the Goddess of the Phoenix Clan.
I have to be the King of all three realms.
Only then will I be good enough for you.
Oh please.
Don't use me as an excuse
to cover up your despicable scheme.
It makes me sick.
Well, well, well.
Can't believe you just stole from my realm,
God of the Universe.
Ye.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪