The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 33]
[I heard the surviving followers
of the Devil God,]
[Si Ying and Jing Mie, lost the devil fetus]
[a while back
at the Battle of the Barren Abyss.]
[That's why they've been out
and about making waves,]
[in the hope of finding the devil fetus
through their devil artifacts.]
[Xiwu, Susu, whoever she is,]
[the Devil God's threat]
[will always be the biggest block
between her and me.]
[We can't start over]
[until I find a way]
[to stop the second coming of the Devil God.]
[I know next to nothing about him.]
[How am I supposed to handle him?]
[But since he's put Si Ying
and Jing Mie on the job,]
they must know about the devil fetus.
[If I could break free from him,]
[then I might stand a chance
of stopping his return.]
[Barren Abyss]
[This is the Barren Abyss.]
[Looks exactly the same
as it did in the Bo're Life.]
[I'm going to go deep into the devil's lair]
[to get to Si Ying and Jing Mie.
It's the quickest way]
[to get to know the Devil God better.]
[This place is like a confusing maze.]
[How do I find them?]
Rain of Swords,
find them!
[Demonic energy swirls in the air]
[where those two are.]
[I'm going to use that
as a compass to get to them.]
[The demonic energy here is thick.]
[They must be that way.]
[It's about time I paid them a little visit.]
That coward Di Mian
took off!
How did he manage to break free from
His Lordship's Decamillennium Demonic Seal?
Wait,
maybe he tampered with
the talismans that he gave us.
I knew this would happen.
Why else would he give a quick yes?
If I ever see him again,
I will rip him to pieces!
What is that?
It's been 10,000 years.
Si Ying, Jing Mie,
do you two remember me?
Yes, My Lord.
So,
how are your missions
coming along?
Si Ying.
My apologies, My Lord.
It took me 500 human years
to pinpoint the location of the devil fetus.
He's now in an immortal sect, hiding.
I need more time.
As soon as I awaken the evil bone within him,
you'll be reborn, My Lord.
I've been trapped
in the Barren Abyss for 10,000 years.
How are you so sure he still has the evil bone?
What if it is destroyed?
Can I still return?
I can assure you that
the evil bone is indestructible, My Lord.
It has a part of your soul.
It will remain
so long as all lives
across all the three realms remain alive,
and grudges continue to grow.
The evil bone is all that's left of me.
I can't control his mind with only that.
No one can resist the will of the evil bone.
Nor can one
stop your return.
If he goes against me,
what do you suggest I do then?
The evil bone will unleash hell on him.
He will eventually die for your cause,
whether he likes it or not.
You seem very certain about it.
Rest assured, My Lord,
no one knows the flaw in your plan
except you.
I knew it was you.
What would a devil fetus
of 500 years of age
know about His Lordship's
resurrection plan devised 10,000 years ago?
Be careful how you talk to the Devil God.
You are just a mortal
lucky enough to be chosen
as His Lordship's devil fetus.
You're not as important as you think you are.
Like it or lump it,
when we collect all three devil artifacts
and activate the All-in-Distress Way rune,
His Lordship will be brought back to life.
However,
if you stay here in the Barren Abyss,
I'll play nice with you.
You are, after all,
the devil fetus of His Lordship.
You should feel honored.
Honored?
You're wrong there.
I am not him.
Not now,
not ever.
You don't get to
come and go as you please!
He has joined an immortal sect.
Determined to pursue what's good.
Deaf to
our words.
So are we supposed to just let him go?
He is essentially the devil fetus.
A wolf
doesn't walk among the sheep.
Father!
Susu.
You…
I was just roaming around.
Don't know how I ended up here.
Now that you're back,
you should go and get some rest.
Father,
come inside and have a cup of tea.
I'll go boil some water.
Lord of Evil?
Di Mian?
[What is he doing here?]
[Does he intend of hurting Susu?]
You're the Devil God?
[He can't be the Devil God.]
[The Devil God hasn't returned.]
You're the devil fetus
the Devil God left behind, aren't you?
It's pretty bold of you to show your face here.
The disciples might take you down
if they see you.
[Seems like
he doesn't know I'm a member of the sect.]
[Guessing he didn't come for me.]
[Is he after Susu, then?]
You can stop pretending to be a man of virtue,
Lord of Evil.
If I hadn't known
you were once the leader of the Demon Clan,
a loyal follower of the Devil God
who massacred thousands of deities,
one of which was Chu Huang,
I thought you were someone else.
Who are you?
[If he's just a devil fetus,]
[how could he know
what happened thousands of years ago?]
[I can't put Susu in danger.]
[I'll find out who he is.]
[He's using Immortal Sect art.]
[But he is a devil fetus.]
[He should be able to do more than this.]
[I'll try again.]
Father!
Susu.
Don't come over.
You don't know this.
He is a…
I know.
I know what you're thinking.
But this man in front of us
is Chang Jiumin,
Xiaoyao Sect's disciple,
not someone else.
Sorry that I can't tell you
the reason why.
But please trust me.
Okay, Susu.
Don't worry.
I won't hurt him.
But you also have to trust me.
This man's background is far complicated
than you can imagine.
You should stay away from him.
Don't be fooled by him.
And I promise you.
As long as he doesn't hurt you,
I won't touch him.
I'll also keep this secret for you.
I see.
It turns out that
the Lord of Evil is your father.
Only Uncle Zhaoyou and he know about this.
Just pretend as if
you know nothing.
Don't blame him.
He is just a degraded devil
who has a blood feud with the Devil God
and thought that you were him.
After all, he's just a repented poor man
who is trying to make amends.
Ye Xiwu.
That isn't my name.
The person I know is Ye Xiwu.
That's not me.
The person you know
has never been me.
Tantai Jin.
Do you want me to keep lying to you?
But I've never lied to you.
I am Tantai Jin,
not what you dread that I'll become.
Ye Xiwu,
every day
in the past 500 years,
I've been carefully recalling
every moment I was with you.
And I've stayed in the Immortal Sect
for a while now.
I roughly know
what you're worried about.
I'm not Devil God.
Whether you'll tell me the truth or not,
I'll never turn into that.
I'll forever keep this
a secret for you.
It's better
to hide it from everyone.
I'll also not breath a word
about the Bone-refining Seal.
There's one more thing.
Bone-refining Seal isn't
the first devil weapon
I came into contact with.
There's also a Devil Crossbow.
I told you
I'd been looking for you
in the Nether River for 500 years.
There, I discovered
and merged with
the God-slaughtering Crossbow by accident.
And that force
delivered me out of the Nether River.
That's how Master found me.
I don't know
how to take it out.
When I woke up,
I was already in Xiaoyao Sect.
If you don't believe me,
you can ask my master,
Master Zhaoyou.
No need.
Have you recovered?
I just suffered some minor injuries
when the Bone-refining Seal backfired.
I'm fine now.
I mean,
the burns you got
in the Nether River.
They were healed by Master.
Good.
You said Ye Xiwu
is just a dream.
But
in Shangqing Realm,
I saw the Hongnai Fruit tree
that was cut down
thousands of years ago sprout again.
Di Mian, the once Lord of Evil,
also has a chance to start afresh.
Do you think
there's a chance for Cang Jiumin
and Li Susu
to start over again?
Jiumin,
isn't it a good thing
that we're in the same sect now?
Why do we have to go back to the past?
♪Every pair of distant stars♪
♪Were lonely souls in the beginning♪
[I'm sorry, Tantai Jin.]
[I can't say yes to you now.]
[Maybe I should leave you]
[and leave this place for a while]
[to take my mind off this]
[and avoid seeing you.]
[It'll be better for both of us.]
[Ye Xiwu,]
[do you really believe in Di Mian's words]
[that I'm Devil God?]
♪I don't care about right or wrong♪
[I've been looking for you for 500 years.]
[I won't let go of the past easily.]
[Morever, I can decide]
[who I am]
[and who I'm going to be.]
[I'll prove to you]
[that I am not Devil God.]
You broke into my life
in the past.
From now on,
I won't leave you alone.
You're often in a daze lately.
Is something bothering you?
You're right.
I'm concerned about a defiant devil fetus.
Isn't it the person
who fought against us
on the Divine Platform a few days ago?
I know him.
He was my enemy
when I went through my tribulations.
Then he really is the devil fetus
Yiyue tribe lost
500 years ago.
He should have possessed
the supreme power of Devil God.
But he is deceiving himself
in the Immortal Sect.
This devil fetus keeps disobeying His Lordship.
Unexpectedly, he's your enemy.
This man is insidious, cunning
and full of schemes.
You must not trust him.
When I was facing tribulations
in the mortal world,
he made me suffer a lot.
It may be hard to take him down by force.
Why don't you let me help you
to make it work?
With your help,
I'll surely be able to revive His Lordship.
Everyone is worried
that the Devil God will resurrect.
If they find out
the devil fetus is living among them,
Immortal Sects will be thrown into a chaos,
pushing blame to each other.
And the devil fetus
will have no place to stay
but return to Barren Abyss.
Brilliant.
This is his past.
We should be able
to find his weakness there.
He is also there.
Who?
The man standing next to Cang Jiumin
is from Yiyue tribe.
He is working for Jing Mie now.
Are you saying
that Nian Baiyu is also in Barren Abyss?
That's right.
Let's do
something nice then.
I'll do as you say.
Chief Qu.
Master.
Your Majesty.
Nian Baiyu?
Jiumin,
you know this evil cultivator?
Yes.
He was my attendant in Jing Kingdom
500 years ago.
When we got separated,
I hadn't turned to the devil way.
I went astray laster on
and it had nothing to do with him.
In that case,
you're turning from evil to good
…and coming to Hengyang Sect
to look for you old master?
Yes.
Nian Baiyu is loyal and kind.
I believe that becoming a devil
isn't in his nature.
I hope you can give him
a chance to start over
on account of our years of friendship.
Your Majesty.
Since you've interceded for him,
well,
I'll let you stay.
Thank you, Chief Qu.
Thank you, Chief.
Get up.
Your Majesty.
Get up quickly.
I…
I'm no longer a king
and anyone's master.
Get up.
Baiyu,
no matter what happened in the past,
you can start
all over again now.
You don't have to stay by my side.
It's up to you whether you want
to stay in Hengyang Sect
or go back to Yiyue tribe.
I want to stay.
Good.
It's not easy for us
to reunite with each other
after a century.
You settle down first
Why are you here?
Yue Ya.
Chief told me to show a devil cultivator
to his room.
I didn't expect it to be you.
Why did a disciple
from Purple-of-Ursa Isles.
become a devil cultivator?
Miss Yueya,
sorry, I…
Chief asked me to settle you in.
Don't worry.
I will do my best
to take good care of you.
Come with me, you liar.
This immortal is incredible.
Yes.
[Jiwu,]
[I don't want to lie to you.]
[There is no room for others in my heart.]
[I got it.]
Thanks you for helping us
fight off the monster.
Sister, look.
This is so pretty.
This is for you.
Let me have a look.
-Miss Mo Nv.
-Everyone, hurry up.
Opening a silk workshop
is indeed a great idea.
Not only can we accomplish the task
with Mr. Si Ying,
but we can also attract some lecherous
and brash men over
to suck the evil essence.
And no one will suspect us.
I've gone through cycles of reincarnation.
So I'm disillusioned with the world.
I've left Barren Abyss.
It is a charitable deed
if I could find you
a place to stay.
Thank you Miss Mo Nv.
[Splendid Silk Workshop]
Someone from Immortal Sect is here.
-Immortal Sect?
Is anyone there?
Mister, what brings you
to my silk workshop?
[Bingchang,]
[I like you]
[not because I have feelings for you]
[but because you're who you are.]
[Unfortunately,]
I haven't told you about it.
We are through
in this life.
Xiao Lin.
Why are you not saying anything?
Oh, it's a handsome man.
[Nothing unusual
from the Devil-detecting Lantern.]
I'm Gongye Jiwu,
a disciple of Hengyang Sect
on Mount Changze.
I was supposed to go
to the capital of Jing.
I entered here by accident
My apologies.
[It turns out that
he's become an Immortal Sect disciple.]
My last name is Mo.
You can just call me Mo Nv.
I am the owner of this silk workshop.
They are all embroiderers.
Miss Mo,
There's a demonic energy around here.
I worry that there's a devil
wandering around.
I don't know if you've run into it.
Mister,
I heard there is a demon
in Capital of Jing.
Maybe it has run over here?
Don't panic.
The lantern in my hand didn't respond.
It shouldn't be somewhere near here.
This is a exorcising talisman
Demons are afraid of it.
Paste it on the door
for protection.
I'll thank you
on behalf of my girls.
By the way,
Mister, are you going to Capital of Jing?
I can give you a ride in my carriage.
There's no need.
It's too much trouble.
Not at all.
Fate has brought us together.
I'm going to town to buy silk thread.
It's a little scary to travel alone.
Since it's in the same direction,
we can go together.
Thank you, Miss.
Nian Baiyu.
You should be memorizing mnemonic
in the room.
What are you doing here?
I haven't seen Cang Jiumin all day.
I wonder what he is doing.
Cang Jiumin?
Lady Susu said
she wanted to take a trip to Jing.
I guess Cang Jiumin has gone with her.
What did they go to Jing?
Are you being a spy here?
You've asked so many questions.
Why are you so nervous?
I'm just joking. You're such a loggerhead.
His Majesty has gone to Jing.
[If the devil fetus is born,]
[the Devil God is likely
to come back to life.]
[Susu is naive and kind.]
[If I take chances,
it may lead to a disaster.]
[I can't stand by and do nothing.]
[Jing Mie's Devil Sound Spell?]
What's the matter?
We've got news from Nian Baiyu.
The devil fetus has gone
to Capital of jing.
Surprisingly, he's a romantic type.
Since he cares so much about that girl,
why don't we make good use of that?
Let's threaten him
with that girl's life.
[This is strange.]
[It should be a bustling street.]
[How come there's no one here?]
[The Descent of Phoenix]
Sir,
wait.
Who are you?
Why are you doing here?
I'm passing by this place
and want to spend a night here.
But the inn is closed.
I don't know what happened.
You better leave.
As night falls,
a demon will run rampant.
It's been more than half a month.
Everyone is terrified
and no one dares to go out.
You should stay
in another inn.
Why?
Why can't I stay in your inn?
The demon target solo travelers.
My inn is the only one
on this street
that hasn't been attacked.
But it'll happen soon.
I'll be doomed if I don't close it.
This demon is so ferocious.
Why don't you get an exorcist
to deal with it?
This demon is so powerful.
The feudal government
has tried their best
but still can't capture her.
Take my advice.
Leave her at once
to save your life.
Lady of Spirituality comes so slowly.
I've waited for you for a long time.
It's the opposite direction.
Why do you always follow me?
I finally got a chance
to walk down the mountain to have fun.
Can we just walk in a different direction?
Finally, you speak to me.
I was just wondering
when you suddenly become mute
as you were still normal
when you came down the mountain.
You follow me around.
You are just like a rascal.
You've wronged me.
I'm not following you.
Even after 500 years,
The Water-splashing Festival
of the Capital of Jing
was still run annually.
People from all over will join in.
I'm a native of the Jing Kingdom.
Of course, I will be here.
If you ask me,
it's you who is following me.
Tantai Jin,
you learned glib-tongued skills a lot
when you were in Xiaoyao Sect,
didn't you?
You didn't cultivate hard there.
Aren't you afraid
of encountering a devil when going out?
Never mind.
You, Lady of Spirituality, are here.
You have great luck
and can protect me.
You are glib.
So enjoy yourself. I'm leaving.
[I don't know if Sect Sister is doing well.]
[I should go back
after going out all this time.]
[So, the Capital of Jing
can be the last stop.]
[If I still can't forget Susu,]
[I'm gonna tell Master about this.]
Are you in a hurry
to go to the Capital of Jing?
Why are you in a hurry?
Slay the evil?
I'm going there for…
an answer.
But I shall slay the evil spirit
when meeting one.
[Xiao Lin,]
[I'm evil now.]
[If you know this,]
[what is your reaction?]
I hear that Emperor Jing offers a reward
looking for warlocks to kill the evil.
The evil seems very vicious
in the Capital of Jing.
So you better take care.
See?
You come here then there is a monster.
It's not good to have you around, is it?
[Gaterhing Spirit & Good Luck]
Then you have to kill that evil quickly,
not losing your reputation.
It's you.
Shopkeeper,
we want to stay here.
Do you wanna risk your life?
I come to
kill that evil.
Miss, why don't you take my advice?
Feel at ease.
Just give me one room.
Shopkeeper,
I'm gonna stay here as well today.
You… You two…
Do you wanna one room or two rooms?
-One room, of course.
-Two rooms, of course.
So…
I came out in a rush,
without any money.
Do you like me to sleep
on the street tonight?
It's ok.
I take them.
Shopkeeper,
give him a room.
The farther away from mine, the better.
Sure.
You are too tricky.
Here it is.
Sir,
you wake up so early.
Lin,
what are you doing here?
I'm worried about you.
You…
come here as well.
Lin,
so great that you are here.
You are adept at evil slaying.
Give us some advice.
Ok.
Why do you stare at me?
Because you're beautiful.
So based on the clues provided
by the locals
and what we know now,
the evil can change shapes and read minds.
Also,
when getting dark,
they can also deceive the divine artifact.
So the general warlocks
have to give up on her.
You have to know yourself
as well as the enemy to take that risk.
I read a book of List of Evils with Pictures
in the Scripture Hall.
It says
there is an evil called Ye Mei.
She can change her looks
and is a sucker for human brains.
She especially prefers those
who have felt the sting of love being rejected.
She will take advantage of you
if you have love thoughts.
The book Lin referred to was read by me.
A weapon is recommended in it
which can be used to track down Ye Mei.
But I can't recall the name
of the weapon now.
That's all right.
The birds and beasts will be asked
to send messages to the sect.
Then Nian Baiyu can check it out for us
in Scripture Hall
and send the weapon for us.
I remember it was on a bookshelf around.
Look at that!
Isn't it the book they're looking for?
Ye Mei, Ye Mei.
That's it.
Ye Mei has a good nose.
She can get what people fear and love
with her nose.
She is sharp-nosed,
so she will fear strong smells.
We can pour spell water along the way
to limit the area she can walk.
You are so careless!
Sorry, so sorry.
You can deploy the red silk
from Lingting country
along the way she'll pass by.
The red silk will be on Ye Mei's body
and can't be got rid of.
Then the tracker will follow it to find her.
She prefers the well-dressed young people
who are alone.
and will become the one they scare or love.
She lures people into the fantasy
she creates,
sucking their brains
when they fear the most.
The one you love?
Don't get the meaningless part.
Then the three of us will split up.
Waiting in the streets
where spell water isn't spilled.
There's a three-way road
with only one exit in the capital.
I will guard the exit.
-I can make sure she has nowhere to go.
-Good wine.
That's a good idea.
One of us can wait for
Ye Mei to arrive in the end.
[The Descent of Phoenix]
A good couple loves each other?
It's not as pleasant as this wine.
[The Descent of Phoenix]
God bless…
Please bless anything go right.
That's the only property I've got.
Please don't ruin it all.
[Beauty,]
[go to sleep now.]
[Tell me what you love]
[and what you fear.]
[Remember to hold the other two for a while,]
[not making spoil our plan.]
[Don't worry, Si Ying.]
[I'll get right on it.]
What is this?
How come I can't get it off?
Hi girl,
it's late at night.
Why are you here alone?
Girl?
Why are you…?
Darling,
you are here.
What?
It's only a short time away,
but you miss me a lot?
[Damn it!]
[I wonder if everything goes well]
[about them.]
You're Ye Mei.
Wait.
Don't kill me.
I won't kill you.
You will be handed over to Emperor Jing.
He will judge your guilt.
Sect Brother,
I have seen
the girl you love.
Do you want to know about her?
You grew up together.
It's you who took care of her
and read and cultivated with her.
You've waited for her for ten years.
Even your master thinks
you're a man worthy of loving.
Demonic words.
I love her
and this has nothing to do with anyone.
I don't care who she loves
and who loves her.
Seize!
Gongye Jiwu,
are you really
not curious about it at all?
Cang Jiumin had married her,
sleeping with her.
Your favorite Sect Sister
is married.
She doesn't love you
but the other one.
She's married to someone else.
She doesn't belong to you.
She doesn't belong to you!
Gongye Jiwu,
you're lucky this time.
[How does this happen?]
[It's you.]
[There are signs of a fight here.]
[Oh, no. Susu.]
Si Ying,
I underestimated the power
of the devil fetus.
And Mo Nv suddenly…
You are such a disappointment to me.
You can't handle the devil fetus.
You can't even control Gongye Jiwu.
Get up.
Listen up.
Our target today is the devil fetus.
Nothing else matters.
I need you
go back
to his divine lover's dream.
And see what the weakness of him is.
It's the Water-splashing Festival.
What place is this?
Why are we here?
You've brought me here.
Look! How lively it is!
Me?
Bravo!
Why are they wearing masks?
It turns out
this is the Water-splashing Festival.
[Where is he going?]
[Tantai Jin?]
[So…]
[It's me.]
These are
the irresistible weakness
of the devil fetus.
Just convince the devil fetus to believe
that Devil God is his inescapable destiny.
Si Ying,
you will get what you want
and control the devil fetus as you wish.
That's interesting finally.
Go and give a big present
to the devil fetus.
[How could I be here?]
[This is the Barren Abys.]
[How come I get back here again?]
Devil God,
it's you again.
What do you bring me here for?
What do I want?
I'm gonna ask you.
Born as a devil fetus,
but you think
you're the God of War, Ming Ye.
Keep my look in mind.
This is the only look you'll ever be.
Wrong!
I used to be a devil fetus.
But now
I am Cang Jiumin,
a disciple of the immortal sect.
If you don't mention it,
I've almost forgotten about it.
Will your fellow disciples
accept you in the immortal sect?
What does this do
with you?
So stupid!
A wolf has to be in sheep's clothing.
Hidden among the sheep,
are you willing to join the immortal sect
just for her?
Look. There she is.
[Tantai Jin.]
[It's all over.]
[You can take off your mask now.]
[You didn't expect it, right?]
[It's me.]
[Tantai Jin.]
All-in-Distress Way lasts forever.
[Do you think, by tricking my affection,]
[you can save the lives
of the Three Realms?]
[Ridiculous!]
[Have you seen it?]
[Remember the face that scares you.]
[That's who I am.]
[No, that's not true.]
[This is a dream created by Devil God.]
Tantai Jin, you can only be me.
[Susu is in danger.]
[I have to go to save her.]
[It turns out]
[that you ]
[always]
[fear me.]
Jing Mie,
what are you hiding here for?
Do you get ready for
the thing I asked you to do?
I walked around just now.
It's a lively place here
on Water-splashing Festival.
It's a pity to ruin it.
A pity?
The festival means a lot
to the devil fetus.
Only this place
can make him realize who he is.
Yes, yes.
What's this?
This one is me.
The other one is you.
Legend has it
that burning the doll of us together,
evil spirits and disasters
can be warded off.
Isn't the earthly custom
interesting?
Wouldn't you be like those mortals
having meaningless affection,
would you?
Remember.
Our only task is about the devil fetus.
After five hundred years,
Water-splashing Festival
looks as lively as ever.
Don't worry.
The nightmare is over.
No Devil God will appear at the festival.
So…
Is the devil yesterday…
So I'm still the one
you're most afraid of.
No.
I believe what you say.
You're not him.
You will never become
that awful look.
How do you know I mustn't be him?
You would never hurt me.
You wouldn't do it before.
And it's even less likely now.
You used to be Tantai Jin.
Now you are Cang Jiumin,
the most kind-hearted disciple
of Xiaoyao Sect.
You are not him.
Nor will you become him.
I believe in you.
I got it.
What?
I've seen the one
the devil made.
That was the one
you showed me in my memory
when it was over the gate tower
and in the thunder of the suffering.
♪My regrets♪
♪In the midst of adversity
there's nowhere to lament the unknown fate♪
♪In the abyss, as time and space keep flowing
the heart calls out♪
♪In the darkness, only you bring light to me♪
He is the Devil God.
You got it?
And you knew it
when you were in the Xiaoyao Sect?
♪You have drifted far from my sight♪
Yeah.
Ever since I joined the immortal sect,
I've always heard
everyone talks about
and judges Devil God.
I'm worried
the one they talk about,
the one in their prophecy
are all me.
I'm afraid of
being exposed one day.
I fear they will discover
that I'm the devil fetus
in the immortal sect
that everyone wanna kill.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪