The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 31]
[Hengyang Sect]
Jiumin,
this is the Hengyang Sect.
Let's go.
The Immortal Sect Competition
will be held in here a few days later.
I'll bring you to widen your horizon first.
It's really magnificent, huh?
[Glow and Thrive]
Let's go meet sect leader Qu.
Allow me to introduce him.
This is my new disciple Cang Jiumin.
[It's him.]
[He was like master.]
[They were both killed by me as the Devil God.]
I'm Jiumin.
Nice to meet you, Sect Leader Qu Xuan Zi.
Have a seat.
Not bad.
Zhaoyou,
you finally took in
a normal-looking disciple.
This is your biggest progress
in the last century or so.
Look what you're talking about.
You really suck at complimenting.
Jiumin,
you came in a bad timing.
My daughter Li Susu just left.
I'll call her back now.
I'll let you two meet.
Thanks, Sect Leader Qu.
But since I entered Xiaoyao Sect,
I've put my mind to cultivation.
Nothing else interests me.
If there's a chance,
I'll meet Miss Susu next time.
Today I'm here to consult you
about something.
Sure, go ahead and ask.
I'll see what I can do.
Five hundred years ago,
I used to live in Sheng Kingdom.
I had a friend
who looked very much alike with your disciple
Gongye Jiwu.
I wonder if there's
something mystic about it.
Jiwu has no parents.
He's not even a "normal" human.
He used to be the Sect Niece
of Immortal Buxu from Xiaoyao Sect.
[A sudden incident took his life.]
[Back then, Immortal Buxu came to Hengyang Sect]
[and borrowed an immortal artifact]
[called the Crystal Lamp.]
[It's said to be made
by the ancient God of War.]
[Although it was slightly broken,]
[it still helped to nurture primordial spirits.]
[He put Xiao Lin's primordial spirit in it]
[and sank it into the core spot of Heaven Lake.]
[After he did that,]
[centuries later,]
[the Crystal Lamp gradually thawed.]
[With the nourishment of divine power,]
[a baby was born.]
[I named the kid Gongye Jiwu.]
I think you've guessed
who he really is.
He's such a special person.
Don't you wanna talk me out of
keeping him in my sect?
Sect Uncle Buxu won't be wrong.
I also think Jiumin is a good kid.
If there's a good chance to enlighten him,
I guess he'll achieve something great.
I trust your vision.
Fantastic.
Now you know how to compliment me, huh?
I was complimenting your disciple.
[I did it.]
Pang Yizhi,
now I know how you rebuilt Xiao Lin's body.
The Heaven Lake of Hengyang Sect is beautiful.
The Leader of Hengyang Sect
has told me everything.
You once
asked me for a bottle of my heart-tip blood.
It must be one of the conditions to rebuild him.
As for the rest, even if you don't tell me,
I'll find out by myself one by one.
To rebuild the body of a deceased person,
you'll need the blood of his enemy,
the tears of his lover,
and the hair and flesh of the deceased himself.
Finally, you'll need to activate
the Soul-gathering Array
where the divine energy is most abundant.
Lover's tears for Ye Xiwu.
The blood of an enemy.
I have them both.
These are not difficult to acquire.
As for her hair and flesh.
[This eye was hers]
[in the first place.]
At most,
I'll gouge it out
and return it to her.
I'll still need the magic array.
Where can I learn the Soul-gathering Array?
You can't bring back a dead person to life.
Practicing this spell is against nature's way.
It's just for meeting your own obsession.
You're trying to stop me?
Is this why you've been keeping
Gongye Jiwu safe?
Because you feel guilty to him.
But you did it
despite knowing this.
You simply miss her.
But it's really unnecessary
to cast this spell to rebuild her.
What do you mean unnecessary?
I've lived five hundred years
just to find her.
Pang Yizhi,
you can't stop me.
Brother Gongye,
you look unsettled
and troubled.
Did something happen?
This actually is supposed to be a good thing.
My junior sect sister Li Susu
safely got out of retreat a few days ago.
So,
your trouble came from her?
After she came back,
she seemed to have lived through something
and changed into someone completely different.
She has the dirtless divine body.
Master looks after her most carefully.
I grew up with her.
But she's been heart-whole all along.
Now after surviving her punishment,
she seems like a different person.
I don't know how to approach her.
Brother Gongye,
don't be so pessimistic.
She didn't understand love in the past,
so she couldn't really respond to your feelings.
Now she's fully grown.
Even if it means you have to start anew,
isn't it a chance to win her heart?
To be honest with you,
actually I…
I was born five hundred years ago.
Five hundred years ago?
Yes.
I had no emotions or love back then.
I couldn't even feel happy or sad normally
until someone showed up.
This person taught me about love,
happiness and sadness.
And then?
Then,
I could finally feel her feelings for me.
But I couldn't let her stay.
I've been searching for her for 500 years.
If she can make you think of her
and can keep you missing her till now,
she must be your true love.
You mentioned it so lightly,
but I guess it must be a sad story
that agonizes you.
Love is the source of sorrows.
I guess I should take my take.
I've waited ten years after all.
To be frank with you,
I feel particularly close to you.
I don't need to hide anything in front of you.
I can say whatever I want.
Although we've only met not long ago,
you feel like an old friend.
I keep feeling that we've been close friends
for many years.
For me,
you're already my old friend.
I used to have
a friend to whom I owe a lot.
He looked just like you.
I've admired him and emulated him
since young.
I wanted to live like him.
Now,
I've entered the immortal sect
to learn immortal arts
and make friends like you.
Maybe I've really had
the chance to live like him.
I cherish this a lot.
I think it's also my pleasure
to befriend you.
You have a strong heart
and an intelligent mind.
I cherish the days of cultivating with you
in Xiaoyao Sect.
Although I don't know
what you've been through,
it doesn't matter.
Whatever happened in the past,
you will always be my friend.
Friend?
By the way, Jiumin,
you haven't told me yet
why you came here today?
Is there anything I can help you with?
I heard that your sect has a spell
called Soul-gathering Array.
I wonder if you know of it?
[Library]
[Book of Demonology]
[Speaking of which, I didn't know anything]
[about the Devil God yet.]
[Sky-Slashing Sword]
[The Sky-Slashing Sword]
[is the Devil God's hand.]
[Bone-refining Seal]
[The Bone-refining Seal is his heart.]
[God-slaughtering Crossbow]
[It's that crossbow.]
So that's God-slaughtering Crossbow.
One of the three devil artifacts.
They interact with the devil fetus,
provide Devil God's power for it,
and also guide those who're looking for it.
[The devil fetus.]
[The Devil God's power.]
[The Soul-gathering Spell]
[The Soul-gathering spell.]
[No wonder Pang Yizhi wouldn't tell me.]
[It's actually a forbidden demonic spell.]
[But I found it anyway.]
[Now my progress on the Heartless Way]
[is behind the]
[Besides, the Heartless Way]
[isn't something that can be achieved shortly.]
[Seems like sealing the evil bone with my body
won't be effective for too long.]
[May be I can find other methods]
[in the Book of Demonology.]
♪All things flow away
Some with ease, some in waste♪
♪A path longer than time
No one to share my sorrows with♪
♪The bell tolls beyond the sunset
I don't know what to write on the paper♪
♪Might as well follow my gut♪
[Now,]
[Soul-gathering Spell]
[I've memorized the ways to launch the array.]
♪The unreserved words of children♪
[Wait.]
[I didn't memorize the method of replacement]
[that requires no primordial spirit.]
♪Leaves change color
Your face seems to have never left♪
♪I see God with my eyes closed
as the autumn leaves fall on me♪
♪It shines on every joy and pain♪
♪Leaves and flowers are falling off♪
♪Now I know what my dream means♪
♪Wandering from place to place
not knowing where I belong♪
♪I have no place to call home♪
♪Nothing lasts forever♪
♪I can't ask for more♪
♪It's an ordinary life♪
♪It's an ordinary song♪
[I've found the residence of that immortal girl]
[whom you asked me to look for.]
[It's by the Heaven Lake of Hengyang Sect.]
[Devil Fetus]
[The origin of the Devil God]
[is called the Devil Fetus.]
[if the evil bone dwells in a body,]
[it can turn into a new devil
after accumulating sins.]
[When it interacts wit the devil artifacts,]
[it'll obtain the Devil God's power.]
[When it was born,]
[its time, location and host can't be told.]
[It's difficult to locate.]
[The bone will not perish]
[if its origin is not eradicated.]
[According to these,]
[Tantai Jin is the devil fetus.]
[But it only says what the devil fetus is.]
[It doesn't say how to destroy the evil bone.]
[Although my dirtless divine body]
[can suppress the evil bone for now]
[and be free from its seduction,]
[my power is receding day by day.]
[I don't know how long I can keep sealing it.]
[Seems like for now]
[I can only use the divine energy
of Mount Changze]
[plus the assistance of Chongyu's power.]
[I can't let the evil bone go out of control.]
[That immortal girl returned to this house.]
[Sorry to interrupt.]
[My apologies.]
[Book of Demonology]
[Soul-gathering Array]
[This array needs to be stimulated by
the primordial spirit of the deceased.]
[If no primordial spirit is available,]
[a drop of blood from a dirtless divine body]
[can gather the soul as well.]
Gather the soul.
The blood from a dirtless divine body.
She has the dirtless divine body.
Master looks after her most carefully.
[If I can obtain Goddess Yuling's blood,]
[I can retrieve Ye Xiwu's primordial spirit.]
[Maybe]
[she can be like Gongye Jiwu.]
[This Heaven Lake…]
[I just miss home]
[when I see the full moon.]
[There's also a lake in the vicinity.]
[When it's summer,]
[the lake water is so clear and cool.]
I'll just lie by the lake to count stars.
In the grass,
there are fireflies flying around.
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up♪
[What's the name of that lake?]
[Where is it?]
[It's somewhere far away.]
[I'll take you there]
[when there's a chance.]
[Now I'm already here]
[But you are gone.]
♪Enlightenment is like washing♪
♪Our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
This sound of harp.
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
[What was that just now?]
[Was it the evil bone?]
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
[I'd better go mediate in the divine well.]
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
[Of course.]
[How could it be her?]
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
The Bone-refining Seal is the Devil God's heart.
It will definitely guide us
to find His Highness's devil fetus.
I didn't expect that one day
we'd come to beg this old geezer.
After ten thousand years,
His Highness's seal is still intact.
Every time I hear Di Mian's screams,
I'd feel so delighted.
Rest assured.
His Highness's seal
can only be undone by the Bone-refining Seal.
Di Mian won't get away.
[For ten thousand years,]
[you've never come once.]
[What's your business]
[here today?]
Let's cut to the chase.
Di Mian,
you and Chu Huang have been married for years.
Do you know how to remove a seal
that's enhanced by the immortals?
[If you need my help,]
[why don't you tell me the whole story?]
During the last 500 years,
although we didn't find the devil fetus,
we accidentally found that
the Bone-refining Seal
was sealed in the Shangqing Realm.
But the Bone-refining Seal
was guarded by immortals' seals.
We can't retrieve it so easily.
[So,]
[now you've found a way in.]
[And then you let me tell you
how to undo the seal,]
[so that you can retrieve the artifact.]
[Take it.]
[As long as you shoot the mantra into the seal,]
[together with your demonic power,]
[you'll be able to remove the seal.]
Lord Wang is surprisingly cooperative.
We'll thank you after we
retrieve the artifact.
[Finally someone is looking for
the Bone-refining Seal for me.]
[As long as they shoot the mantra in the seal,]
[I]
[will no longer need to stay in this hellhole.]
One immortal soldier.
Skip.
I'll take it if you don't.
One She-devil Si Ying.
What game are you playing?
This is called Devil VS God.
It's super fun.
It's said to be invented by Immortal Buxu.
It's popular around the four continents.
Our Xiaoyao Sect is so proud of it.
Junior Sect Brother,
-Shuffle the cards.
-your card is the evil bone.
Try it. You'll definitely love it.
But it may backfire
if paired with other identity cards.
It'll be more badass
if paired with the devil fetus,
because it will summon the ultimate Devil God.
If now there're no
identity cards of gods on the table,
the Devil God will win.
The ultimate Devil God?
Yes.
With the devil fetus and the evil bone,
the ultimate Devil God will resurrect.
By then the Devil God will have
devil artifacts like God-slaughtering Crossbow.
If there's still no immortal showing up,
the Devil God will be able to activate
the ultimate weapon:
the All-in-Distress Way.
But the Chronicles of Four Continents said
the Devil God was killed 10,000 years ago.
The God Devil is born out of sins.
As long as there's pain in the mortal world,
the Devil God will be born
one generation after another.
When the devil fetus reappears,
and the devil artifacts find their owner,
the Devil God will resurrect.
The three realms
will face destruction.
Yeah.
I heard a few days ago the Yunchang Sect
was wiped out by Si Ying and Jing Mie
who were remnants of the Devil God.
I heard it was the Yiyue Tribe
who entered into a bond with the Devil God
that lost the devil fetus.
That's why they wreaked havoc.
They're trying to find the fetus
through the guidance of the devil artifacts.
Then what do the artifacts
have to do with Yunchang Sect?
I have no idea about that.
Anyway, the devil fetus is the origin of evils.
It's safe to say that.
So they've been searching for it for 500 years.
But they
found nothing till now?
If the devil fetus refuses to show up,
the Devil God won't resurrect,
right?
It's not as easy as that.
Although the fetus's will
may not be controlled by the Devil God,
what the evil bone and devil artifacts carry
is the Devil God's will.
It's predestined.
How can it be altered so easily?
If
the devil fetus shows up,
what will happen?
If the fetus shows up now,
the demons will surely go all out
and do anything to awaken the fetus
in order to revive the Devil God.
Now there's no god in this world.
If they managed to revive the Devil God,
even if the immortal sects try out best,
I'm afraid…
We won't be able to stop his resurrection.
The three realms' doom will be inevitable.
This is horrible!
Then we should go find the devil fetus
and kill him before the demons find him!
-Yeah!
-That's right!
What are you doing?
-Master is here!
-Master.
Slacking again, huh?
-Come on.
-Put them away.
Come on.
Master.
Not bad.
Despite training hard for the Competition,
you still remember to treat your master.
Not bad at all.
Sect Leader Cen is about to return
from his traveling.
Please go welcome him
at the hall, Junior Leader.
Welcome back, Sect Leader!
Welcome back, Father!
Mi,
this Wind-harnessing Fan is forged with
rare spiritual gems from four continents.
It's perfect for you.
Take it.
Thank you, Father!
The Immortal Sect Competition is coming.
I hope that you will train harder,
kill more demons,
and protect Chixiao Sect's good reputation.
Yes.
I shall not fail your expectation!
Sect Leader.
A letter from the Leader of Hengyang Sect.
[Lately you found out that
Si Ying and Jing Mie were planning]
[to break into Shangqing Realm.]
[You have always been
keen on eliminating demons.]
[Let's take this chance to unite all sects
and defeat the two demons in one go.]
[Time is of the essence.
Please come soon for a discussion.]
The perishing of Yunchang Sect
is a warning for all immortal sects.
We must unite even more firmly
and give no chance to the demon realm.
Nothing is more dangerous
than underestimating our enemies.
As per the current intel,
the two demons are so eager
to enter Shangqing Realm.
They must be after something.
I think this intel is reliable.
Last month,
when I was assigning shift guards
to watch the entrance of Shangqing Realm,
we suffered from a sneak attack.
An elder even got injured.
Thankfully there's a barrier at the entrance.
It didn't escalate to something bigger.
There's actually such a thing?
I thought
Penglai Island offended somebody.
I didn't expect that it's related to
the two demons from Barren Abyss.
The Immortal Sect Competition is imminent.
For this event,
we must select fresh blood
to fight against the Devil God.
Why don't we just
let them come to this event?
What Immortal Zhaoyou means is that
since the two want to go to Shangqing Realm,
let's host the competition right in there
If they want to get something,
we must close Shangqing Realm even tighter.
How can we host the competition there?
Isn't it like inviting the wolf into the house
and let them have their way for nothing?
Listen to me,
if we set a trap for them,
we're providing them the access,
rather,
to their doom.
Well done.
Good for the guy.
What a poor pack of fervent champions
of saviourhood!
They attempt to trick us.
In that case, why not just do
as they wish
to live up to such a grand design?
All we want is the Bone-refining Seal.
Don't bother to linger over
the fight against them.
I heard of
a minor sect of immortals at the North Sea
called the Purple-of-Ursa Isles.
Perhaps we may
get in disguised as its sectaries.
Jiumin,
this is always the case.
Every time we come to Hengyang Sect,
we're always served with
the roast chicken of Mount Changze,
which has accumulated
plenty of immortal energy here
to serve as a great source
of nourishment.
Up the Mount Changze
stretches the way to
the deities' former residence,
the Shangqing Realm.
The Shangqing Realm?
From this day forward,
the Yuqing Palace will be closed.
And the Shangqing Realm
will see no deity any more.
So all of you
may go your own ways.
[Since the god Ming Ye's departure,]
[the Shangqing Realm has been closed.]
Jiumin,
you know it?
Our immortal sects
were established according to
the will of the gods
to take over as champions
of the justice in the world.
However, it's a hard job.
Hey man,
stop complaining about that.
As the Contest is held,
we can drink deep of this vista.
So will the Contest be held
in the Shangqing Realm?
Exactly.
The Heaven Gate of Triones
is the entrance.
could be found because of the war
between the gods and the devils.
the ancient Devil God
broke the Heaven Pillar,
which dipped and slit the Dome of Heaven.
But it's usually invisible.
Only by the joint work of all the chiefs
can it be opened.
By convention,
all the immortal sects take turns
to host the Contest.
This year,
it's the Glorious Glow Sect's turn.
Chief Cen is simply a miser.
He asked us to do the cleaning
of the Shangqing Realm.
Clean what?
Over the past ten thousand years,
the departure of deities
has left the Shangqing Realm deserted,
which has provided a habitat
for some spirits and demons.
This year,
we hold the contest in order to
work together
to clear the Realm off the evil spirits.
And
Lady of Spirituality is said to attend.
She has got a reputation
among the immortals.
I bet a whole bunch of guys
will kill for a meeting with her.
[Li Susu will show up, too?]
[It's a good chance to ask her
for a drop of her blood.]
Lady Susu,
no matter where I am,
I can always hear the talk of you.
Even some guys have asserted that
it's does not matter
if they win the Contest.
What matters most is
to win the gorgeous Lady.
Leave them alone.
No.
Those libertines
had better pray not to
come into my sight,
or I'll definitely beat them black and blue.
So ferocious of you.
Once they see you tomorrow,
they must stay out of your way.
Where can you catch them?
Lady Susu,
I've got an idea!
Hold it.
What...what are you doing?
It's done.
You little sprite.
Lady Susu,
At your ease tomorrow.
As for something unpleasant,
just leave them to me.
What are you thinking this time?
I have a piece of divine silk veil,
which can obscure
the face of one who wears it.
Then I'll disguise myself as you
and fix those libertines
to teach them a lesson!
I prefer to say
that you'd just like to play a trick on them
to have fun.
Alright.
You need to know
when enough is enough.
Don't go too far.
Okay.
I promise I'll not.
Be reassured, Lady Susu.
All the immortal sects are here.
Here we go now.
[The Resources School]
[The Masculine Integrity Pavilion]
[The Vermilion Pheonix Mansion]
[The Great Medicine Valley]
[The Land-and-Ocean Alliance]
[The Penglai Islet]
[The Xiaoyao Sect]
[The Glorious Glow Sect]
[The Third with the Heaven and Earth]
All the immortal sects are here!
Who are they?
Hi, you two of our allies.
We are from the
May I know where you're from?
We are disciples of Immortal North Star
from the Purple-of-Ursa Isles.
The Purple-of-Ursa Isles?
A minor sect of immortals at the North Sea.
Glad to meet you.
There we go.
Let's go.
What a big crowd!
Look, it's the Hengyang Sect.
Seems it's almost time to begin.
Lady of Spirituality!
She's gorgeous!
She's beautiful!
That's Lady of Spirituality?
Not as attractive as we've heard.
She wears a magic veil,
which will show you nothing, of course.
I presume that
[That's Li Susu?]
only her Mr. Right can know
what she really looks like.
[Just ask her for a drop of her blood,]
[and Ye Xiwu will...]
Lady of Spirituality.
Look.
That's Cen Mi.
By the authority
of his father, chief of one of the Three Sects,
he is arrogant, avaracious and lascivious.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to attend
the Contest of Immortal Sects.
The criterion is the same as
that of the previous.
That is, how many demons you've caught
and how long it takes for you.
Each competitor will receive
an empty Demon-Locking Sachet.
During the contest, whenever
you feel you've got enough,
we can drink deep of this vista.
Finally on how long you've spent
and how much your sachets weigh
depend the top rank in this competition.
You can find partners.
But each group consists of
no more than three.
It's almost time to begin.
Everyone,
Ready, go.
[Shangqing Realm]
[has changed so much.]
[My top priority now]
[is to find out Lady of Spirituality.]
My buddies,
it's such a golden chance
to get access to the Realm.
I have no intention of
winning the competition.
I just want to saunter about
to see what the Realm looks like.
I'd rather go alone.
Please excuse me.
Jiumin.
Lady of Spirituality.
-Lady of Spirituality.
-Miss Susu.
I'm Liu Jianghai, the premier swordsman
of Land-and-Ocean Alliance.
Have you heard of the title of my sword?
It's Rivers-in-Reverse.
I learnt that you've just finished
your secluded cultivation.
So I brought the centerpiece
of our sect's treasures
specially for you to appreciate.
Could you please do me an honor?
Lady of Spirituality.
Would you mind partnering me?
Gosh!
What's that?
Lady of Spirituality.
Miss Susu.
Little Yue Ya has told me that.
Such a big trick
must put you both on the blacklist of them.
It doesn't matter.
I don't like being bothered.
She likes playing pranks.
This plan has a double effect.
If it makes you uncomfortable,
I can transform back into my form.
Susu,
this year
I cannot partner you.
Don't press yourself too much.
Be assured.
I'm just taking a walk for a relax.
[My allies,]
[the barriers of all regions
are to be opened.]
[Let's make it a fair competition]
[and help Shangqing Realm be free of demons.]
[Now,]
[the competition officially begins.]
We've put so much effort into this.
Let's hope the two demons will bite the hook.
Wonderful.
Wonderful plan to lure them out.
I wonder what Leader Qu's got in mind?
Since the first Competition,
all immortal sect members know,
as long as you speak the mantra in the event,
you'll be teleported back to Hengyang Sect.
As long as the two demons show up
in front of our disciples,
we'll be able to
lock on the two demons
from the position of our disciples.
By then we'll set up the barrier,
and we shall personally kill them.
Si Ying,
the demonic energy is abundant here.
The Bone-refining Seal
must be here.
Nian Baiyu,
go search over there.
Report to us if you find anything.
Yes.
What?
You still don't trust him
even when he followed us 500 years?
What do you know?
You can't read their minds.
Let's go.
You!
Harder.
Greetings, Junior Sect Leader.
As long as you do a good job,
Chixiao Sect won't treat you unfairly.
Thank you.
Junior Sect Leader,
we've found the whereabouts of Goddess Yuling.
[Shangqing Realm is a vast place.]
[Even if I entered]
[Ming Ye's Bo're Life,]
[looking for Li Susu is still like]
[dredging for a needle in the sea.]
[Those are]
[disciples of Chixiao Sect.]
It's you.
Junior Sect Leader Cen.
I've never offended you before.
Why did you snatch my things?
What are you looking at?
If you may be so kind, Goddess Susu,
why don't you let me see your face?
I'll not only return
the Demon-Locking Sachet,
but also am willing to
watch the ruins of Shangqing with you.
How can Sect Leader Cen
have such a shameless son like you?
You scoundrel!
Go!
Let go of me!
If you prefer not to take your veil off,
allow me to do it for you.
You're as pretty as expected!
Goddess Susu,
I've been admiring you for so long.
Please accept my feelings today.
Don't touch me.
If you do it again, I'll shout for help.
We're just on a date.
No need to shout.
You bloody rogue!
We're on a date?
In your dreams.
Who's there?
Who dares to assault me?
Make your presence.
Who are you?
Cang Jiumin of Xiaoyao Sect.
It's our own affairs.
None of your business.
Stop your interference!
But I've interfered already.
If you disagree,
you may as well
Cang Jiumin,
I'm the son of Chief Cen.
Are you going to kill me or what?
I dare not.
Then why don't you pull back your swords?
But,
it's a vast realm with many
dangerous demonic spirits.
It's common for one or two disciples
to die in this place.
Brother Cang,
let's talk this through.
Why do you have to be so rude?
Alright.
Apologize.
Sorry.
I shouldn't have assaulted you just now.
I mean
to see what the Realm looks like.
Prince Susu,
I'm sorry for my rudeness.
Please show some mercy
to spare me, Brother Cang!
Alright...
He's the son of Chief Cen.
We cannot punish him.
Please!
Just let me go.
I'd like to give back
your Demon-Locking Sachet.
Princess Susu.
Get lost!
Miss Susu.
Watch your sachet.
Thanks.
You're Cang Jiumin.
Thanks for helping me out.
Was it
the Xiaoyao Sword-play?
It's my first time to see it.
May I know who your master are?
Miss Susu, just forget it.
It's nothing.
I
am disciple of Immortal Zhaoyou.
I heard from my master that
Immortal Zhaoyou just took in a little disciple
whose talent for cultivation is astonishing.
It turns out you're the one.
The demonic energy is getting denser.
The thing we're looking for
would be in that direction.
We can't blow our covers.
We can only walk slowly
in this vast Shangqing Realm.
What a bummer.
Shangqing Realm isn't our home ground.
Let's try to avoid head-on conflicts.
[They're in clothes of Purple-of-Ursa Isles.]
Greetings, I'm Gongye Jiwu of Hengyang Sect.
I'm Xisheng from Penglai Island.
My master is Lord Liuzheng.
Nice to meet you.
You're indeed gentle and cultured.
I've been looking forward to meeting you.
[Jiwu,]
This time, the Immortal Sect Competition is
totally different.
I have more important tasks to entrust to you.
After the beginning of the competition,
You need to work with the disciples
Penglai Island and Xionggui Sect.
to search for those two monsters in
Shangqing realm.
Once you found those two monsters in
Shangqing realm,
report it as soon as possible.
Shangqing realm has the most
positive energy,
so the monsters will be doomed out there.
But is good for the immortal sect
to improve your skills.
Once Si Ying and Jing Mie come,
We can use this opportunity
to take them all down.
The competition has been on for a while.
The two of us have been doing the rounds,
but nothing out of the ordinary.
Did
no monster sneak in at all?
If they change their appearance
and dress up as disciples,
they will be hard to spot.
By the way, Cang Jiumin,
since you settled here,
have you ever seen me?
No, I haven't.
But I've heard of something about you.
[What a mess]
[I've made!]
[If I tell him the truth,]
[will he get angry?]
Cang Jiumin,
I...
What is that place?
It's the Yuqing Palace.
[Ten thousand years ago,]
[it used to be where the gods'
nuptials, funerals]
[and rituals took place.]
[Why does my saunter]
[bring me back here?]
[Tantai Jin,]
[It's so hard]
[to erase you from my mind]
[Why can't I get rid of your image]
[no matter where I go?]
[Ming Ye,]
[please tell me]
[whether you've ever]
if any little bit,
or if for any moment,
[loved me?]
[Ming Ye,]
[in order to fight against the Devil God]
[and safeguard the world,]
[you did give up Sang Jiu.]
[How did you make it]
[Why am I always so indecisive]
[I am always immersed in
memories of 500 years ago]
[I can't help it]
[Ming Ye]
[You and Sang Jiu are separated]
[As well as me and Ye Xiwu]
Ms Li.
Can you
do me a favor?
It turns out
that you want to take my
blood of pure spirit body
to get your wife's spirit back.
I thought...
May you give me a
drop of your blood?
I don't ask for more.
Just a drop of it.
Whatever you want me
to give in exchange,
I'll say yes.
Well...
Cang Jiumin,
I...
I'm not mean with what I have.
And I'd love to help you
get your wife back.
But, I'm sorry I can't
give you the blood of pure spirit body.
Why?
In fact...
[In fact I lied to you.]
[I'm not Li Susu.]
[She's my senior.]
[My name is Yue Ya.]
[So where is Li Susu?]
Why not have a try?
The died Hongnai Fruit
will sprout in ten thousand years.
Even you get a second chance.
I must get more than you.
Jiwu.
Don't we wait for Jiumin?
Don't worry, he's better than you.
Let's go back first.
Who is that?
♪My fate is in prison.♪
♪Time and heart wander in the abyss♪
♪Only you can light me up♪
♪in the dark♪
Ye Xiwu,
is that you?
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪