The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 28]
Ye Qingyu. Pian Ran.
Your Highness, please take
this bottle of Ruo Water.
OK.
What's special about this Ruo Water?
Your Highness,
I was worried about your safety.
To be prepared for
any unexpected situations,
I have specially prepared
this bottle of Ruo Water for you.
It can greatly enhance
the power of the Puppet Soldiers,
which may save your life.
I still have you, don't I?
If our plan still fails,
then I will rush into the palace
and kill all the people
Tantai Jin cares about in front of him.
Fu Yu,
you won't die for nothing.
I will return everything
I have suffered back to Tantai Jin.
Run!
Get out of here!
Run for your life!
Dad!
It's chaos out there.
They said that Tantai Minglang's rebel army
have entered the city,
and they are killing the civilians.
Let's escape the city!
Chuntao,
pack up some small valuables and money,
and leave everything else behind.
We have to hurry and run.
Go, hurry!
Hurry up!
Dad.
Dad,
what are you doing?
Doing what I should do.
But, Dad,
this is Jing's capital,
and what does this kingdom
have to do with us?
Zeyu,
I am already in my declining years,
and my remaining time is limited.
I was powerless when our Sheng
suffered defeat and decline,
and that made me disloyal.
I will never forgive myself
even till my death.
Now that the kingdoms are unified,
the people of every kingdom
are all citizens of the same country.
As someone who practices martial arts,
if I turn a blind eye to
the rebels slaughtering innocent people,
it would be unjust.
I, Ye Xiao, am not
a disloyal and unjust person.
Dad…
Zeyu,
Take Chuntao with you and escape
from the east side as quickly as you can.
No, Dad…
Dad!
I'll kill Tantai Jin's beloved woman,
and Fu Yu,
I will have avenged you.
Dad,
I am also a man from the Ye family,
so I must go with you!
Mr. Zeyu, Mr. Ye!
Chuntao,
have you packed up the money?
Don't lose it.
We may not be able
to take care of you in the future.
You should take care.
Indeed, you are a man of our family.
Dad!
Tantai Minglang is so despicable.
He actually used sorcery
to control the people.
Dad, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Son,
let's protect the people together!
Don't kill me!
Where are Ye Bingchang and Ye Xiwu?
I'll show you the way.
Don't kill me!
The divine essence has been cultivated.
Mr. Ye!
Mr. Zeyu! Mr. Ye!
Mr. Ye died in battle
to protect the people.
Your Majesty,
there are survivors.
These people have been infused with
Spirit Fire by Tantai Minglang,
and are already dead.
They are here doing this
probably to threaten us.
Your Majesty, it's dangerous,
don't go there!
Tantai Jin,
do you like the surprise I gave you?
Don't get too excited yet.
Things are just starting.
I will make everything you cherish
disappear one by one in front of you.
Tantai Minglang,
I will kill you!
[Sima Gate]
Tantai Jin,
[Yingtian Gate]
what took you so long?
You kept me waiting for a long time.
Tantai Jin.
I got you two great presents.
You are really lucky.
I specially
dressed them up nicely for you.
the southern border battle
almost exhausted my power,
but I can't expose any flaws.
Tantai Minglang,
Your subordinates have been
completely wiped out by me.
You are now undoubtedly defeated.
What's the point of resisting?
With my current appearance,
what can't I do?
You are right.
I lost to you this time,
and I am afraid that
I cannot make a comeback.
However, I don't want to
go to hell alone.
Don't, please!
I am reasonable.
Choose one of your beloved
to return to your side,
and the other will be buried with me.
No!
How is that?
Tantai Minglang,
don't go too far!
Ye Xiwu or Ye Bingchang?
Make a choice.
The Lightning Punishment is getting closer.
Ye Xiwu,
at such a critical point,
don't you even want to take a look at me?
If you don't choose,
I will take both of them.
No!
I only have one chance to hit.
So, have you decided?
Your Majesty,
please, save me!
-Ye Xiwu,
-I don't want to die!
-don't you want me to save you?
When two people are wearing
the Yin-Yang Bracelets,
as long as the one wearing
the Yang Bracelet doesn't die,
the owner of the Yin Bracelet won't die.
In terms of the reason,
the one wearing the Yang Bracelet
is using his lifespan
to resist the fatal disaster
for the owner of the Yin Bracelet.
Ye Xiwu,
even if you loathe me,
I would do anything
to keep you alive.
Choose!
Or I'll kill both of them!
Help me!
Choose!
Let go of
Ye Bingchang.
That's good.
This way, I don't owe you anything anymore.
Ye Xiwu,
don't you even care?
Looks like you mean very little to him.
Let me free you then.
[Yingtian Gate]
You will never be able to repay it.
No, no way…
Ye Xiwu,
what are you doing?
Stop it!
Ye Xiwu,
don't you leave me!
I will not allow you to leave me again,
not like what Sang Jiu did.
The World-overturning Jade?
Ye Xiwu,
why do you have it?
This World-overturning Jade
was exchanged
with my left eye from you.
♪I wanna hang it in a wrong time♪
♪to forget my everything♪
It was you…
♪trade you with a drop of tear♪
This is your eye?
Ye Xiwu,
why did you do that?
Because you lost an eye,
and you looked really pitiful.
Tantai Jin!
-You were about to die.
-Tantai Jin!
At that time, I thought that
you should not bear this curse.
Tantai Jin,
now only one of us
can survive,
and I choose you.
I will bear the curse
of the World-overturning Jade.
You see,
now the curse
is about to be fulfilled on me.
No, it won't.
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
Tantai Jin,
stop wasting your strength.
The Lightning Punishment comes after me.
With your mortal body,
you can't block it.
Why did you take matters
into your own hands
and do these things for me?
Yes,
Tantai Jin,
because you are the Devil God.
You were already
the greatest curse in this world,
born with the burden of all beings' karma.
What are you talking about? What Devil God?
Ye Xiwu,
what the hell are you saying?
Tantai Jin,
Do you know why
you were born to suffer loneliness,
with weak family ties?
Why were you born without love threads?
Why do demons fear your blood?
Because you are not an ordinary person.
You were born with an evil bone
and destined to become the new Devil God,
destroying the heaven and earth
and overturning the universe.
No way.
♪Do you know a wise man♪
That's not true.
You are lying.
What Devil God? That's ridiculous!
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
♪Like blessing, like suffering, it never ends♪
Is it?
I don't mind telling you.
Actually, I am not
Ye Xiwu in the first place.
I was born in the immortal sect.
The reason why I came to your side
and became your wife Ye Xiwu
is to reverse the fate
and save the world that you destroyed.
Now, the Four Continents and Three Realms
have become a world of you demons.
Today,
I will slaughter all beings
in the immortal sect.
From now on, there will be
not one immortal bone left
in these Four Continents and Three Realms.
Dad!
No way.
I don't even know them.
I didn't kill them.
That's not me, Ye Xiwu.
Who are you?
All these
have nothing to do with you anymore.
Ye Xiwu,
in your mind,
am I really so horrible
that I am not worthy of your trust?
Trust?
Tantai Jin,
why should I gamble
the fate of all living beings
on the extremely faint hope
that there may still be
a trace of goodness
in the heart of the Devil God?
I cannot afford to take that risk.
What a high-sounding explanation.
Fine,
you've always been cruel.
I'm not some Devil God.
Ye Xiwu,
let me tell you,
I
will never allow you to leave me.
Even if my soul shatters,
and even if I die
under this Lightning Punishment,
I will not
let go of you.
Tantai Jin,
don't overestimate yourself.
From beginning to end,
you were just a target of my mission.
I shot six soul-slaying spikes into you.
I did hurt you,
but I also bore
the pain from the World-overturning Jade.
Now I'm taking your evil bone
and paying you back
with the divine essence.
You won't become the Devil God anymore.
What did you say?
Now we are even.
You won't be able to keep me.
Tantai Jin,
you hate me so much,
and I also hate you to the bone.
[My divine essence for you evil bone.]
[We don't owe each other anything.]
Ye Xiwu,
I don't want your essence.
I'll return it to you.
Stop it now!
I said I wouldn't let you leave me.
Even if I have to live in your hatred forever,
I'm willing to accept that!
You can't do this to me!
Heaven above!
I'm willing to give up my body,
my vitality and my everything.
I wish that we will never
meet again
in every life.
Ye Xiwu,
are you going to abandoning me, too?
♪I've seen winds of every color♪
♪Engulfed by the sea of clouds♪
[Why did you come back to save me?]
Because I love you.
Alright?
[What exactly is love?]
[Love means you don't want him to die.]
[You wanna stay with him.]
[You'll be worried when you don't see him.]
[And you'll be happy when you do.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[staying inside that little loft for too long]
[will turn you into a pervert.]
♪I'm trapped within your one thought♪
[I don't care at all]
[whether others like me or not.]
[As long as you're willing to love me,]
[it'll be enough.]
♪Light and darkness can overlap with each other♪
Ye Xiwu.
♪The most difficult wish♪
♪Is worth the longest dedication♪
♪Maybe only by turning love into sword♪
♪Only then can disasters be
turned into opportunities♪
♪And cut through the horizon of fate♪
[Don't worry.]
[With me by your side,]
[nobody will bully you anymore.]
[We can be as happy as this every year.]
[We still have a chance.]
[Now, in this world,]
[only she hasn't given up on me.]
[Only she is willing to return to me,]
[to keep me company,]
[and to love me.]
[I can ask for nothing more.]
Ye Xiwu!
[Sima Gate]
Ye Xiwu.
Haven't I locked you up in the cold palace
so you can never
escape from me again?
What are you doing in here?
Wake up, Ye Xiwu!
Stop sleeping. Get up, okay?
Yes, the bracelets.
Ye Xiwu,
as long as I'm alive,
you'll be fine.
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
We still have the bracelets.
Where's your bracelet?
Ye Xiwu,
where did you bracelet go?
The bracelet.
Ye Xiwu.
I found it.
Ye Xiwu,
I got your bracelet back.
You'll be okay.
You'll wake up soon.
Why?
Why doesn't it work?
Your Majesty,
the rebels have all been destroyed.
Ye Xiwu,
[it's too cold outside.]
[Let me take you home.]
♪Every pair of distant stars♪
♪Were lonely souls in the beginning♪
♪Floating in the stream of time
and entangled in the threads of love♪
♪Fate is unfathomably deep♪
♪And indifferent to meeting and parting♪
♪Blame heaven for breaking us apart♪
[Tantai Jin]
[go home with me.]
[Let's go home to celebrate the birthday.]
♪To love the people whom you love♪
[I just think that]
[you've lonely living in the palace.]
[So I want you to hang out with me.]
♪I just trap my heart in prison♪
♪The dust of the moon is silent♪
[I'll give you a chance.]
Pick a parcel of land that you like.
See where you'd like to be buried.
Stop showing off.
Who said I'm gonna be with you for life?
[Mother,]
[she is Ye Xiwu.]
[I'm your daughter-in-law.]
[If you could see her with your own eyes,]
[you'll definitely like her, too.]
♪The remaining gentleness♪
♪Thaws out my remaining life♪
[Are you willing to be with me in the future?]
♪Is the pain from loving you♪
[Rest assured,]
[from now on,]
[I'll stick with you every day.]
[There's no way you can drive me off.]
[Okay.]
♪Like a stone smashed into dust
Like a flower falls in an instant♪
[In the past,]
[I was like]
[a blind man living in the dark.]
[I was trapped in void for over twenty years.]
[Everyone says the sun is bright and warm.]
[But I didn't know what exactly]
[true brightness means]
[until I met you.]
♪You alone livened up the entire world♪
Dad.
Mom.
Chief.
The doctor said,
His Majesty's heart were injured to begin with.
Now he suffers from too much grief.
It's hard to tell when he'll wake up.
What about other casualties?
Chief Pian Ran died on her post.
General Ye is being treated.
He hasn't woken up yet.
What about the other Ye family members?
Ye Xiao and Ye Zeyu died for protecting
the civilians when the rebels entered the city.
They have been encoffined.
Give them a proper funeral.
Also,
Ye Bingchang went missing in the chaos.
We've been searching for her.
No results yet.
Keep searching.
Dead or alive, she must be found.
Yes.
[This is Ye Xiwu's room.]
[Why would it be like this?]
[Tantai Jin.]
[Tantai Jin, when are you gonna be back?]
Ye Xiwu,
where are you?
[From now on,]
[I'll stick with you everyday.]
[There's no way you can drive me off.]
Ye Xiwu,
come out!
Ye Xiwu, where are you hiding?
Come out!
Ye Xiwu, just come out!
Why?
[Because she's dead.]
[She left you for good.]
[In order to leave you,]
Come out.
[she's even willing to die.]
Nonsense!
Come out now!
[She's dead.]
[But I won't die.]
Come out!
Just come out!
[Is it because of that woman?]
[What a shame.]
Get away from me!
[She's dead.]
[Everyone around you will leave you.]
That's not true.
[You will only bring disasters
to those who stay.]
[They all hate you.]
[They'd rather die to get away from you.]
[Look how your hands]
[are stained with her blood.]
[From beginning to end you can only live alone.]
What a shame.
I will never
let you have your way.
Ye Xiwu won't leave me!
Why don't you show up now?
Prove it to him now!
Ye Xiwu!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty, the doctor said you need to rest.
Just take a good rest, Your Majesty.
Where's Ye Xiwu?
I'm asking you where is Ye Xiwu!
I don't know.
Scram!
Your Majesty!
Ye Xiwu.
There you are.
I've been looking everywhere for you.
No.
Why are you here?
It's so cold in here.
Wake up.
Come back with me.
Ye Xiwu, wake up!
I'm talking to you.
Ye Xiwu!
[She's dead.]
Ye Xiwu, get up.
-[She abandoned you.]
-Just get up!
Ye Xiwu,
I'm talking to you.
I'm talking to you!
Why don't you answer?
Speak!
Didn't you want to kill me?
Weren't you crueler than me?
I'm right in front of you!
I'm right here!
Get up and keep killing me!
Keep hating me!
Just say one word, please.
Ye Xiwu.
You're really hateful.
[From beginning to end,]
[you can only live alone.]
[Your won't succeed.]
[If I can't save her,]
[I'll die with her!]
The post-war compensations have all been done.
The hardest times are finally over.
But I'm just wondering
when His Majesty will get himself together.
If this goes on, I'm afraid his body will…
Send more hands over there.
Including the hall.
Go ahead now.
General Ye,
you can walk now.
What about His Majesty?
His Majesty's been staying in the mourning hall.
General Ye,
you're Miss Xiwu's younger brother after all.
Please go talk to him.
You're his only family now.
I'll go meet him.
Hold on.
His Majesty sealed the door with demonic power.
Regular people can't get in.
We gotta find out a way.
It's fine.
I can get in.
Let's go.
What's this?
He melted the original Ruo Water Ice Coffin,
so that he could be sealed with her forever.
Just like…
Just like amber.
General Ye,
one will die of coldness
if he's lying in there for too long.
We must get His Majesty out of it first.
Your Majesty!
How dare you do this?
Your Majesty.
Get out.
You're courting death.
And you're hindering my sister
from leaving the world decently.
Leaving?
She's my wife.
She's my queen!
She can only be with me!
What if I insist on taking her away?
Go ahead if you dare.
Why would she marry you?
Don't you know that?
She said she loved me!
Nian Baiyu, stay out of it!
My sister might have loved you,
but you?
You used her
to kill Xiao Lin with her own hands!
You tortured her
so much that she had to kill herself!
Now you're still trying to trap her,
and to stop her from leaving.
Tantai Jin, you hate her so, huh?
No. I don't hate her.
She's the only one who's good to me.
The only one who loved me.
Ye Qingyu, do you understand?
You!
Break it off!
Since that's the case,
just let my sister go.
No.
[Till the End of the Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
Come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪