♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of the Moon]
[Episode 21]
Emperor Jin lives there.
Just do as we agreed.
Go in and take a look.
Take one look and come back.
I'll ask someone to send you back.
Got it. Where are you going?
I'll go see Ye Qingyu.
I'm afraid he broke his head.
His head is already broken,
or how could he like you?
Be quick and neat.
Come on…
Keep going.
How is your injury?
It's fine, thanks.
You're just in time.
Here's a thing that bothers me.
-Chief Pian.
-What did I teach you?
You've forgotten everything
in just a few days.
I don't care whatever kind of imps
you were.
Even I have to
carry my tail between my legs
since we're on board.
If you keep going like this,
the emperor might kill you for your elixirs.
Your Majesty.
[Little Devil God looks fine.]
How's your assignment
[going so far?]
It looks like he isn't seriously injured.
[Has he recovered?]
Your Majesty.
[Thankfully, he's fine.]
If something goes wrong…
[But why is my head so heavy?]
What's that sound?
Are the chefs killing pigs?
No.
Your Majesty.
The crow said it had just seen the devil
who asked them to deliver letters
eight times a day.
[I fled fast.]
[Little Devil God couldn't have seen me.]
Ye Xiwu.
Why are you here?
I hid in the troops.
Pian Ran doesn't know this.
Don't punish her.
I just wanted to see you.
I heard you're injured.
And I haven't heard from you for days.
I…
[A nail.]
Ye Xiwu.
You smell bad.
This dress looks beautiful.
Baiyu, ask the doctor
to bring some medicine.
Yes.
♪Your gaze, a little closer♪
♪Heart beats faster
taking root in the void♪
♪The stars scattered in the sky♪
♪Quietly fall on your brow♪
♪As my heart sets its direction
time passes and deepens♪
♪Let the galaxy be my pillow
and let the moon be my kiss♪
♪I want to enter your dreams♪
♪To explore the spring in your eyes♪
♪We are devout, turning the gears of fate♪
The camp isn't as good as the palace.
If your wound is not treated timely,
it will worsen.
Understand?
♪We are devout
opening the door of our hearts♪
♪Wishing to see only one person
in this lifetime♪
♪Only hoping to be moved♪
♪Not to be afraid♪
♪The mark on my heart
don't ask whether it's worth it♪
It's done.
Is there anywhere else you feel unwell?
No.
Thank you.
I feel…I feel much better.
I'll go back now…
Be careful.
[The demon soldiers couldn't]
[have shown up coincidentally.]
[What exactly is Xiao Yi up to?]
I can't wait
for your demon soldiers to be ready.
Do you have a faster way?
Your Majesty, if you're willing to take risks,
my Lord can give you an idea.
Take the bones of a close relative
of Tantai Jin as a medicine inducer
and nine pairs of boys and girls
as well as Tantai Jin's loved one
as the sacrificial offers.
Only in that way, your wish will come true.
However, the conjuration
requires the bones of his close relative.
Okay, that's easy.
I'll send someone to get it.
As to Tantai Jin's loved one,
I'll have the mad maid here.
There is a sign of thunder for tonight.
It's a good time for the conjuration.
Once the conjuration is finished,
Tantai Jin will die for sure.
[These tents all look the same.]
[Why do I feel I've been]
[circling this place?]
The military region has
a complex topography.
If you're lost,
you can follow Golden Crow.
Tantai Jin.
Don't you blame me for leaving the country
and secretly coming to the camp?
Why did you have to walk here?
That fox was deliberately
giving you a hard time
to make you quit.
Didn't you see that?
So what?
Should I go back?
I never go backward.
I said I would come to see you.
I would keep my word.
But you're late.
My injury
has been healed.
[What did Pian Ran tell me?]
[I should play hard to get.]
Since you're well,
I'll go back tomorrow.
Unless your foot recovers,
you're not allowed to go anywhere.
That makes no sense.
You didn't want me to come
but don't allow me to leave now.
Do you think I'm
such an easy girl?
You…
Ye Xiwu, don't go too far.
You left without saying goodbye
and came to Jia Pass,
leaving me alone
in Palace of Jing
and making me worried about you.
Alright, I won't do it again.
Okay.
[Pian Ran's method worked.]
[Soul-slaying Teardrop is burning again.]
Then I'll go back to sleep.
Be careful.
[Why do I feel unsettled tonight?]
[Lingxing Hall]
[Tomb of Concubine Rou, Yue Ruanruan]
Ye Xiwu.
Ye Xiwu!
Gosh, you…
Absence makes the heart grow fonder.
Every minute of tonight is precious.
What are you doing in my bed?
Do you want me to be assassinated
by Tantai Jin?
You go to his bed.
I'm not going.
You told me to play hard to get.
I…
As we're in the army,
we must always be on guard.
Tantai Jin is the leader of the army
and should set an example for his soldiers.
Ye Xiwu, you…
I…
You beat me.
I thought
you would run back in tears.
I didn't expect you to stick it out.
Ye Xiwu.
You really like Tantai Jin, don't you?
I…
Not very genuinely.
I'm just stupid.
I mean
I'm a dumbhead.
Pian Ran.
Let's sleep.
Good night.
Your Majesty.
What's going on?
Emperor Sheng, Xiao Yi,
stole the skeleton of Empress Dowager.
Quick… Hurry up.
Quick.
Pian Ran.
Tantai Jin.
Ye Xiwu.
Why is Tantai Jin suddenly leaving the camp?
What happened?
I have no idea.
I haven't been told, either.
Stay in your tent.
Don't come out, understand?
How much longer?
Your Majesty.
The spell will be done in a quarter.
Is your spell
really as good as you said?
I dare not lie to you, your Majesty.
The spell is super powerful.
No one can get rid of it.
The skeleton of Yue Ruanruan
has been crushed into ashes.
With Tantai Jin's maid
as the sacrifice offer,
I will burn them all together
when the time comes.
Tantai Jin will head for his doom.
He'll die of a sudden illness
in three mouths.
Three months is too long.
It's the fastest way.
All right.
Be quick. It's thundering.
Yes.
Your Majesty, what's that?
Your Highness,
there's a woman outside wanting to see you
for something important.
Let her in.
Yes.
Xiao Lin.
Miss Xiwu.
Are you alright?
What do you mean?
Anything strange happened tonight?
Did you come to send a message?
I'm afraid
Sheng Kingdom will
lose another battle tonight.
Your army is
the last army of Sheng Kingdom.
I heard they had followed my dad
in many battles.
If they're killed,
I'm afraid Sheng Kingdom will…
What did Tantai Jin do tonight?
He left the camp
an hour ago.
I thought he would take a night attack.
I've sent out all the scouts
but received nothing from them.
The Jing Kingdom's military is quiet, too.
Why?
[Tantai Jin.]
[What exactly are you trying to do?]
It's bad.
Miss Xiwu, get on your horse.
I'll ask Pang Yizhi to escort you back.
We can't let Tantai Jin
know you've come here.
Zhong Tai, Chen Xian.
-Ask Dragon Guards to defend the capital.
-Palace of Sheng.
It has been a long time.
How did you get in?
What's the demonic hex?
Xiao Yi.
You ordered someone
to excavate the graveyard of my mother
and take her skeleton to Sheng Kingdom.
Tantai Jin, you want to beat me.
Do you think I didn't know you ganged up
with Prince Xuancheng?
Given your crime,
how can I forgive you?
When you killed your brother
to seize power,
had you thought of getting punished?
It seems like
it was really you who gave the order.
These wizards.
You asked them to cast a spell
on my mom's skeleton
to kill me.
I'm not paying you to stand around.
Keep on.
Kill him.
Xiao Yi.
For your own prestige,
you caused the deaths of innocent civilians.
Protection!
In order to kill me,
you sacrificed your own people.
What's the difference
between you and demons?
I wanted to give you extra days.
Unfortunately, you're asking to die.
Shut up!
Sheng Kingdom is thriving now
and needs your head as a sacrifice.
Since you delivered yourself up,
I'll dispose of you.
At dawn,
the army of Sheng will conquer the Capital of Jing,
and I'll rule the world.
You want to kill me?
Arrest him.
What's wrong with you? Go!
Demonic cultivation.
You learned demonic cultivation!
No wonder Tantai Wuji
had kept you in the palace
and left you for death.
Tantai Jin.
You should have been killed by Tantai Wuji
if you hadn't been a hostage
in the Capital of Sheng.
Is this how you repay your debt to me?
I extraordinarily regret
having shown mercy on you.
I raised you in the palace.
Instead of feeling grateful to me,
you're actually being aggressive to me.
Xiao Yi, you're mistaken.
There's not even a trace
of affection between us.
In Palace of Sheng,
I had been living like an ant.
If there's someone I hate,
the person I hate the most is you.
Xiao Yi.
Kneel,
kowtow to my mother,
and apologize to her.
Then I'll leave your torso alone.
No way!
Drop to your knees!
Dream on!
Stop…
I'll kneel
and apologize.
Tantai Jin, you're doomed!
You monster,
why did you come back?
Why are you still alive?
You want me to apologize to her.
But it's you who should apologize.
Everybody knows
that your mother died giving birth to you.
You caused her death!
Tantai Jin, have you forgotten it?
You should thank me
for calling for the rain
and washing up everything.
Mom.
You are left with nothing.
You jinx, you're doomed.
Go to hell! You monster!
[You promised my mother to take care of me.]
[I'll repay you with the stab.]
[Yingxin.]
[You've suffered too much.]
[Death is a merciful release]
[for you.]
[Jialuan Hall]
Miss.
Miss, where can we go?
You're right.
Sheng Kingdom is conquered.
Where can I go?
Give me your valuable things,
or I'll kill you.
We don't have anything valuable.
Please let go of us.
Miss.
I wanted to rob you,
not kill her.
[All over the world,]
[besides Ye Xiwu,]
[there's actually no one I care about.]
Your Majesty, watch out.
Dragon Guards. You work for Xiao Lin.
Prince Xuancheng will be here in a second.
Tantai Jin, you can't escape.
News surely spreads fast.
But…
it's not your place to decide my fate.
Today,
I won't kill you.
Xiao Yi is dead.
I'll definitely rule the world.
Your Majesty.
[Tantai Jin.]
[The most powerful person in the world]
[is Tantai Jin.]
[Ye Bingchang…]
[Why hadn't I thought of it?]
[The safest place]
[is Palace of Jing.]
Your Majesty, I'm Bingchang.
Your Majesty.
Back off.
Your Majesty, I'm Bingchang.
Ye Bingchang.
What do you want?
Your Majesty.
Now that Sheng Kingdom is conquered,
you've ruled the world.
I'm a weak woman
who has no one to depend on.
Your Majesty, I beg for your mercy.
Please take me with you.
All right.
Take her away.
Prince Lin, they all fainted.
[I'm late.]
[Father.]
[Your Majesty.]
[There's another thing.]
[The crow reported]
[that Miss Xiwu went to]
[Xiao Lin's camp alone after we set off.]
[After that,]
[we encountered Dragon Guards.]
[Miss Xiwu is suspected]
[of treason.]
[Ye Xiwu…]
[Did you]
[write to me everyday because
you were worried about the Sheng?]
[Did you hurry to my camp]
[to protect Xiao Lin?]
[I can't believe you]
[betrayed me for Xiao Lin.]
Why is Bingchang here?
[Right.]
[Little Devil God is fond of her.]
Did you see my medicine?
Pian Ran.
What happened last night?
Did you find out about it?
They went deep into Sheng territory.
The Sheng will be destroyed soon.
By that time,
Tantai Jin probably won't need me anymore
and will let me go.
Do I sound too delighted?
I forgot you were from Sheng.
It's okay.
By the way,
I heard Tantai Jin came back with a woman.
A pretty one.
You should be careful.
All men
are unreliable.
You know, Ye Qingyu
got himself bruised
from head to foot
and got wet in the rain.
I found it.
[Tantai Jin went to the Capital of Sheng.]
[What exactly happened last night?]
[Why did he become like this?]
Tantai Jin.
Were you waiting for me in the camp
last night after I left?
Were you worried about me?
You left the camp abruptly last night.
What happened?
Do you want to know what happened to me
or what happened to Xiao Lin
or what happened to the Sheng?
Yes.
Tell me everything.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
Last night,
I went to Palace of Sheng and killed someone.
Ye Xiwu, you're afraid of me.
I'm not afraid of you.
Why should I be afraid of you?
Look at my eyes.
Don't lie.
Who did you kill?
A lot of people,
some of whom are familiar to you.
Let me think.
[Emperor Sheng, Xiao Yi.]
[Go to hell! You monster!]
[And Yingxin.]
You…
I cut Xiao Yi to pieces
and summoned the blood ravens.
The ravens gnawed him clean
and ate up his bones.
I ripped out Yingxin's neck
and burned her.
By the way,
I want to thank you for tipping off Xiao Lin
and brought him to the gate.
I was so close
to killing him last night
and feeding him to the blood ravens.
Tantai Jin.
I thought…
What did you think of me?
Did you think I was a righteous person?
Did you think
I was not insidious or calculating?
Did you think I wouldn't kill anyone?
Did you think I would forgive them
and let them go?
Or did you think
I was not a heartless freak?
[Right.]
[Devil God is born to be heartless.]
[I actually thought he would mend his way]
[and become a wise king.]
It's true.
You never changed.
You're always the Tantai Jin.
So do you regret it?
You regret staying with me.
You regret saying you liked me.
Yes.
I was blind.
How could I believe
human nature can be changed?
Nature? What nature?
I was being so stupid
for wanting to be with you,
cook for you every day,
and serve you.
Yet you killed someone at midnight!
I would rather
feed a dog than you!
Well said.
That's well said!
I've told you.
I'm born to be heartless.
Now I get it.
Tantai Jin.
[Whoever is around me,]
[whoever serves me,]
and whether they are you or others,
or there's no one,
it makes no difference to me.
Do you think I'm willing to serve you?
Then you get out of here!
Ye Xiwu.
Don't be too arrogant.
Watch your tongue.
Don't think I
will spare your life only.
Your Majesty.
Don't move, please.
You're seriously injured.
Yingxin
almost stabbed your heart.
Take the medicine.
We'll get a doctor
after arriving at the capital.
Keep it a secret.
Doctors can't cure the injury.
Her sword was attached to a spell.
What can we do?
It'll be scabbed after eight to ten days.
Put down the medicine
and get out.
Yes.
Is he here?
Yes… Do you want to go inside?
Who said I would go inside?
The ointment is good
for external injuries.
Yes…
Don't tell him I brought it.
Why can't I tell him you brought it?
Just do as you're told.
Don't be so curious.
If General Ye asks me about it,
I…
You tell him you found it
on the ground or got it out of water
or it dropped from the clouds.
Why?
You're just as obtuse as your general.
Who's outside?
Who is it?
Don't misunderstand.
General Ye's eldest sister
came to visit on His Majesty's order.
Why does she have to see her brother by order?
General Ye.
[It's her.]
Chief Pian brought you an ointment.
Thanks. Keep it.
Yes.
Pian Ran, this is my eldest sister.
Her name is Bingchang.
Bingchang, this is Pian Ran.
She's my…
My comrade.
Are you dumb?
Bingchang, thank you for visiting me.
You must be tired after the trip.
Take a good rest.
Your Highness.
The troops of Jing outflanked us last night.
We got caught up.
After the capital was conquered,
we had to escape here with civilians.
Did you count our troops?
Yes. Casualties account for nearly one half.
The wounded have been captured.
Half of our army is still remained.
They're our last soldiers.
The scout reported
the captured soldiers had been disbanded.
Side Concubine Ye is safe too.
Tantai Jin brought her
to his camp and accommodated her.
She is a woman.
I guess she was cornered into going with him.
You don't need to comfort me.
I'm glad Bingchang wasn't blindsided.
This war has nothing to do with them.
No matter whom she took refuge,
she's lucky to have survived.
Her family is in Jing Kingdom.
She can reunite
with her family there.
Let's forget about these annoying matters.
The emperor has died.
What's your plan?
That's right, Your Highness.
Sheng Kingdom is at stake.
We can't do without a mainstay.
That's right.
Sheng Kingdom
doesn't need the emperor anymore.
Where are the people who escaped
with the army?
Your Highness.
I have failed to defend the capital.
I'm sorry to have disappointed you.
Your Highness, don't be guilty.
Every country has a destiny.
It's not your fault.
Yes. Your Highness.
Your Highness, we got news.
Speak.
We got a secret report
that Emperor Sheng had failed.
He failed the formation
and infuriated Tantai Jin.
He was killed in his palace at night
and burned to ashes.
He's dead,
which is none of my business.
Yes.
I gave demon soldiers to Xiao Yi
because I needed him
to cover for my formation
on the southern border
and needed him to start the war
to pin down Tantai Jin for a while.
It's okay that he's dead.
The two countries are against each other.
No matter who's defeated,
it's not a bad thing.
Now that the formation is almost done,
the entire southern border will soon
become a poison fortress
and no life will survive.
Although Tantai Jin can read animals' language,
there won't be any messengers.
It's brilliant, your Highness.
Let's go
to see our inventions.
Yes.
[Have a taste.]
[I cooked it for a long time.]
Please make an exception for me.
I want to thank His Majesty in person.
You can't.
I left the Sheng in a hurry
and didn't have much money with me.
Buy yourself some things.
No.
Nian Baiyu.
Let her in.
Yes.
Your Majesty.
Are you feeling unwell, Your Majesty?
I came to thank you in person.
I'm much obliged to you
for rescuing me from disaster.
I really don't know how to show my gratitude.
Your Majesty, since you're in a bad mood,
I won't disturb you.
If you want to repay me,
stay with me,
accompany me day and night,
and never leave me.
Yes, your Majesty.
[It was surprisingly smooth.]
Now go and make white fungus soup.
From today on,
you
make me a meal once a day.
I'll go right away, your Majesty.
[Tantai Jin still has feelings for me.]
[Ye Bingchang, you can make any man love you]
[if you want to,]
[including a monster like Tantai Jin.]
[I'll try to please him]
[to gain his trust and become his concubine.]
[Then I'll plan for my future.]
[But I mustn't let the secret]
[of love threads to be discovered.]
[This is the last one.]
[Luckily, not all of them have dissipated.]
[No, Li Susu.]
[You're here not to have a quarrel
with Tantai Jin.]
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪