The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 25]
I'm not hungry.
I'm going to take a nap.
Remember to finish it while it's hot
after marking your memorials.
Ye Xiwu,
have you fallen asleep?
Did you cook this porridge
for me specifically?
I'm asking you
whether you made
this porridge especially for me.
That's right.
Have you taken it?
Do you want me to take it?
What's the matter?
I guess I'll have some
if you feed me.
I want you to feed me.
(Tantai Jin, you're scaring me.)
Why are you being so mushy
out of the blue?
Open your mouth.
Scholar Pang,
do we still wait?
Yes.
His Highness ordered us
to lead the main army down south
if he didn't return on time.
I will go against his order.
At most, I'll receive military punishment
when Xiao Lin comes back.
Head to the camp and ask the soldiers.
Those who are willing to stay
and wait for Prince Lin
can stay here.
As for the rest, you can
escape to the South with them.
Miss Xiwu, do you feel unwell?
Xiao Lin?
Have we managed to escape?
That's right.
Miss Xiwu,
you don't look too good.
Please hang in there.
Let's find a place
and rest there before dawn.
Your Majesty.
Do you have the result?
Traces of dry mylabris
were found in the porridge.
It's a type of deadly poison
from the Sheng Kingdom.
What will happen if I take it?
It will kill you instantly.
And,
there is no antidote for it.
Ye Xiwu,
did you try to poison me?
So, you wish to assassinate me?
Didn't you say that you liked me
and wanted to stay beside me?
Why?
Why did you do so?
Nian Baiyu,
get me some Ruo Water.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Mighty Ruo Water,
control her soul.
Ye Xiwu.
Wake up.
Yes, master.
You can do whatever you want now.
Yes.
Ye Xiwu,
were you looking for this?
Tell me.
What do you want to do with it?
To save Xiao Lin.
Ye Xiwu,
did you poison the porridge?
Yes, I did.
So, you did everything
for Xiao Lin's sake?
That's right.
Do you love him?
You're actually
willing to do this for him?
You're willing to kill me for his sake?
Go now.
Tail her.
Let her achieve her goal.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Ye Xiwu,
you said you wouldn't leave me.
It's too late for you to regret it.
Put it on.
It can keep you warm more or less.
Thanks.
Here.
I'm afraid Tantai Jin's soldiers
will leave town soon.
We can't afford to take
official routes along the way.
Xiao Lin,
how did we manage to escape?
I feel a little blurry.
Miss Xiwu, sorry for this.
You have a fever.
Maybe it's because you were frightened
and caught a cold during nighttime.
You poisoned Tantai Jin
and stole the Tiger Tally.
Due to that, we had access
to all city gates.
That was how we made it out.
Everything was proceeding so smoothly
that I felt something was off.
(There are no pursuers or stalkers
behind our tail.)
(Tantai Jin, what exactly are you up to?)
I want you to feed me.
Open your mouth.
That's right.
I remember now.
This is great.
I finally got you out of there.
Miss Xiwu,
you saved my life.
No words can express my gratitude.
I feel much better now.
You should leave.
Tantai Jin will wake up after dawn.
We should leave together.
You stole the Tiger Tally.
Tantai Jin won't let you off.
You mustn't head back.
Miss Xiwu,
we should head to the army camp first.
We need to plan things out.
I have to go back.
I haven't accomplished my mission.
I have to return to his side.
But you're right.
Tantai Jin will be infuriated
if I return now.
I will lay low for a while.
I'll head back
once he cools off.
So, where are we heading now?
The South.
The South?
Do you two intend to leave
the Jing Kingdom together?
What a shame.
You can never
escape from me for the rest of your life.
What's the matter?
Your Majesty,
we received a message
outside of the palace.
Something had happened to the Ye family!
Hurry! The imperial physician is here!
Hurry!
How is it?
Her Ladyship was struck by lethal poison.
I'm afraid
there's no cure for it…
Aren't you an imperial physician?
You have to do something!
Her Ladyship was poisoned by dry mylabris.
This is…
Grandma!
Grandma, please wake up!
(How is he still alive?)
Grandma!
Your Majesty.
Your Majesty, why have you
graced us with your presence?
Mother!
What do you want to say?
Xiwu!
Mother,
what do you want to say?
Your Ladyship,
don't worry.
I'll surely take care of Ye Xiwu
and won't let her suffer any grievances.
I promise.
Grandma!
-Grandma!
-Mother!
Mother!
-Grandma, wake up!
-Mother!
Grandma!
Mother!
Ye Bingchang,
tragedy has befallen your family.
You don't need to return
to the concubine house.
Stay here and take care of your family.
-Grandma!
-Your Majesty.
-Mother!
The porridge Grandma took in the evening
was drugged.
The imperial physician concluded
that it was dry mylabris.
Bingchang said the porridge was made
by Xiwu herself.
Grandma.
She served Grandma a bowl of it.
Ye Xiwu,
did you make this porridge
especially for me?
Traces of dry mylabris
were found in the porridge.
It's a type of deadly poison
from the Sheng Kingdom.
Open your mouth.
Your Majesty,
Xiwu would never poison Grandma.
Grandma must have eaten
the poisoned porridge by accident
and died as a result.
I'm afraid we need to find out
who the poisoned porridge
was prepared for.
There's no need for that.
It was me.
Why?
It's impossible, Dad.
It can't be Xiwu.
Grandma!
Your Majesty!
Ye Xiwu,
time for you to be abandoned by all.
We've finally arrived.
Arrived?
But there's not a single soul here.
We're four days late.
Maybe they've already left.
Let's go take a look first.
Your Highness.
Junior Sect Uncle.
Thank god you're still alive!
I knew you could make it back.
So you defied my order
and waited for another four days?
Yeah.
I've foreseen it.
Welcome back, Your Highness.
Miss Xiwu is also here.
Did you escape by yourself
and took her along with you?
Tantai Jin's gonna be so mad.
Alright.
I can get out of there alive
all thanks to Miss Xiwu's assistance.
You should thank her, Junior Sect Uncle.
Xiwu, what happened to you?
Xiwu?
Ye Xiwu, wake up.
Wake up.
Ye Xiwu,
you'll be back soon.
I'll be waiting for you.
You have nowhere else to be
except by my side.
Your Highness!
Miss Xiwu,
why did you do this?
You followed him all the way here
just to assassinate His Highness
for Tantai Jin?
Miss Xiwu,
how could you do this?
Your Highness.
Ye Xiwu,
even if you will hate me,
even if you will never forget me,
I'll make you stay by my side
to keep me company.
Your Majesty,
you clearly knew what Miss Xiwu would do.
Why did you let her stab Xiao Lin
after the two of them met the Sheng remnants?
Only by letting her betray Xiao Lin
in front of everybody's eyes,
can she be discarded by all
and have nowhere to go.
They will hate her.
Pang Yizhi will hate her.
Xiao Lin will hate her more.
But with the protection of the puppetry barrier,
nobody can hurt her.
She can only return to Jing.
Return to me.
Because there's only me who can protect her,
keep her company,
and love her.
Relay my order to the troops:
catch Xiao Lin and Ye Xiwu.
Remember,
keep them alive.
Yes.
Ye Xiwu,
I'll wait for your return.
Let her go.
Your Highness!
I said let Miss Xiwu go.
I'm sorry.
I didn't do it on purpose.
I didn't know why.
I… I didn't mean it.
Xiwu,
don't be afraid.
It's not fatal.
I won't die for now.
Junior Sect Uncle,
help me get up.
Listen up.
I was hurt by Jing soldiers.
I'm fine now.
It has nothing to do with Miss Xiwu.
Nobody must talk about this.
Remember that?
Yes.
Let's go.
Did you accommodate Miss Xiwu?
I've undo her spell.
She wanted to come look after you.
I stopped her.
This is called Soul-gnawing Wedge.
It sucks blood from the victim.
After many days,
the victim may die from weakness.
What if I dig it out
with a dagger?
You must be kidding.
Listen to me.
You gotta be lying in bed everyday.
Waiting for death?
I'll figure out a way.
We don't have time.
Have you thought of this?
He could've killed me
by using Ye Xiwu as his puppet,
but why did he only immobilize me?
What is this for?
What exactly happened?
Ye Xiwu, wake up.
Xiao Lin's gonna be okay, isn't he?
Why are you walking around
instead of being resting in your room?
Why did you change your outfit?
Someone will prepare a carriage
to send you out of here later.
Where are you sending me?
Just somewhere to lay low.
Don't worry.
The Dragon Guards will keep you safe.
There's a war coming, isn't it?
How can you fight when you're injured?
Just let me stay.
It's all my fault.
I can't just walk away.
Xiao Lin,
are you hiding something from me?
News just came from the capital.
I thought about it back and forth.
I guess I'd better tell you.
What news?
Your grandma
passed away.
That's impossible.
Did your men made a mistake?
Calm down.
You men must made a mistake.
Grandma has always been healthy.
She's perfectly fine when I left.
Xiwu,
If this thing happened because of me,
I must take responsibility for it.
I can only repay what I owe
to your grandma in my next life.
Why did it happen because of you?
Last night Tantai Jin went to the Ye family.
Grandma.
It's all fake.
He just learned how to pretend.
It's Tantai Jin.
Tantai Jin.
Tantai Jin!
Xiwu,
my condolences.
I don't have too much time to stay.
You can't stay here, either.
where are you going?
Your Majesty, according to your order,
the pigeon letter will arrive today.
Okay.
I'll be expecting the good news.
Your Majesty,
why don't you just kill Xiao Lin?
I have my own plans.
Yes.
I've just received His Majesty's pigeon letter.
It says Xiao Lin is too injured to lead his army.
Launch a surprise attack at dusk,
and we'll be able to catch him alive.
Prepare for it immediately.
By His Majesty's order,
Ye Xiwu and Xiao Lin
must be captured alive.
This is the Virid Blood Pill.
It'll stop your bleeding
and keep you alive temporarily.
I didn't expect there's
someone like you who courts death.
Thanks, Junior Sect Uncle.
Go call together the officers for me.
Stop the carriage!
Send me back!
Xiao Lin's gonna die!
By His Highness's order,
I must take you away from the battle field.
Chongyu, help me.
Please.
Your Majesty.
Speak.
Your Majesty,
General Feng led three troops
to surround the headquarters of Sheng army.
But…
He didn't catch Xiao Lin.
They escaped?
No.
We surrounded the Sheng troops,
but Xiao Lin led his remnants and broke through.
He launched a raid from behind
and caught us unaware.
He burned all of our provisions.
He even rescued all the prisoners.
Impossible.
Xiao Lin was stabbed by the Soul-gnawing Wedge.
He can't even get on the horseback.
How can he lead his army?
Did someone see this with their own eyes?
Yes.
All of our soldiers saw it.
It's absolutely true.
He led his remnants
and the refugees and headed south.
But he left this in his camp.
Show me.
Yes.
Brother Tantai,
no,
I should address you as Your Majesty now.
Back when we're in the Sheng palace,
I was a prince and you were a hostage.
Our paths were nothing alike.
When you left the palace and got married,
we're separated and rarely met.
Another year later,
who'd have thought we will be at war
and become each other's archenemy.
Now what separates us will be
the boundary of life and death.
Jing Kingdom is on the rise.
Sheng Kingdom has perished.
But there are still loyal civilians and officers
who choose to follow me.
I've ordered my troops
to escort these refugees southward
and travel far by sea.
Now the world belongs to Jing Kingdom.
My land and people will be yours, too.
They say a kingdom rises
because it values its people.
A kingdom perishes
because it acts the opposite.
I wish that you would treat kindly
this beautiful land and these good folks.
Thanks for granting my wish.
I've nothing else to offer
but this ultimate treasure Heart-guarding Scale.
Please take it as a congratulatory gift.
Xiao Lin,
you're congratulating me like this?
Miss Xiwu,
how come you're back?
Miss Xiwu.
Why are you hanging the memorial banners?
Who's gone?
Also, I have another request.
Bingchang is sensitive and jealous.
Now she's lost her husband.
I'm afraid her life will be difficult.
Although I've cut all ties with her,
I wish that you could spare her life.
My highest respect
and best regards
Xiao Lin
Why are you so stubborn?
Why do you have to sacrifice yourself?
Zhong Tai and Chen Xian will lead
the remnants to leave the camp
and sail south after dark.
What about you?
I don't know.
Sheng Kingdom is gone. Xiao Lin is gone.
This is such a heart-wrenching world.
I don't wanna stay here any longer.
Maybe I'll return to Xiaoyao Sect
and resume my cultivation.
Safe journey.
Miss Xiwu, what about you?
Still no news?
The Moonshadow Guards are all out searching.
But nobody has heard that
Miss Xiwu assassinated Xiao Lin.
There's no rumors saying Miss Xiwu is a traitor.
Doesn't matter now.
Did you find her whereabouts?
Not yet.
The Sheng army camp has all been cleared.
It's said that all the remnants had gone south.
Miss Xiwu didn't follow them.
Should we keep pursuing?
No need.
Let them go.
Ye Xiwu.
Still no news?
Your Majesty, please don't worry.
Miss Xiwu should be back very soon.
Back?
She won't be back again.
She loved Xiao Lin.
She loved Xiao Lin for so many years.
But I let her kill the one she loved
with her own hands.
She's never coming back!
Your Majesty!
Leave me.
Get out!
♪Take a look at this world that we love♪
Yes.
♪The vivid and splendid dreams
are but a regret that won't fade, it seems♪
♪Rather than wake from this slumber
I'd prefer the dream to last forever♪
♪A bond of marriage
entwined for thousands of years♪
♪I soothe the reckless face♪
♪I'm tired of goodbyes and lingering fondness♪
Ye Xiwu,
Have I lost you too in the end?
♪My emotions ebb and flow like the seasons♪
♪Even if sorrows never end♪
♪A fair complexion remains unafraid
of being soaked in tears♪
♪I can exchange everything for this life♪
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
♪True love is rare though♪
♪For I still believe in the touching you gave♪
Do you love him?
You're willing to go this far for him?
You're willing to kill me for him?
♪But this time, who will come and go♪
♪While waiting and enduring this bitter sorrow?♪
[Tomb of Xiao Lin]
Ye Xiwu,
you'll never come back.
You will taste all pains in this world.
You will carry the curse of fate
and end tragically.
Yeah.
I'm afraid
I'll live this life alone.
Stop!
Who's blocking the way? Go away!
How… How could it be you?
I'm… back.
♪I've seen winds of every color♪
♪engulfed by the sea of clouds♪
♪So many lovers didn't get what they want♪
Ye Xiwu,
why do you come back?
I just wanna stay by your side.
♪I'm trapped within your one thought♪
♪I have colored bitterness and happiness now♪
♪Nothing escapes from the rules of the universe♪
♪Even when my heart of fire is covered in ice♪
♪Actually, the sun and the moon
can shine together♪
Ye Xiwu,
that day…
♪The most difficult wish♪
♪Is worth the longest dedication♪
Tantai Jin,
what's past is in the past.
♪Only then can disasters be
Turned into opportunities♪
Let's not mention them again,
shall we?
Okay.
I wanna start over with you.
I forgive you.
Will you forgive me?
Sheng Kingdom is gone. Xiao Lin is gone.
You go with Dragon Guards.
You can always find a place to live.
No.
I still have something
that's left unfinished.
This time,
I must finish it.
Ye Xiwu.
♪I pray that my life only have this moment left♪
♪I can't escape the rule of destiny♪
♪I've suffered and loved♪
♪Actually, the sun and the moon
can shine together♪
♪Light and darkness can overlap with each other♪
♪Love and hate has blurred boundaries♪
♪The most difficult wish
is worth the longest dedication♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪