♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 20]
Don't you have feelings for her?
Feelings?
Yes, feelings.
Anyone can have feelings
for someone else.
[Unless one doesn't have love threads.]
I'll leave you to think about it.
I can find a way to enthrall her.
♪Your gaze, a little closer♪
♪Heart beats faster
taking root in the void♪
♪The stars scattered in the sky♪
♪Quietly fall on your brow♪
One, two, three…
All of them.
-Yes.
♪I want to enter your dreams♪
A full moon is coming soon.
In Mount Changze,
this would be a good time
stargazing along Heaven Lake.
[I haven't seen Tantai Jin for two days.]
[I wonder what he's doing.]
It's so heavy. Do you want to tire me to death?
♪Only hoping to be moved♪
♪Not to be afraid♪
♪The mark on my heart
don't ask whether it's worth it♪
♪Just believe that it's the right time♪
[Pian Ran's tips work well.]
Tantai Jin.
What do you want from me?
Why did you suddenly give me gifts?
Do you like them?
Not really.
However, I've heard
that girls love them.
I thought you would as well.
Throw them away if you don't like them.
♪From the first glance
to being immersed in passion♪
♪I carefully trace the lines of your palm♪
♪We are devout
opening the door of our hearts♪
Tantai Jin,
I made you food to delight you.
Did you send me gifts
for the same good reason?
♪Just believe that it's the right time♪
Let me tell you this.
You need to know their taste.
If you want one happy,
you need to give him what he likes.
Well, what do you like then?
Ye Xiwu, the hour is late
and mosquitos prevail.
Why do you bring me here?
Didn't you want to give me a gift?
Stay here and keep me company
for a little while.
Look. Those stars are shimmering.
Take a seat.
What's wrong? Did something happen?
Nothing.
It's just that the sight of the moon
reminds me of my family.
Not the one out there.
It's the one when I was young.
When you were young?
There was a lake as well.
It's pure and cold in summer.
I used to lay beside it and watch the star
while fireflies lit the bushes.
Look. Fireflies.
Look.
[What's the name of that lake?]
[Where is it?]
[Somewhere far away.]
[I'll show you when the chance comes.]
Your Highness.
We're stuck.
So is the Jing's Army.
We don't know how long it will last.
No.
We're stuck,
but they're not.
Please enlighten me.
Jia Pass has natural barriers,
and it's only 20 miles from the Mohe River.
Even if we manage to pass the river,
we can't breach barriers along it.
Before we realize it,
the Jing's Army will pour from the pass
and force us back to the river.
However, His Majesty has ordered
that we mustn't retreat.
Based on what you said,
we can only win
by confronting the pass after passing the river.
How could that be possible?
We have no supplies
nor stamina.
Tantai Jin knows that very well.
That's why he returns
without caution.
He retreated to lure us,
expecting us to lose patience and attack.
What should we do then?
We have three options.
Option one,
cease fire before it's too late.
That won't do, Your Highness.
His Majesty won't agree.
Option two,
wait until the river freezes.
However,
that might take months.
What about option three?
Option three,
we pretend to attack the river
while sending a squad
to find the weak point.
However, this approach requires cooperation.
I can't do it alone.
Your Highness,
accomplished generals in the court
are either persecuted
or have retreated.
Even General Ye…
We have no men.
There's nothing we can do
but to wait for the river to freeze.
However, His Majesty is paranoid.
He won't allow it.
Moonshadow Guards of the Jing?
What are they doing here?
Let's go.
Your Majesty. It's done.
The letter has been intercepted by the Sheng.
I'll send men to watch their moves.
How about those who have been sent?
They've returned, and some of them are injured,
but their life is not in danger.
Good.
Give them handsome rewards
and a promotion of two ranks.
Yes, Your Highness.
You may leave now.
Why do you want me here?
I have no food for you.
What's this?
A star.
A star?
It fell from the sky
and was collected by a farmer in the north.
[I never thought
he would really look for a star.]
Today is your birthday.
This is a gift for you.
[So today is Ye Xiwu's birthday.]
[And he remembers.]
Why? You don't like it?
No, I'm just a bit surprised.
Ye Xiwu.
I'll give you one-day leave.
Go home.
Great.
Tantai Jin.
Come with me.
Let's celebrate it together.
Sure.
Grandma, I'm full.
Have more. The noodles stand for a long life.
Look at you.
You've lost a lot of weight in the palace.
Chuntao told me
that Tantai Jin stays outside the door.
As far as I can see,
he has every reason
to refuse to enter our house.
As I recall,
when he was here,
he had a pretty tough time.
Even if Zeyu
didn't find fault with him,
me and your father
have never really looked at him with respect.
We mistreated him.
[No wonder he happily came with me,]
[but then refused to come in at the door.]
[It seems that he is reminded
of something unhappy from the past.]
To be honest,
he spares our lives
despite our ill-treatment,
so I'm grateful for that
even though he's an enemy of the Sheng.
Besides, I can tell
he really cares about you.
Xiwu, you should cherish it.
As for other aspects,
we can save them for later consideration.
There's no need to rush.
You're right, Father.
I'm full. I should go back now.
I have some unfinished business in the palace.
Xiwu.
[Ye Mansion]
Tantai Jin.
What happened?
Why do you return so early?
You had a tough time here.
It's so foolish of me to take you back.
I only thought you'd feel lonely in the palace.
The trip is meant to cheer you up.
Yet, you end up waiting for me here.
I…
It's okay.
Did you enjoy your birthday?
That's enough.
Although I didn't visit your family,
still,
I'm happy you take me with you.
Since we have come,
let me show you a place.
[Lingxing Hall]
You mentioned your old home.
This is the place
I desired most when I was young.
[Auntie Lan'an.]
[Do you know where Lingxing Hall is?]
[Is it far from here?]
Lingxing Hall?
They said Concubine Rou is buried there.
She's my mom.
I want to take a look.
Can we reach there in one or two days?
Well, Lingxing Hall
is right beside the city gate.
It's quite close.
Only an hour's walk.
However, it's an imperial graveyard.
It's not for you to come.
Understand?
This one hour's walk
is so long that I didn't finish
until I took the throne.
[Sun Huiran, Concubine Yun, Yue Ruanruan, Concubine Rou
Meng Jingshu, Concubine Lan]
Mother.
She's Ye Xiwu.
I'm his wife.
If you saw her for yourself,
you'd love her.
Tantai Jin is now the Emperor of the Jing.
He's doing pretty well. You can rest assured.
I'll come and see you when I have time.
This is my line.
Come.
I give you this opportunity
to pick a place you like
and decide where you want to be buried.
Stop patronizing me.
I never said
I'd spend the rest of my life with you.
Answer me, Ye Xiwu.
Do you have feelings for me?
One day together, deep love forever.
Of course, you're my husband.
No, I don't mean the marital duty.
I want your true love.
[Little Devil God.]
[This is the only thing I can't give.]
It's fine. I understand.
True love doesn't come easily.
There's no need to rush.
I heard your mother also passed
when you were young.
If you want to commemorate her,
I can set up a spirit tablet here for her.
Don't bother.
She passed away a very long time ago.
Are you sure?
You used to cry
every time you went to pay respects before.
Remember?
A bit late to restore decency, don't you think?
[Sorry, I'm not Ye Xiwu.]
[I'm lying.]
[Why does he want my affection?]
[Is he ]
[in love with me?]
[The spikes accumulate so slowly.]
[I suppose he doesn't understand love yet.]
[Until when]
[will I collect all of them?]
[Ji Ze said after his fall,]
[Barren Abyss Barrier lasts only 300 days.]
[I should move faster.]
[It hurts by one single poke,]
[while nine will pierce his heart.]
Your Majesty.
This is the information we intercept.
How dare Lin harbor such a thought
when I give him the control.
Calm down, Your Majesty.
How can I calm down?
Haven't you heard the rumor in the city?
They said
Prince Xuancheng disapproved of my decision
to start a war.
He thinks I abuse force
at the cost of people.
A rumor is a rumor.
I've urged him many times.
Have you ever seen him deploy his troops?
I suppose everyone in the court
is expecting me
to hand him the throne.
Your Majesty.
Prince Xuancheng is loyal to you.
There must be a reason
why he doesn't deploy troops.
Maybe you think too much.
I didn't mean it.
I suppose you're one of them.
Guards,
drag him out
and club him to death.
-Yes.
Please spare me, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
Please spare me.
Report.
Your Highness. An order from the capital.
What is it, Your Highness?
His Majesty demands us
to march north in three days.
What should we do?
If we do this,
the casualties will be grave.
What do you think, Your Highness?
Follow the order, of course.
Your Highness.
There's something I must say.
A general does what needs to be done.
As you said earlier,
as long as we stay put,
we can hold the Mohe River.
If we attack recklessly,
we're almost sure to fall.
I'm a subject of the Sheng
and the son of Emperor Sheng.
I can't disobey my father's order.
I shall lead the soldiers
and make a final attempt.
This battle is going to be tough.
Yes.
What should we do?
Your Majesty, Xiao Lin has passed the river
and landed on the north bank.
As I expected, Emperor Sheng takes the bait.
Qingyu, I promised you
to unite the country and end the war.
The time has come.
Qingyu.
Follow me. Let's ride to Jia Pass.
Yes.
Where is Tantai Jin?
He left for the battlefield.
Not long ago.
They said Xiao Lin
swooped on the Mohe River last night.
Xiao Lin.
Why didn't he take you?
What an innocent girl.
With so many great generals in the Jing,
including your own brother in the front,
why would he ever think of me?
Your Highness.
The enemy at Jia Pass
didn't expect us to cross the river so quickly.
We can break
through this pass in less than half a day.
It would cost too many lives.
If we can't take Jia Pass today,
we'll lose nearly half of our men.
We'll succeed.
There are only
a few thousand troops here in Jia Pass.
We almost broke
right through here following them.
They won't last long.
Never underestimate your enemy.
We lost our men to cross the Mohe River.
We fought so hard for days
before seeing a glimmer of hope.
If we can't take Jia Pass by force today,
then we crossed the river in vain.
Everyone.
Return to the city at once.
[Jia Pass]
Tantai Jin is already here.
He came faster than I thought.
Your Majesty.
Shall we send the Moonshadow Guards
to flank them from the outside?
We could eliminate them once and for all.
There's no need.
Today, I'll hold Xiao Lin captive
by myself on the battlefield
and destroy the Sheng's will to fight.
-Your Highness.
Your Highness.
He's the Emperor of the Jing.
He can do witchcraft.
I heard that he could drive demon beasts.
It was his Firewing Army
that breached General Ye's defenses
and defeated him in less than half a month.
He was a hostage prince in the Sheng.
His Majesty didn't treat him well.
He's not going to get back at us, is he?
Xiao Lin, we could talk.
Don't go there.
It's okay.
Xiao Lin.
Now you have all the prestige of the Sheng.
If you would submit to me,
I don't mind sharing the world with you.
Likewise.
If you're willing to withdraw your troops
and submit yourself to the Sheng,
I'm also willing to tell my father
and make you a lord.
You really don't care about the lives
of the Sheng's soldiers, Your Highness.
Your army has suffered heavy losses
at the Mohe River and Jia Pass.
You knew that your odds
of winning this battle were slim,
but you couldn't go
against your emperor's orders,
so you decided to take the plunge.
Am I right?
What a pity.
Had I been here a few hours later,
perhaps you really could have taken Jia Pass.
However, as smart as you should know,
even if you managed to retreat today,
the Sheng
will only last for a few more days.
The Sheng has not come to an end yet.
Don't you try to mislead people here.
Xiao Lin.
A great man should go with the flow,
not fight it pointlessly.
Looks like
there's no deal.
Xiao Lin, you knew perfectly well
that you couldn't win.
-Your Highness.
Heart-guarding Scale.
What a treasure.
Jia Pass is such an ideal place
to draw lightning.
Look how much thunderbolt and lightning
just one Lightning Charm can draw.
It's a pity that you reacted too fast,
Your Majesty.
Otherwise, you could personally taste
what it's like to be struck by lightning.
We missed our timing. There's no need to fight.
Let's call it quits and retreat.
Your Majesty.
Let them go.
Why, Your Majesty?
He's a smart man.
This war
was first started by Emperor Sheng.
It's a war with no just cause.
The forced attack on Jia Pass
was just his last attempt.
He knew he couldn't win.
[Only when I reunite all the lands]
[will the war truly end]
Useless!
You are all useless.
Tantai Jin is almost here.
Go back and tell Xiao Lin
that if he can't hold Boshan City,
he doesn't have to come back.
Also, send an edict
to Side Concubine of Xuancheng.
Tell her to come to the palace at once
and stay at the Empress's side.
Your Highness.
Why did you get hurt so badly this time?
Tantai Jin was on the battlefield himself.
Tantai Jin?
His troops will soon reach here.
If we lost Boshan City,
the Sheng will have
no more strongholds to defend.
However, judging from our current situation,
there's nothing we can do.
Your Highness.
A country's fate is unpredictable.
The current situation
is not something you can control alone.
Bingchang, I'm a son of the Xiao family.
My father may be unkind,
but I can't be unfilial.
The current war situation is not good for us.
If I die on the battlefield one day…
Your Highness,
please don't say something like that.
Death is always a hair's breadth
away on the battlefield.
I should have told you this earlier.
Bingchang.
If I die in the future,
I hope you won't have to remain a widow for me.
If you find someone reliable
who happens to win your heart
and can take care of you
for the rest of your life,
it's not a bad idea to marry again.
No.
If that day comes,
I'll die alongside you.
Didn't you say that
no matter how good or bad it is,
you'll bear it with me?
I shouldn't have scared you.
It's okay. Don't cry now.
I'm fine right here.
Don't worry.
No matter what happens, I'll keep you safe.
[However, if you can't even save yourself,]
[how can you save me?]
It took me so hard to collect a few spikes
and now, Little Devil God ran away.
What should I do now?
The way I see it, little meteor,
you're just like him,
all dark inside and out.
And you've got so many holes in you,
just like he has so many tricks and schemes.
Why don't I call you Little Jin?
What do you think?
Little Jin.
Luckily, you won't run away
without saying anything.
[If we are apart for long,]
[those spikes might shrink back again.]
[I wonder how he's doing on the battlefield.]
Tantai Jin said
that if you wanted to talk to him,
you could write a letter
and give it to the crow.
♪Reviewing the past years♪
To Tantai Jin.
♪A bond of marriage entwined
for thousands of years♪
No.
To my husband.
♪I'm never heartless♪
♪My emotions ebb and flow like the seasons♪
♪Even if sorrows never end♪
♪A fair complexion remains unafraid
of being soaked in tears♪
♪I can exchange everything for this life♪
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
♪True love is rare though♪
♪For I still believe in the touching you gave♪
♪While the fireworks of life
are short-lived and easily enjoyed♪
♪But this time, who will come and go♪
♪While waiting and enduring this bitter sorrow?♪
Your Majesty.
Has Ye Xiwu sent another letter?
Yes. It's the fourth one today.
How can she write so much?
The crow will be exhausted.
The crow did complain about it lately.
Put it down.
Yes.
♪Have been pushed away several times by fate♪
♪I've had my fill and left in a flutter♪
To my husband, Jin.
♪But I never forget that you have no regrets♪
[I was back at Ye Mansion this evening.]
[I had Grandma's flower cake.]
[It tastes sweet and smells so nice.]
[You would love it]
[if you were here.]
[So I learned how to make them with Grandma.]
[However, I don't know
why the flower cakes I made smelled funny.]
[How is the food in the barracks?]
[Not so good. I bet.]
[Come back soon. I'll be waiting for you.]
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
♪True love is rare though♪
♪For I still believe in the touching you gave♪
[No.]
[I can't let her see
that my handwriting has changed.]
♪Who is not willing to let go?♪
♪Who doesn't dare to force?♪
[She urged me to go back.]
[It's probably only
because she didn't want the Sheng]
[to be defeated by me so quickly.]
[I guess it's not because she liked me.]
♪No more talk of leaving or staying♪
♪Silence is the best cure♪
♪One who wants to get drunk needs no alcohol♪
Not only did he leave without telling me,
but he also doesn't answer my letters now.
Xiao Lin was always good at leading his troops.
Little Devil God wouldn't have been
ambushed by Xiao Lin, would he?
The front line ordered me to lead a troop
and leave the capital immediately.
I'm here to tell you
that I'll leave tomorrow morning.
Wait.
Why do you have to leave all of a sudden?
What happened on the front line?
Do you know you're really a jinx?
It's nothing serious.
Tantai Jin is injured. That's all.
Was it bad?
I don't know. He's not dead.
Why are you so worried?
Ye Qingyu is also injured but not seriously.
Tantai Jin and Qingyu both got hurt.
Pian Ran.
Will you take me…
No.
Tantai Jin had given strict orders
before he left
that you must not leave the capital.
I'm just going to sneak a peek.
I won't let him find out.
I'll come back right away
as soon as I'm sure he's doing fine.
Not a chance.
I won't take responsibility for this.
Besides,
if you just want to know how he is,
whether he's dead or alive,
I'll take a look for you.
Didn't you say you didn't like him before?
Why are you so nervous now?
[Capital of Jing]
[This wild girl really can't be stopped.]
[I have no choice but to teach you a lesson.]
Listen, you all.
March a hundred miles before sunset today.
[A hundred miles?]
[I'm so done for.]
[Capital of Jing]
[Li Susu, you're really asking for it.]
Your Highness.
I don't want to leave.
Bingchang.
You'll stay with Mother
in the palace for just a couple of days.
I know.
You're worried
that the people of the Sheng won't accept you.
However, Father also sent
his personal guards to escort you,
so there won't be anything wrong.
Besides, it's much safer
to go back to the capital
than to stay at the battlefront.
Jiahui,
help the concubine get into the sedan.
Yes.
♪As if my wrist were tied♪
♪On to the edge of a gleaming blade♪
♪My keenest quest for your company♪
♪All my life never fades♪
♪The less we talk about it♪
♪The more we are fated to be separated♪
♪All the scenic hours we've spent
are merely mistakes♪
♪We're all in the game♪
Your Highness.
In the future,
I'll not be by your side.
Please take care.
I'll wait for you to come back.
♪I recall the fragrant rains♪
♪Which melt into my eyes' waves♪
♪The peach blossoms,
fallen on the delicate arch of your brows♪
Depart!
♪Beyond the deepest depths of our hearts♪
♪You left me before we could grow old together♪
[It's only a matter of time before we lose]
[and if the capital is breached,]
[what will happen to Bingchang?]
[And what will happen to Father?]
Since Side Concubine of Xuancheng
came into the palace,
she has been following the Empress
day after day to pray to Buddha
and copying sutras in small script.
She also eats vegetarian food with her.
There isn't any meat in her meal.
What a poor woman.
Why should a servant take pity on his master?
The entire Ye family
betrayed our country so shamelessly.
It's merciful to keep her alive.
She's here.
Are you all right, my lady?
I'm fine.
After we get back,
I'll use hot towels to warm your knees.
There's no need for that.
Our place is still leaking.
I'll go ask them to fix it for us.
Don't bother. No matter how many times we asked,
it didn't work.
In the future,
we'll repair the leaking roofs
and torn clothes by ourselves.
As I said before,
power is a powerful tool.
However, I'm just a weak woman.
I can only rely on powerful men.
I thought Xiao Lin was my lifelong support,
but now he won't even answer my letters.
Thank you
for watching out for me
in the palace these days.
I don't understand.
You keep saying
things like this lately, my lady.
I'm a little scared.
It's okay.
I'm here with you.
Let's go.
Be careful.
Your Majesty.
No letter today either.
It has been half a month.
Have you asked the crow why?
You can also speak with birds and animals.
Why don't you ask him yourself, Your Majesty?
This is your family business after all.
Nian Baiyu, you brat. I'll beat you to death.
I don't care if she writes to me or not.
Your Majesty.
All of you must be exhausted today.
Get some rest.
-Yes.
I didn't expect you to keep up with us.
You evil fox.
You knew I was here all along,
and you watched me suffer every day.
I haven't written to him for many days.
I wonder if he has forgotten about me.
[Luckily, that spike didn't shrink back.]
Rest assured. You're playing hard to get now.
As you know,
if you cling to men all day,
they won't take you seriously.
Being cold toward them occasionally
can be very effective.
Trust me.
His Majesty lives there.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪