♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 8]
Why did Yingxin go crazy?
You made her go mad.
She colluded with Tantai Minglang
and tried to kill me.
Can't I fight back?
Prince Minglang said
the hostage prince
should never leave the palace.
Tantai Minglang wants me to kill him?
Yingxin.
Do you remember
a bottle of imperial wine was buried
under the tree outside the gate?
Now we can leave the Palace of Sheng.
How about digging it up?
[She offered me drugged meals]
[and planned to ask Tantai Minglang's man]
[to strangle me to death
while I'm unconscious.]
[And they would make it
look like a suicide.]
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
I hurt you.
[I switched our bowls and chopsticks]
[and pretended to be unconscious.]
I'm sorry, Your Highness.
[When she went out
to call her accomplice,]
[the drug kicked in,]
[and she fainted on the way.]
[Chief Wu always makes things difficult
and humiliates us.]
[That day, when he passed by
with other chamberlains,]
[he took Yingxin away]
[and abused her.]
[Yingxin became crazy since then.]
I only wanted to let her pay the piper.
It's all because of her petty kindness.
She wouldn't have to suffer all of this
if she didn't drug the meals
but poisoned them.
[Yue Yingxin was evil.]
[But he treated her like a stranger]
[with no mercy at all.]
[Is the Devil God really heartless?]
[Is there no remedy?]
Tantai Jin.
I really regret saving you.
Ye Xiwu.
Back then, I thought
it was my fault.
But now I understand
it's not me who is at fault,
but the world!
So, for those who abused me
or wanted to kill me,
I will not let go of them!
Including you.
[I can't just sit and wait.]
General Ye!
It was your daughter
who was shameless
and consorted with the Prince of the Jing.
For your sake,
I agreed to let her marry Tantai Jin.
I let him leave the palace and
live with your family.
It's been less than a year!
And you are telling me that he ran away?
Your Majesty, please punish me.
Punish you?
General Ye,
you fought dauntlessly
on the battlefield
and hold Tantai Jin hostage here.
Now you want to release him.
How dare I say anything?
Your Majesty, I know you are angry.
Tantai Jin has fled.
And I didn't take precautions.
I am guilty of negligence in guarding him.
But I have never collaborated
with the Jing
or released him on purpose.
Your Majesty, please look into it.
Of course, I will.
It's such a big incident.
Look.
So many civil and military ministers
have written memorials
about what you have done!
I'm guilty!
Well.
Go to the jail
of three interdependent judicial departments.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty.
My father is old.
His body has old wounds
from fighting for our country.
He can't bear the suffering in prison.
Your Majesty, if you want to punish him,
please let me go for my father.
Wait, Junior General Ye.
I will sympathize
with the meritorious officials.
The prison there
is the cleanest and the most spacious.
If you don't want your father to suffer,
bring back the hostage prince
as soon as possible!
It will clear your family of suspicion.
And I can explain it to my officials.
Listen!
If you can't capture him alive,
bring back his body!
Don't let Tantai Jin
return to the Jing alive!
We would rather kill all just for one!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your mercy.
What a fishy smell!
What's in it?
Your Highness.
The priestess has been asking us
to hunt demons for you.
We just got this demonic elixir.
Please enjoy it.
His Highness asked me to bring you a meal.
How do I know
whether you poisoned the food or not?
His Highness is frank and forthright.
How could he poison you?
Yeah, he is really frank and forthright!
Why are you staring at me?
I have to watch you eat.
His Highness ordered me to.
Dude.
My hands are tied! How can I eat?
Okay, I'll eat.
You!
I told you I am not capable of holding it.
I'm sorry, dude.
[I need to find a way to get the boat.]
Something's wrong.
Moonshadow Guards, assemble for orders.
Hurry!
Gather for orders!
The female prisoner
in the water dungeon has escaped.
Isn't she tied with a Ruo-River rope?
How can she untie it without the spell?
What do you want from me?
This spell can untie the Ruo-River rope.
As for whether you can escape or not,
it depends on your ability.
Why are you helping me?
Consider it as a favor for myself.
[What is Jing Lan'an up to?]
[I can't let them find me.]
Your Highness.
I heard you had a demonic elixir.
I'm here to check on you.
Your Highness, you're sweating a lot.
Do you feel uncomfortable?
I'm fine.
You're just in time.
I want to give you a gift.
Your Highness. This is too precious.
The steps are full of tawny daylily.
I've heard that people use this flower
as a metaphor for mothers.
I lost my mother when I was young.
And I have no one to give this hairpin to.
How about
you have it?
Here.
Lan'an.
You did your best to bring me up,
and made plans for me.
I will remember all of this.
I wonder if my elder brother
will be surprised
[Memorial Tablet of Holy
Emperor of the Great Jing]
when he sees me.
Congratulations, Your Highness.
Tantai Minghan and his party
were bound by our spell
before they could leave the palace.
They were all beheaded.
Well done.
Your Highness, it's my honor
that you appreciate me.
Now, my third brother
is the only family I have left.
I miss him a bit, though.
Your Highness,
I brought some cooks from the Yiyue tribe.
They cooked some of our hometown dishes.
I wonder if Your Highness likes it.
Thank you.
I haven't been back for many years.
What's going on in the Jing now?
Emperor Jing just passed away.
The new Emperor is Tantai Minglang.
There's one more thing.
I want to know what your opinion is.
Although Ye Xiwu is vulgar,
after all, she is your wife.
In the future,
when you return to the Jing…
She is not my wife.
Your Highness,
I not only brought cooks
from the Yiyue tribe,
but I also brought the beauties with me.
They can all sing and dance well.
Your Highness, you may enjoy it.
Just kill time.
Sure.
So beautiful.
What do you think of this?
Ziling.
Your younger brother is the head
of the Moonshadow Guards.
Did he tell you
what His Highness looks like?
-Tell us.
-Yes, tell us.
Please tell us.
Baiyu is a dummy.
He only cares about his duties.
He wouldn't tell me that.
But it doesn't matter
what His Highness looks like.
I just want to know what girls he likes!
Isn't that right, girls?
-Yeah!
Well.
-Keep searching!
-What kind of girls does he like?
We can find her.
What are you guys doing here?
Miss Nian. We're looking for someone.
I wonder if you've seen
a young lady before.
Young?
We're all young.
We're young ladies.
Well, can we go in and search?
Alright, I won't make it hard for you.
Aunt Lan'an asks you all to perform.
Finally!
I'm sorry.
Girls, let's go.
Let's go.
[Perform?]
[Dance?]
[I don't know how to dance!]
[I can play this.]
[Oh no.]
[The harp humans use]
[is so different from Chongyu Harp.]
[Even the strings are loose.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
[How did she escape?]
Your Highness.
It's my fault.
Ye Xiwu has escaped.
Is that so?
I've ordered someone
to guard the dinghy closely.
Patrol of the Moonshadow Guards
did not see anyone jumping into the river.
Ye Xiwu must be on the boat.
Your Highness, please give the order
to search cabin by cabin.
No need.
Let's listen to the song first.
She can't escape.
[Ye Xiwu.]
[I'll see how long you can hold out.]
[Why are they still dancing?]
[If I keep playing,
I'm going to get caught.]
[Finally, I managed to muddle through.]
Your Highness, do you like the dance?
It's nice.
How about another solo dance?
Let that dancer dance.
Who is it? Who?
Who would dance before His Highness?
Who is it?
Yes.
The one with the harp.
I made a fortune telling for them.
Guess what?
Water will bring them luck.
It's threatening but not dangerous.
It's highly auspicious!
Highly auspicious?
Don't worry about it.
Maybe Miss Xiwu
was taken to the Jing Kingdom
to be their queen and enjoy her happiness!
If she becomes a queen
in a hostile country,
I'm afraid our family will be
in even more danger in court.
Why did His Highness choose her to dance?
-Why?
-Don't know.
Why her?
[Tantai Jin!]
[How dare you play me like this?]
What?
You can play the harp but can't dance?
[I can't just sit and wait.]
[I must find a way to get out of here.]
[Tantai Jin.]
[You asked for it.]
[Don't regret it!]
Your Highness.
Stay back.
Come with me.
Don't move, or I'll strangle him to death.
Miss Ye.
What the hell do you want?
Stop the boat!
Let us go to the dinghy.
When we get to the shore safely,
I'll let him come back here.
Don't know you want to run away so badly.
If you don't want to be strangled,
let me get into the dinghy.
Let's split up there.
Merry meet, merry part. Alright?
You can't get away.
You are overconfident!
Ye Xiwu.
I guess you have not seen
how a beast hunts its prey, right?
Some beasts do not kill their prey
so easily.
They just
tease and torment the prey
until it takes its last breath.
Unfortunately,
I am not your prey.
Since you asked me to dance,
I'd make you regret your decision.
Let me get in the dinghy!
[Since you want to play,]
[I'll play with you to the end!]
Nian Baiyu!
This cold palace
has few visitors all year round.
Go to the dinghy.
Yes.
Wise decision.
Cut the rope.
Don't you dare!
Cut it!
Yes!
Tell him to stop, or I'll strangle you!
Catch her!
Your Highness.
Do you want her dead or alive?
It doesn't matter.
Yes!
Wait!
I want her alive.
Yes.
Ye Xiwu.
You have no other choice.
Just give up.
Go back to the Jing with me.
I'll never go back with you!
Didn't you say
you would kill me sooner or later?
You…
I am going to kill you.
But even the nonentities want to be alive.
Isn't it good to live in dishonor
for one more day?
Is that so?
Thank you so much, Your Highness.
It's a pity.
I don't want this kind of charity.
She jumped overboard!
She wanted to run away from me so much!
Lan'an.
Is she going to die?
Qi Shuang.
Yes.
Bring someone to look for Miss Ye.
Find her,
dead or alive.
Yes.
Father, I heard
you ordered General Ye Qingyu
to capture Tantai Jin.
I wonder…
if you can let me do it instead.
Why?
Forgive me for speaking frankly.
Tantai Jin has escaped back to his domain.
It is difficult to stop him.
But there are many powerful forces
along both sides of the river.
It's a complicated place.
It is difficult for us
to collect taxes there every year.
If the Dragon Guards
can inspect the states and counties
in the name of hunting the hostage prince
and check their repositories
at the same time,
we can punish someone
as a warning to others.
So, we can solve a big problem
for the Sheng.
My son is really smart.
You tried so hard.
You've thought out such a good idea
for the Ye family,
to let them atone for their faults.
The Ye family was negligent.
They are indeed guilty.
But the two generals
are both talented and useful
for our country.
With the Ye family helping us,
Jia Pass will be safe,
and the Sheng will be safe!
What's more,
I've heard
Tantai Minglang is cruel and sinister.
Even if we can't get Tantai Jin back,
he has to fight with his brother
after he returns.
For the Sheng,
it's not a bad thing.
That's what you wanted to tell me today,
am I right?
What?
You've learned to say things
you don't mean before me now.
I'm terrified.
Alright.
The Ye family is useful to us.
A stumble may prevent a fall.
I'll give this favor
to the Ye family for you.
Check the repositories while you're there.
I will reward you.
Leave us.
Yes.
Tantai Jin has been a hostage
in Sheng for many years.
His mother is of a different race.
So, he has no foundation
in the court at all.
He's nothing.
May I make bold to ask
why you always take him as an eyesore?
Because someone has been
thinking about him all the time.
[Memorial Tablet of Holy
Emperor of the Great Jing]
[You are the eldest lineal son]
and my most capable son.
The Jing is in your hands now.
Father, you entrust me with this.
I'm really grateful.
Now,
I only have one unfulfilled wish left.
Minglang.
Would you please fulfill my wish?
Of course, I will.
Your wish is the will of God.
Please tell me.
[I want to bring Tantai Jin back
to the Jing as soon as possible.]
[In this world…]
[only his eyes look like Concubine Rou's.]
[I really want to see these eyes again.]
Then I can rest in peace.
Is Concubine Rou the only regret
you have in your life?
Have you forgotten why my mother died?
[It was the first year after the witch
who could talk to animals]
[entered the palace.]
[During the autumn hunt,]
you were attacked by a beast.
My mother died
to save your life.
Everyone said it was the witch
who manipulated the beast
to kill my mother.
But you are so partial and protective!
Don't bring up the old story again!
It was only an accident.
[There's a sharp question I've always]
[wanted to ask you.]
If Concubine Rou
hadn't had a difficult delivery
and Tantai Jin had been born safely,
would you still entrust me
with the kingdom today?
The Jing kingdom
will soon be mine.
A man dies the way a lamp goes out.
This is just your guess.
That's right.
A man dies
the way a lamp goes out.
Tantai Jin.
Your Highness.
Why is the boat slowing down?
I think we are approaching
the confluence with the Mohe River.
The Mohe River is muddy and turbulent.
Every year, it breaks the dike.
It's an unlucky river.
That's why the boat slows down
when passing it through.
Oh.
I'm coming to tell Your Highness
Qi Shuang has sent a message back.
They have been searching the shore
all night.
Finally, they found Miss Xiwu.
I didn't dare to delay.
So I asked them to wait for us
at the ferry in the front.
How is she?
Her life is not in danger.
She choked on a lot of water.
I've said it. She wouldn't get away.
Well done.
Let her take a rest.
Take off the hood.
Yes.
Your Highness!
Protect His Highness.
Your Highness.
Your Highness!
Are you okay, Your Highness?
You took a poisonous demonic elixir,
and were blinded by a poisoned needle.
How do you feel now?
Qi Shuang!
Why are you rebelling against our tribe?
Your Highness, let's retreat now.
[D*mn.]
Nian Baiyu.
There are more enemies besides these guys.
We don't have much time. Take the board.
Yes.
Stop!
High Priestess.
Tell them to surrender.
Or I will kill Tantai Jin right now!
Everyone, put down your weapons!
Excellent! Excellent indeed!
The High Priestess of the Yiyue tribe.
You're very resourceful.
Somehow, you found a way
to trick this idiot into docking.
It was a bloodless victory.
You've made a great achievement!
Your Highness, you're wise.
Your daughter has been set up for life.
Her illness is almost cured.
You've done such a wonderful job.
I'll send Fuya back to you when we return.
Thank you, Your Highness.
My third brother.
We meet again after so many years.
You do have the same eyes
as that witch.
What a pity.
One is blinded.
Do you know?
When our old father died,
he said he wanted to see these eyes again.
How about I grant him his wish today?
I'll dig out your eyes
and put them
in front of his memorial tablet.
What do you think?
You haven't changed since you were young.
You don't like to talk,
but you like to bark like a dog.
Say!
Say something!
Tantai Minglang.
Why are you wasting time
recalling past events?
I trusted the wrong person
and fell for your trap.
I admit my loss.
Oh, my third brother.
I'm not cruel by nature.
Even if you want to die soon,
it depends on me
to give you this grace.
Someone!
Bring the gift.
Do you know how I got these scars
on my body?
The question sounds meaningless.
Apparently, it doesn't.
It's all thanks to you!
Me?
When I was six,
Concubine Rou called wild beasts
to kill my mother during the autumn hunt.
[Even though everyone knew no one else ]
[Memorial Tablet of Holy Empress of the Jing]
[but Concubine Rou did it.]
[But Father was partial to her]
[and defended her.]
[He totally disregarded]
[my mother's devotion and sacrifice.]
Shut up!
[Stop discussing this matter further.]
[I have my own decision.]
[My mother just passed away.]
[But Concubine Rou was pregnant.]
[Everyone in the palace said]
[if she gave birth to a prince,]
[she would definitely be the new queen.]
[Her son]
[would become
the future emperor of the Jing.]
If Concubine Rou gave birth to a prince…
[The servants who served me]
[became more and more slack
because of this.]
[One day in winter,]
[a pot with no cover appeared]
[in my chamber.]
What happened?
Something's wrong.
[I fell into the charcoal fire.]
[My life was at stake.]
His Hignness…
[My father, however, is coaxing
Concubine Rou to take a nap.]
[And he came very late.]
[I didn't know
how long I had been waiting.]
[He finally came.]
[But he didn't even check on me.]
[I only heard him say one sentence
outside the room.]
Minglang has hurt his face
and looks ominous now.
I'm afraid it will be difficult for him
to inherit the throne.
This is your and Concubine Rou's fault.
You must pay for it!
Try the coals' heat!
Your Highness!
I promised to help you kill Tantai Jin.
But I didn't promise you
I'd watch you torture him.
Shut up!
See where you stand!
I know your story now.
But your pain has nothing to do with me.
If you want revenge,
you should go to Tantai Wuji!
I don't owe you anything.
You do!
It's all your fault!
I'll make you suffer
a thousand times more!
I will torture you
until no one can recognize you.
I want you to get down on your knees
and beg me to kill you!
Today,
I can't escape.
But there is one thing
I want to know.
Fine.
I will give you a chance
and let you die after you get the answers.
Auntie.
Why did you betray me?
I shouldn't have betrayed you.
It's my fault.
But…
I have Fuya now.
She is my daughter.
It's just for your daughter.
You were not such a weak person.
Right.
I was not like this before.
But once I love someone,
I have a bond.
I'm no longer indestructible.
A few years ago, Fuya got lost.
Prince Minglang helped me find her.
I want to be loyal to you,
but I can't lose my daughter.
Before,
I had no children.
I treated you as if you were my son.
But these years, God took pity on me
and let me have a daughter.
You are gloomy and hard to understand.
But my daughter is pure and beautiful.
If I had to choose one person to save,
it's not you. I think
everyone would make the same choice.
Is that so?
What about the relationship between us?
Can you bear to…
Your Highness!
I already know the reason
why Yingxin went crazy.
I don't believe
you did it because of this traitor.
That's just another reason.
It made me understand
you are a cold fish,
heartless and ungrateful.
She tried to kill me.
Yingxin and I brought you up.
But for you,
our betrayal
is no different than anyone else's!
We're not special.
That's the worst part.
You take advantage of people
who are good to you without burden.
For those who treat you badly,
you can just kill them with no mercy.
How can you do that!
What's wrong with that?
But this is inhuman!
I didn't expect I could use Ye Xiwu
to set you up this time.
It was you who let Ye Xiwu go.
It was you
who untied the Ruo-River rope for her.
And then, you lied that you found her
to make the ship dock.
If you didn't go that way,
and if they boarded the boat by force,
there would be more casualties.
You see?
Once you fall for someone,
you're not indestructible anymore.
You are wrong.
For me, Ye Xiwu
isn't special at all.
Finally,
you have feelings for someone.
But I used her
to kill you.
How ironic it is!
Auntie, let me ask you.
Do you regret betraying me?
My child,
I don't regret it.
Back then, in the cold palace of the Jing,
I saved your life
with the blood from my fingertips.
[What goes around comes around.]
Today I will choose for you.
OK.
Great!
Tantai Minglang.
Do it.
[There's something I want you to have.]
[I've heard]
[people use this flower
as a metaphor for mothers.]
[How about]
[you have it?]
Once the poison in your left eye
spreads throughout your meridians,
you'll spit blood three times and die.
There's no need to struggle.
This poison is so powerful.
Thanks for reminding me.
You're crazy!
How can you cut your wrist
to release poisoned blood?
I'm not crazy.
I'm just curious.
Will I die of poison
or die of excessive bleeding?
You're still resisting
at the end of your life!
How pathetic!
Tantai Minglang.
Remember what you've done today.
From now on,
you will never sleep in peace again.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪