♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 2]
Rest well, Miss Xiwu.
I'll be next door…
if you need me.
[Father,]
[I'm pretty much settled here.]
[Hope it puts your mind at ease.]
[As for the Devil God…]
[I have found him.]
[But…]
[I can't kill him to stop the Devil God…]
[from manifesting. Not just yet.]
[The good thing is,]
[he's still a weak mortal.]
♪A path longer than time♪
[Anyway, I made him kneel in the snow.]
[That'll be enough
for the punishment, for now.]
♪Not knowing where to start♪
♪Might as well follow my gut♪
♪I saw a village
outside a window in my dream♪
[The wind is picking up.]
[Oh,]
[it's going to be a long night.]
♪Leaves change color♪
[It's really windy out there.]
[Is he going to be okay?]
♪I see God with my eyes closed
as the autumn leaves fall on me♪
[Father, Uncle Zhaoyou, Jiwu,]
[I'm not doing anything wrong, am I?]
♪Leaves and flowers are falling off♪
♪Now I know what my dream means♪
♪Wandering from place to place,
not knowing where I belong♪
♪I have no place to call home♪
♪Nothing lasts forever♪
[Huh, he's actually still on his knees.]
♪I can't ask for more♪
♪Just an ordinary life♪
♪And compose an ordinary song♪
[Ah, I fell asleep.]
Miss Xiwu, you're awake.
The wind was howling so loud last night.
Did you sleep well?
What is Mr. Tantai still doing here?
This is, what,
his third day?
Tough guy, that one.
Yeah, that's what he gets…
for messing with Miss Xiwu.
♪Just an ordinary life♪
♪And compose an ordinary song♪
[I'm pretty sure he's faking it.]
[He's unpopular here.]
[If he didn't play the victim,]
[his life here would only be much harder.]
Thank you so much, Miss Ye.
Miss Ye has the kindest soul.
On every first
and fifteenth day of the month,
she would come here,
giving out porridge to people in need.
And she's been doing this for years
as if nothing would stop her.
-Hold that.
-I'll go to the temple tomorrow to pray.
-Hope she and Prince Lin get married soon.
-Here you are.
Not a problem.
God willing, they'll start a big family.
You're welcome.
Miss Bingchang,
Prince Lin sent Zhong Tai
to drop off a letter last night.
-Said he had a day off today and would come.
-You're welcome.
-His Highness should be here any minute.
-Careful.
-Give me the spoon.
-Thank you.
Go spruce yourself up a bit.
That won't be necessary.
-By the way,
-Here you go.
Thank you, Miss Ye.
Zhong Tai said
they went for military training yesterday.
-They ran into Miss Xiwu in the suburbs.
-Here.
Turns out that crazy woman is still
refusing to leave Prince Lin alone.
Mind your language.
You're welcome.
Xiwu is a married woman.
The fiasco is only going to
further tarnish
her reputation in the capital.
All this gossip…
make sure it doesn't reach
the ears of Grandmother and Father.
Miss Bingchang,
-that's not yours to worry about.
-Not at all.
-She pushed you into a lake the other day,
-No worries.
which gave you a cold.
Yet she got away unpunished.
Do not speak of it again.
-Here you go.
-Thank you, Miss Ye.
Don't mention it.
Would you clean this up?
Prince Lin is here.
I should get going.
Bingchang.
Don't go just yet.
I've waited so long to see you.
The sun is setting.
I'm going to get nagged
if I get home late.
Pardon my discourtesy, Your Highness.
I've been on a boot camp
just outside the capital.
About half of the rules
in the Sheng military
were made by your father, General Ye.
I thought I could spend more time with you
when I came back here.
Didn't think there would still be
the Ye family rules
that I needed to follow.
Oh, Your Highness,
there are indeed strict rules
we Ye family have to follow.
And I've been living with those
since childhood. I'm used to it.
Well, apparently,
they aren't strict enough
to keep Miss Xiwu under control.
She even made
the hostage prince of the Jing Kingdom
kneel in the snow.
Tantai Jin was made to kneel in the snow?
Well, as the word
"hostage prince" suggests,
he is a prince of the Jing Kingdom.
How could Ye Xiwu do that to him?
Let it go, Your Highness.
Ye Xiwu is not a rational person.
Anyway, you haven't fully recovered
from the fall.
You should go home and get some rest.
Right.
I'll take my leave now.
It's been four days
since your vicious wife
forced you to kneel here.
You would die like this.
Don't you get it?
She wants you to be dead, intentionally!
Miss Xiwu.
Xiwu.
I know what happened earlier by the lake
was unintentional.
Oh, it was intentional.
Look at you.
All dressed up for Prince Lin's visit,
only to end up being soaked through.
What a shame for you.
How does it feel, hmm?
Xiwu,
why are you doing this to me?
I've done nothing to hurt you.
Please. Say that to Prince Lin.
You know,
I'm definitely curious about
what you've done to him
to make him go crazy over you.
He hardly ever looks at me.
Let's not forget Jin,
my unfaithful husband.
He, too, has fallen prey to your charm.
Since he loves
being the center of attention,
well, wish granted.
And if he do die in the process,
all there is to do is fill Grandmother in.
Know what?
I'm just going to level with you.
Jin is in his last days of life.
There's nothing you can do to change that.
And with the two of you gone,
I'm sure Prince Lin will like me.
Oh, what a heartless, wicked woman.
Someone's coming.
Hmm.
Why there are crows
flying around the house all the time?
This is a bad omen.
This has always been the case
since Mr. Tantai's arrival.
[The sun has set again.]
[It's the dead of winter.]
[If he stays out there much longer,]
[he may not live to see tomorrow.]
[As much as he deserves it,]
[I can't risk
having the evil bone come back.]
[Or there'll be hell to pay.]
Ah, Mr. Tantai,
I'm terribly sorry.
I didn't see you there.
Yeah,
we didn't mean to get your clothes wet.
Come on, let's go.
[It's freezing cold out there.]
[He is just a mortal man.]
[And with his clothes wet through,]
[he's not going to make it.]
It's cold out here,
Xiwu.
Go back inside.
No need for you
to come and watch me suffer.
Well, I didn't come here for that.
I just…
Just what?
I just wanted to check if you were dead.
I would hate to collect your corpse.
I am so sure
you don't need to do it yourself,
even if I die.
Many in this world want me dead.
Probably more than I care to admit.
They might even flood in here
to congratulate you on my death.
You don't actually think
those words are going to
make me go soft on you, do you?
Go soft on me?
[Goodness,]
[he's in bad shape.]
[He's not going to make it
if this doesn’t stop.]
[Screw it.]
[You are not going to
get away like this.]
Boy, this cloak is ugly.
I'm not wearing it.
You can have it.
I couldn't, possibly.
It's yours.
But if you don't like it,
You may have Chuntao
get rid of it tomorrow.
You…
Will there be anything else?
[See, Li Susu?]
[He is not a creature
made of flesh and bone.]
[You expressed sympathy for him.]
[Yet he was sarcastically
mean to you in return.]
[He doesn't deserve your kindness.]
[Not while he's still breathing.]
[So save the empathy,]
[and do something meaningful.]
[Patience is the key to success.]
[No doubt Jin is worthy of death,]
[but he is the key to the future of]
[the Four Continents and Three Realms.]
Jin, hey.
Drop the act.
It's not going to
make me feel bad for you.
[Why do I feel like
I've been here and done this before?]
[Is this where he died]
[and morphed into a demon?]
Jin! Jin!
Wake up!
Chuntao!
Miss Xiwu,
are you asking for me?
I am, yes! Come in, quick!
Miss Xiwu,
is this a dream?
Or are you not right in the head?
What are you talking about?
Go boil some water! Quick!
He's dying!
Go!
Miss Xiwu,
why were you
and Mr. Tantai clinging together?
Well, we are a married couple.
Isn't that what
human husbands and wives do?
Sleeping together in the same bed?
Human?
Go check the water temperature.
Absolutely.
It's comfortably warm, Miss Xiwu.
All right, Chuntao, you're dismissed.
Yes, Miss Xiwu.
[Did Xiwu do all this to him?]
[If I had known he was this fragile,]
[I wouldn't have put the future of]
[the Four Continents
and Three Realms at stake]
[just to get even with him.]
[Come on, Jin.]
[Please. You're a Devil God.]
[Don't die. Think about
the Four Continents and Three Realms.]
Tantai Jin, you poor, poor man.
It's you again.
You're always there
whenever death comes knocking.
I never left.
I know.
You're inside of me.
Do you want it?
Not yet. Now is not the time.
Then when is it?
Why? You've run out of patience?
But I don't blame you.
For the past 20 years and more,
this body has done nothing
but make you feel pain,
hungry, cold, and humiliated.
And made you helpless.
One of these days,
you'll be free from the flesh.
And you will offer me your soul
and find eternal peace.
It doesn't matter.
My body,
and my soul,
you can have both
if you like.
I couldn't care less.
You have to be
a bit more patient, Tantai Jin.
You're going to
go through all hardships of mortal life.
And be drowned in endless bitterness.
You'll walk a dark and cursed path.
There's no escaping the pain.
And when you’re in your hardest time
and approach the end of life,
I will come for you
and accept your offerings.
[The moon 500 years ago]
[shone so much brighter.]
[Such a shame that
the Devil God has descended,]
[throwing a blanket of
foul fog over the Earth.]
[I haven't seen the moon
for… God knows how long.]
[Born from an evil origin,
with an evil bone in him.]
[Where is that bone located?]
[How does it look like?]
[I wonder which of these is the evil one.]
[Hmm, they all feel pretty normal to me.]
What are you doing?
You're awake.
Xiwu,
what game are you playing this time?
It doesn't concern you.
Now that you're up,
don't soak in there pretending to be dead.
Go get dressed at once.
Where are you going?
To the lake.
It's still dark outside.
No, don't go.
Stop right there.
You're not going to the lake.
Not today, not tomorrow, not ever.
Why?
You're my husband.
You were kneeling out there
with many people passing by.
It's only going to embarrass me.
Well, I'm sorry.
I'm tired. I'm going to get some sleep.
Don't talk to me.
[Father,]
[I guess you didn't expect
I would be sleeping with the Devil God]
[when you sent me here.]
Why are you standing over there?
Do it.
I want to get it over with
and then go to bed.
Do what?
Things that you do to me
every night, of course.
Have you forgotten?
[Shoot.]
[He can't find out who I really am.]
Oh please.
How could I forget?
Hang on. I'm a little parched.
Chuntao,
get me some tea.
Chuntao, help me remember.
What exactly is the thing
Jin and I do every night?
You beat him.
You have become rather moody
after marrying him.
And you whip him every night before bed
as an outlet for your anger.
What is she, a psychopath?
Where's the whip?
Under your mattress, Miss Xiwu.
[And how many times?]
[Well,]
[I guess it depends on your mood.]
[This is a long whip.]
[Geez, Xiwu does have a twisted mind.]
[Li Susu,]
[you can do this, right?]
[You used to slay demons
without even blinking an eye.]
[This is for that Devil God]
[you'll be turning into in 500 years.]
[Oh, Devil God,]
[you deserve this.]
[Li Susu,]
[what are you doing?]
[He is not yet a Devil God.]
[All these beatings and insults,]
[all the bullying and the torture,]
[that can't stop
the Devil God from coming to Earth.]
[What it really does is]
[making you feel worse.]
I'm tired.
I'm going to call it a night…
and off to bed.
Jin.
Jin?
Jin!
[He's burning up.]
[Oh dear.]
[He knelt in the snow for days,]
[and he was beaten up.]
[All too much for a mortal like him.]
[Li Susu, oh, Li Susu,]
[what have you done?]
Chuntao!
Are you awake?
Miss Xiwu,
the potion is ready.
Anything else before I go?
No, that's it.
I mean it this time, Chuntao.
Go back to bed.
Jin.
Here, drink this.
[He's fuzzy with a fever.]
[And I'm not even sure
if these herbs from Earth work.]
Open your mouth.
His temperature isn't going down.
[Father would place
a cool washcloth on my forehead]
[every time I had a fever as a kid.]
You're finally awake.
I knew this would work.
All right now,
you get some rest.
I'm going to go to bed.
Seriously, what did I do to deserve this?
[She's a different person ever since
she comes back from the temple.]
[Is she got possessed]
[by some evil spirit or something?]
[Ye's Mansion]
Miss Xiwu,
you should have slept in a bit.
You stayed up late last night.
Where's Jin?
Apart from getting corporal punishment,
a typical day in his life also involves
copying sutras in the Librarium.
He's probably been there
since this morning.
[Jin,]
[you owe me a life debt
that you can't get out of.]
[Someday, you'll pay with your life.]
[Bear that in mind.]
What time is it?
Almost noon.
Mrs. Ye, Mr. Ye, and Mr. Zeyu,
they're waiting in the dining room.
Miss Xiwu.
[So these are Xiwu's family,]
[who she sees every day.]
[If I want to stay here,]
[I'll need to get through this first.]
[This must be Xiwu's father,]
[the Sheng's
Pillar of the State Great General.]
[And this must be Zeyu,]
[Xiwu's eldest brother.]
[As for these women,]
[They may be concubines of Xiwu's father.]
[This old lady
dressed in strikingly luxurious clothes,]
[she's got to be Xiwu's grandmother.]
Grandmother.
What's with you, Xiwu?
Don't look at Chuntao.
Unless you want her to be punished too.
[Geez.]
[Xiwu is such a trouble magnet.]
[What she had done this time?]
Come here.
[Oh gosh, please
don't cane me on my palm.]
What in God's name are you thinking,
walking around
without a windbreaker
in the dead of winter?
Look at her.
She’s hardly wearing anything.
Oh, my poor darling.
You are surrounded
by a bunch of incompetent people.
At the end of the day,
family is all you have.
Here.
Wear this. It'll keep you warm.
[Whew, I thought
I was going to get punished.]
Now this is so much better.
Chuntao,
fetch some pelts from the storage room.
Xiwu could use a couple more coats.
Certainly.
Grandmother,
I'd love a white fox fur coat, too.
Oh,
ask your father for it.
Father, can I have
a white fox fur coat made?
In your dreams.
Have you no shame,
Zeyu?
As my eldest son,
you are supposed to train to fight.
Guard the borders
and contribute to the country
as your younger brother does.
Instead, you mess about with your gang.
Wasting your time on having fun.
Look at you.
No decent girl
in the capital would fall for you.
[That's harsh.]
The food's getting cold.
Let's just eat.
Buttercup,
go sit by your father.
Go.
All right.
Easy.
Father.
Xiwu, honey,
try this.
I know you haven't been
in a good mood lately.
I specifically ordered the kitchen staff
to make your favorite dishes.
I have been told by the helpers that
you were up all night last night,
steeping in a hot bath and brewing potion.
You must be tired
after a sleepless night.
You must eat more to fuel up.
Right, here you go.
Here, have some more.
You need more protein in your diet.
Eat this.
Don't take that personally.
[So…]
And this, too.
[this is family love,
as described in the book.]
These dishes were made especially for you.
They're all your favorite foods.
[Father,]
[these people are good to me.]
The tofu soup is amazing.
[The same as you are.]
I understand from
the Marchioness of Order yesterday that
everyone in the capital is talking about
how Xiwu pushed Bingchang into the water.
The news spread far and wide.
People can talk all they want about Xiwu.
Words can't hurt.
It'll harm her reputation.
What's done cannot be undone.
Plus, Xiwu's already married.
But Father,
before Xiwu got married last year,
you said she should be
allowed some harmless fun.
And that she would have to
take responsibility for her behavior
after marriage.
And now this.
How is she always right?
Keep quiet.
Eat your food.
[Xiwu, oh, Xiwu,]
[now I know why]
[you are such a spoiled brat.]
Actually, I've given it a lot of thought.
I shouldn't have pushed
Bingchang into the lake.
It's my fault.
I’d like to pay her a visit today
and ask for her forgiveness.
Mother,
are you hearing this?
Oh, isn't Xiwu thoughtful?
[He calls this thoughtful?]
Well…
Xiwu's always been kind and dependable.
Absolutely worthy
of being called my granddaughter.
[These people really spoil her rotten.]
You can skip the niceties, though.
What if Bingchang's cold hasn't gone away?
We wouldn't want you
to catch it.
It's okay, Grandmother.
I agree with you, Grandmother.
If Xiwu did make an apology,
then she'd be underestimating
the bond of our sisterhood.
Bingchang.
Sit, Xiwu.
I'm sorry,
Grandmother.
I haven't felt well enough
to greet you and Father
for the past few days.
And I must also
apologize for interrupting the meal.
I didn't think it would take me so long
to get freshened up
after giving out porridge to the needy.
You heard her,
Xiwu.
No apology is needed.
Bingchang,
sit next to Zeyu.
Yes, Grandmother.
[No wonder Gong…]
[I mean,]
[both Prince Lin
and Jin have a thing for her.]
[She's beautiful.]
[She's gentle. And she has a kind soul.]
[Nobody could ever hate her.]
I don't see Jin.
Why isn't he here eating with us?
Do you honestly think
you're one of the employers here?
You eat the food,
yet you don't help with anything.
Yeah, you can't just do nothing all day.
What do you want?
What do I want?
Well,
the boys and I
have spent the afternoon doing chores.
There's a pile of dirty dishes over there,
all used by the family.
I see you laze around all the time.
So do me a favor
and wash those dishes before you eat.
-Is that okay?
-Mm.
That's right.
Thank you, Mr. Tantai.
Go on, Mr. Tantai.
Go.
Thanks a bunch.
Come on, guys.
Time for lunch.
Come on over. It's lunchtime.
Yeah, coming.
Get me a bowl of rice.
Hey, pass the pot over here.
Nope, I'll help myself.
Here you go.
Yeah, all right.
Ugh.
There.
Here you are.
So Jin has never joined us at the table
ever since he came here.
He has his meals
with the helpers in the kitchen.
Mm-hmm.
You hate his guts.
Having him around ruins your appetite.
And from what I hear,
He isn't getting enough food.
The helpers in the kitchen
take their cue from you.
They watch what you do,
and they imitate.
[Well, severs him right.]
[He's a devil after all.]
[But he's been
keeping his distance from me.]
[I can hardly keep an eye on him.]
Where is the kitchen?
Let me tell you something.
Some people…
may seem to be in a higher social class.
But deep down, they are inferior.
That's so true.
It's… what do you call it again?
A broken-down noble.
Even we are living
better lives than he is,
aren't we?
That's right.
Guys, let's dig in.
Yeah, come on.
Go on, eat your food.
This smells so good.
Mmm, yum.
I'm not going to lie.
His life is absolutely pathetic.
He may as well take his own life
and free himself from all these miseries.
[So Xiwu has been encouraging]
[the helpers]
[to treat Jin like a doormat, huh?]
I couldn't agree more.
He should just end his miserable life.
Go.
Yum.
There's a fly buzzing around.
Where did it come from? It's winter.
What's wrong?
Are you okay?
Have some water.
Are you all right?
Is everything okay?
I just swallowed that fly.
I can't eat anymore.
You guys go on without me.
I'm leaving too.
-You guys just eat.
-Let's continue the meal.
Come sit right here.
Done for the day.
Guess this isn't my lucky day.
Come on.
Miss Xiwu.
-Miss Xiwu.
-What brings you here?
Um, Mr. Tantai is…
Tell me. What did Jin have to do
to be told to kill himself?
Uh, Miss Xiwu,
I put Mr. Tantai on dish duty.
In the bucket were chunks of ice
that we collected
from the frozen lake last night.
Oh, by the way,
I spilled icy cold water
on him while I was at it.
Too bad he survived the freezing cold.
I'll make sure
his hands are in the ice water
long enough to lose his fingers.
And we didn't save him any food today.
Only a bucket of swill.
So this is how poorly
you people have been treating him?
Human beings are all equal.
But some prefer to stoop low
and be stuck in service.
And to feel good about themselves,
they walk all over people
who are weaker than them.
Do you seriously take pleasure
in watching people struggle?
Miss Xiwu, you're
taking this a little bit too seriously.
We were just trying to avenge you on him.
You have our absolute loyalty.
You've been utterly rude to Jin
because you know he's alone and unaided.
If the Ye Family
were no longer prosperous one day,
you would do the same to my family and me,
wouldn't you?
Oh, no, no.
Absolutely not, Miss Xiwu.
I'm sorry, Miss Xiwu.
Please forgive us.
Please forgive me, Miss Xiwu.
-We're terribly sorry.
-Please forgive us.
Forgive us, Miss Xiwu.
Do not eat that.
Well…
One would be dead without any food.
It's awfully dirty.
Only God knows
what those helpers have added to it.
It'll make you sick.
I've eaten far worse.
Why didn't you defend yourself
when they said those things to you?
Why would you, a prince of a kingdom,
let people push you around?
Don't you have any dignity?
Dignity?
It means nothing to me.
For me, personally,
this bowl of rice matters more.
Xiwu!
Come with me.
I cannot survive without food.
But if I had had dignity,
I would have died long ago.
Shut it. You're coming with me.
Eat this.
And I'll let you go.
You're too skinny and physically weak.
Even flu can kill you.
Now you're pulling
the same trick twice.
I'd be a fool to trust you again.
Now, if you'll excuse me.
Sit down.
What trick?
Make yourself clear.
You asked if I had dignity.
The truth is,
I don’t think you
have such a thing, either.
You want me to repeat myself?
Fine.
I'll say it again.
I'm listening.
Your sister Bingchang
met up with Prince Lin
at the royal feast six months ago.
They were roaming around
the garden hand in hand.
And you,
you were desperate to break them up
so you could have Prince Lin your man.
You got this tranquilizer
called Love Fury.
You were going to drug Bingchang
and Prince Liang,
hoping they would
sleep together under the influence.
[Unexpectedly, Prince Liang cornered me]
Prince Liang.
That was quite a feast.
Even the maids and the eunuchs
can have some exquisite food.
You got nothing to eat tonight, did you?
Lucky for you,
I have a big heart.
Have a pastry.
Thank you, Your Highness.
Oops.
I don't know if you've heard,
but my country and yours are at war.
If anyone reminded
my father of your existence,
he might just have you beheaded
as a sacrifice for gods before a battle.
This might happen, right?
I've just remembered.
You like foods broken into smaller parts.
Small enough?
Mm-hmm.
[Next thing I knew,]
[was my head started spinning.]
[Then you came out of nowhere
and wrapped your arms around me.]
[I ate the drug-laced food
meant for Prince Liang by accident.]
[Oddly enough,]
[the one meant for Bingchang]
[was eaten by you for
all the wrong reasons.]
[Many in the palace
knew about that night.]
[Your father had no choice
but to arrange for us to tie the knot.]
To celebrate the love between
the Pillar of the State Great General's daughter,
Ye Xiwu, and the third Prince
of Jing Kingdom, Tantai Jin,
a marriage has been bestowed upon them.
Then one day, you told me the whole story.
Since that point in time…
you've been mocking
and torturing me just for fun.
And you've become
increasingly twisted and cruel.
[Geez, Xiwu.]
[You are unbelievable.]
So, Miss Xiwu,
what did you do
to my food this time?
Nothing.
Really?
You're doing all this
just to make sure I have enough to eat?
I see nothing wrong with that.
Let me tell you something.
Don't even think about
starving yourself to death.
I won't let that happen.
Now watch me.
You happy now?
From today on, you will
have all of your meals here.
Chuntao will bring food to you.
And you will eat
whatever she puts before you.
Don't you ever eat disgusting,
straight-up nasty food scraps again.
[This rice
does seem like it's safe to eat.]
[What's gotten into her, really?]
Guessing this is the first time
you've had a square meal
here at the Ye's Mansion.
Have you noticed that
that broad's a little too sane these days?
Does she have a loose screw, or what?
Well,
Maybe she's come up with other ways
to play her twisted games.
They have me.
If I die...
let's just say
they can't get away with it.
You are right.
She does behave unpredictably.
You can't stay here much longer.
The problem is,
where else can you go?
Oh, by the way,
I bumped into
a couple of crows from Jing Kingdom.
The Jing Kingdom…
I was born there.
What a coincidence.
Have you ever been to its palace?
It's the worst place in the world.
They told me…
they saw a shaman
performing some sort of ritual.
They smelled a decaying body.
And there were also
uptight ministers pacing the hall.
It must have been
because of the King of Jing.
The man I should have called Father…
is dying.
[I'm stuck in here.]
[Guess I'll just stay out of it all.]
Father,
I have something important to report.
Lin.
Your timing is perfect.
I've just received an urgent message.
Tantai Wuji is at death's door.
Tantai Minglang
will take the throne after him.
Looks like Tantai Jin
has outlived his usefulness.
From what I've been told,
Tantai Minglang is a ruthless man.
He may not even show empathy for his siblings.
We would be giving him
what he wants by killing Tantai Jin.
I knew you were a smart one.
Now, if I spare Tantai Jin,
he's going to be a pain in his brother's ass
for as long as he's alive.
I'm going to summon Tantai Jin over.
I want to sound out his opinion.
If he has ambitions,
I could get him back to Jing first
to muddy the waters.
And then have him killed amid chaos.
But if he is unambitious,
then he's of no use to me.
We will then send
a male of similar age to Jing
to trick Tantai Minglang into thinking
that's his brother.
Sometimes...
honesty isn't always the best policy.
Father…
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I’ve seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far
I travel, come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪