♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 6]
Teach me.
What should I teach you…
The one you used to repel the crows
at Xiao Lin's that day.
Not that one.
That spell is too dangerous.
You're just an amateur,
and if you mess the charm up,
you might blow up the house.
[It's always wise to play safe.]
[Because you are Tantai Jin,]
[I will never teach you spells
that can kill.]
Then what are you going to teach me?
I got one.
Watch this.
[I'll teach you this today.]
OK. That's it.
A charm is finished.
But you need the right incantation
to make it work.
What do you think?
What's this spell for?
This spell is called "Sketch".
When I was little,
I was always clamoring to go out to play.
My father…
An immortal taught me this spell,
so that my spirit
could wander around the world
even when I was stuck in a small room.
Also, every time I scribe the charm,
I get to see different sceneries.
These monastic people are so aimless.
Instead of improving their cultivation,
they choose to waste their time
on such useless things.
That's not true.
The immortals say,
body, heart, and mind
are three different parts.
When the three parts are unified,
the internal elixir is formed.
[Empty thy heart to unite soul and character]
[Calm thy body to silent energy and mood]
[Steady thy mind
then all three merge into one.]
Unite the body, heart, and mind,
and the elixir will be cultivated.
But how to unify them?
Turn your energy into Qi
and your body won't move.
Turn Qi into soul,
and your heart won't move.
Turn your soul empty,
and your mind won't move.
Destroy your desire for romantic love,
and then you can understand
the universe and all lives.
This
is the one and only way of Heartless Way.
♪The vivid and splendid dreams
are but a regret that won't fade it seems♪
♪Rather than wake from this slumber
I'd prefer the dream to last forever♪
♪A bond of marriage
entwined for thousands of years♪
♪I soothe the reckless face♪
♪I'm tired of goodbyes and lingering fondness♪
But I'm way off the mark.
All roads lead to the right way,
and Heartless Way
is just one of them.
♪My emotions ebb and flow like the seasons♪
OK, I will learn it.
♪A fair complexion remains unafraid
of being soaked in tears♪
[But I've looked into it.]
[The Little Devil God doesn't have
an immortal bone.]
[No matter how hard he works,]
[there's no way
he can achieve immortality in this life.]
[But as long as
he doesn't turn to the dark side,]
[staying a mortal
might not be a bad thing for him.]
♪While the fireworks of life
are short-lived and easily enjoyed♪
♪But this time, who will come and go♪
♪While wait and endure this bitter sorrow?♪
Ye Xiwu,
this charm is drawn correctly, right?
But why is it not working?
Well, you can't guarantee to succeed
every time you scribe a charm.
This is your first time.
Getting the pattern right
is impressive enough.
Also, the Sketch charm
will show you the purest
and most beautiful things.
You must clear your mind of all thoughts
when chanting the spell,
especially evil thoughts.
Only by doing that can you make it work.
Take your time.
Don't waste the materials.
Remember, clear your mind.
As the teacher,
you fell asleep right
in front of your student.
Unbelievable.
Wake up!
Make sure I've learned it
before you go to sleep.
Wake up.
Why are you being so unreasonable?
I haven't learned it yet.
This is not the Sketch charm.
I'm showing you a new one.
Are you not satisfied?
Ye Xiwu, what are you doing?
Let go of me.
You can't practice
without taking any breaks.
What do you want?
If you practice all night,
you might tire yourself to death.
Come on.
Ye Xiwu!
-What…
-Be good.
Let's resume the study tomorrow.
Ye Xiwu, let go of me.
Be quiet.
Ye Xiwu.
[Because I have feelings for you, OK?]
[When you have feelings for someone,
you want to keep them alive,]
[and spend time with them.]
[You get anxious when they're not around,]
[and feel happy when you see them.]
The universe manifests in an inch of land.
The soul follows the mind.
Rise!
[Please check it out.]
Trifeet Crow is the royal totem of Jing Kingdom.
Were there any people from Jing
at the wedding that day?
The hostage prince Tantai Jin
was also there.
It's said that Yiyue tribe can
communicate with birds and control them.
This thing…
This kid has been lurking for many years.
He is extremely scheming.
Keeping him alive will sooner or later
lead to disaster.
Your majesty, what's your order?
I want him dead.
Hide the traces well.
I will get it done.
Your Majesty,
Ye Xiao's second son, Ye Qingyu,
is coming back from the border today.
I remember he was smart when he was a kid,
and very orderly when doing anything.
He is a young talent
no less gifted than Xiao Lin.
Yes.
I heard people are lining the streets
to welcome him.
The Great General's hard work
showed great values.
The army is full of his supporters.
And this son of his
is excelling him.
I think this kid's reputation
is even better than his father's.
What's going on?
They both came from the same dad,
but the firstborn is hopeless,
while the second son
is young and promising.
He outshines his father.
No big deal.
Even your ten fingers
are different lengths.
[Ye Mansion]
Who is missing me?
My brother will be back soon, right?
Our house has been in turmoil
since early in the morning.
None of us can get a moment of peace.
I-I can't stand any longer.
I'm exhausted.
I'm still injured.
Mr. Qingyu is home.
Greetings, Mr. Qingyu.
Grandma, Father.
I'm back.
Thanks to God's blessing,
you are home safe and sound.
It was unfilial of me
to leave Grandma and Father for so long.
Please punish me, Father.
Why would I punish you?
You were guarding the country.
Is there anything more honorable than that?
Although you couldn't stay home
to keep us company,
our ancestors would be very proud of you,
and the people of Sheng admire you.
I'm very proud.
Stand up now.
Up.
Here,
let's start eating.
We waited so long for you to come home.
Come on.
Don't bring up "punishment"
the moment you get back.
Why isn't my sister here?
You mean Xiwu?
She was in the attic last night,
busy with something.
Qingyu,
Xiwu has been studying so hard these days,
forgetting food and sleep.
She probably forgot to eat again.
Let's just
send her some food later.
Yes.
That's not appropriate.
Grandma and Father are both waiting here.
How could a junior be absent?
Qingyu.
Xiwu,
Xiwu is still a kid.
She is in her 20s
and a married woman.
Xiwu has married
into another family anyway…
Married or not,
everything she says and
does represent our family tradition.
Well…
Though having been
at the border these years,
I have also heard of
Xiwu's infamous behaviors.
She maltreated our servants,
pushed Bingchang into the water,
got drunk and lost her virginity
in the imperial palace,
and even got married muddleheadedly.
That's right, Qingyu.
You should discipline Ye Xiwu.
Look at my injuries!
On the wedding day of Prince Lin,
an evil bird made a ruckus in our house.
Xiwu left us outside
and rushed back to save her husband,
protecting outsiders.
She's not worthy of her last name Ye!
Zeyu,
as a Ye,
you failed to help someone in need
and protect your sisters,
yet you have the nerve to criticize Xiwu.
At least Xiwu was trying to save someone.
Who were you trying to protect
when getting these wounds?
I'm starving.
I feel so dizzy.
I can't hear anything clearly.
Xiwu has always been unruly.
I'm afraid after I left,
no one was here to teach her how to behave.
I need to go check on her.
Qingyu!
Chuntao, go and help Xiwu out!
Ye Xiwu.
Get up.
We got company.
Let me sleep a little longer.
Someone is coming here. Time for lunch.
Let me sleep.
Tell Chuntao to save some food for me.
This is ridiculous!
Your Ladyship!
Your Ladyship, you…
Why are you yelling?
Who was here?
Your brother, Ye Qingyu.
Yes, Your Ladyship.
Why are you still sleeping here?
Mr. Qingyu came home today!
What does Qingyu's return
have to do with me?
[Got beaten in the palm after all.]
[What will come will come.]
[I can't escape my destiny.]
[Oh no.]
[How come Qingyu
is even more overbearing than Ye Xiwu?]
Ye Xiwu,
Grandma and Father were waiting
in the dining room today,
but you were absent for no reason.
That was unfilial.
Your brother came back
from thousands of miles away,
and Father and Grandma were there
to welcome me home, yet only you weren't.
That was disrespectful.
You are married,
but you were doing…
doing licentious acts in broad daylight.
That was shameless.
I was away from home for three years
and neglected to discipline you.
How could you become such a rascal?
I am unworthy of Ye's glory.
I've realized my mistakes.
Since you've realized your mistakes,
and I just got home,
I won't punish you too harshly.
Kneel here for half an hour
and introspect on your behavior.
Your Ladyship, straighten your back.
If Mr. Qingyu sees you like this,
he will make you kneel
for another half an hour.
But as the younger brother,
he shouldn't teach me a lesson.
Even the oldest brother is scared of me.
But he has the power.
He is our home supervisor.
I thought the supervisor was my dad.
Yes, it used to be him,
but he doesn't like too much red tape,
so when dealing with a lot of things,
he always muddles through them.
But people in Sheng take
clans and etiquette very seriously.
[Clan Patriarchs]
[Then one time, Master found it too much work,]
[memorial tablet]
[so he gave all the worship ceremony work]
[to Mr. Qingyu.]
[Unexpectedly, Mr. Qingyu did a great job,]
[much better than Master.]
[Ever since that,]
[Mr. Qingyu was voted to be the supervisor]
[by all Ye members.]
[Clan Patriarchs]
[Sure, some became prime ministers
at the age of 12,]
but just how unreliable was my dad
that got the whole clan to approve
of this brat becoming the family head?
Don't say that about the Master,
or Mr. Qingyu will punish you again.
When is Qingyu going to leave?
After the Spring Festival, the earliest.
Your Ladyship.
Y-Your Ladyship.
Who is the home supervisor
beating this time?
Mr. Qingyu went to your husband.
[Ye Qingyu is so fierce.]
[If he finds out that Tantai Jin is evil,]
[my brother will get rid
of him immediately.]
Your Ladyship,
Your Ladyship, be careful.
The universe manifests in an inch of land.
The soul follows the mind.
Prince Tantai.
I've heard a lot about you.
Whatever you heard about
is probably not something good.
Slanders and rumors can ruin a person,
but I believe in seeing with my own eyes.
You came here
not to chitchat with me, right?
Firstly,
I want to apologize
for all of Xiwu's misbehavior.
Secondly,
I want to invite you
to a meal with me one day.
Lastly,
my sister is ignorant and unruly,
so please don't let her
mess around in the future.
For example,
her shameful act earlier today.
If word gets out about it,
the Ye family's
and your reputation will be stained.
Shameful act.
Why don't you be straight and tell me
what exactly we were doing?
I can just let it go.
I shouldn't interfere
in your private matters.
But there is another thing
I want to ask you about.
What is it?
Earlier,
were you chanting a spell?
You misheard.
I cultivated in Xiaoyao Sect
for three years.
Although not a master,
I can tell when one is chanting a spell.
Does Xiwu know about this?
Does my father know about it?
You want to know if Ye Xiwu knows,
then why don't you go ask her yourself?
I grew up with Xiwu.
Ahough naughty and mischievous,
she is careless.
She can be easily deceived.
Prince Tantai,
I've heard that there have been
frequent disturbances
and rampant demonic activity
in the capital recently.
What does it have to do with me?
The Xuancheng Palace
suffered a disaster on their wedding day.
Many places still urgently need repair
and my eldest brother's injuries
have not yet healed.
Even my father,
Pillar of the State Great General,
has been injured.
I heard you were there too,
but you're unscathed.
So what?
I was just lucky.
Jing Kingdom's royal symbol
is a three-eye crow.
The beast that broke into
Xuanchen Palace that day
happened to be a crow.
What a coincidence!
General Ye,
considering your amazing imagination,
it's an awful waste of your talent
to have you defend the border.
Prince Tantai,
I have a spell called Bone Inspect,
which can tell one's nature.
Would you care to try it?
Do you have to do this?
If you are innocent,
what's there to be scared about?
Qingyu,
you misunderstood him.
Is half an hour over so fast?
Not yet.
I'll soon go back to the ancestral hall
to make up for it.
Qingyu,
when the monsters were rampaging,
I was with Tantai Jin the whole time.
He almost died.
It wasn't him. Really.
Let me ask you for the last time:
have you been secretly studying spells?
I thought you were mad over some big deal.
Yes, he is practicing spells.
I learned some simple spells recently,
and I thought it was boring
to practice alone,
so I had Tantai Jin practice with me.
But he is so dumb
that he can't grasp them at all.
That's why he was secretly
practicing in the room.
So that's what you are worried about.
What's so secretive about it?
Why couldn't you just tell him?
Learning spells?
Who did you learn spells from?
Remember there were demons in the capital?
I had Scholar Pang teach me a few tricks.
Prince Tantai,
I was rude to you just now.
My apologies.
Xiwu,
I just told Prince Tantai,
since we are family,
he shouldn't eat alone at a single table.
Starting tomorrow,
he may dine with us.
Great. I agree.
You made a very wise decision.
[You only care about eating.]
[Just now if it weren't for me,]
[you might've been killed.]
Qingyu.
Speaking of spells,
can you perform magic as well?
The Bone Inspect spell
you were talking about…
Fake, just to intimidate him.
[I was scared to death.]
Oh, well, Tantai Jin.
Ignorance is bliss.
You are so ignorant and so blessed.
Mr. Qingyu.
Prince Xuanchen sent people
to invite you over.
His Highness said that
after being long parted from you,
he misses you very much.
He invited you to his place to catch up.
Get the horse ready.
Yes.
[Ye Mansion]
General Ye,
it turns out you are also a disciple
from our Mount Buzhao.
Your Highness, I wouldn't figure it out
if you didn't say anything.
Descendants from Sheng's official families
are most likely sent to immortal sects
for a few years of cultivation,
no matter whether they are talented or not.
It's something of a tradition now.
It's normal that Scholar Pang can't tell.
Unlike His Highness,
I don't have his talent in
making elixirs and cultivating.
I only fit in armies, playing with weapons.
You are joking, General Ye.
A talent like you
can even be humble about your gift,
then I would be a parasite of your kingdom.
I heard the emperor of Jing has died.
If the news is true,
I don't know what kind of disturbance
the world will suffer.
You don't need to worry.
Tantai Wuji died of a severe illness,
and his throne would fall into
Tantai Minglang's hands.
I heard this man is paranoid
and bad-tempered.
If he succeeds to the throne,
I'm afraid
Jing Kingdom itself will be in trouble.
As the saying goes,
"the rise brings suffering to the people,
and the fall also
brings suffering to the people."
It has been like this since ancient times.
Your Highness,
although Jing Kingdom is an enemy,
their soldiers and civilians
are all flesh and blood,
no different from us.
General Ye, you are very broad-minded.
I feel ashamed of my shallowness.
As the guardian general of the borders,
I receive the salary from the court.
I am duty-bound to protect Sheng
with all my heart and effort.
However, deep down in my heart,
I hope there will be
no more wars in the world,
and one day the countries can be reunified.
But the hostility between the two kingdoms
has been there for years.
I wonder which powerful lord
will have such courage,
and in which year and month
this will happen.
Your Highness,
if someday you become the emperor
of Sheng,
I…
General Ye,
my father is in his prime.
You should not have said such things.
I spoke out of turn.
Please punish me, Your Highness.
Don't be like this.
The general trend of the world
is that what has been divided
must be united, and vice versa.
You mortals should accept this reality.
How about this?
I'll conduct fortune-telling for you guys.
What fortune?
What's the matter?
According to the divination result,
the person who can end the chaos,
pacify the empire,
and bring happiness to the people
is now in Sheng's capital city.
Let me check again.
[That day, I devoured the succubus,]
[and it gave me temporary power,]
[but it ran out very quickly.]
[My body's yearning for demonic powers]
[seems to be insatiable.]
[Why is this happening?]
Ye Qingyu suspects me,
and Ye Xiwu follows me around every day.
I have to figure out another way
to find new demonic power.
Mr. Qingyu.
Chuntao,
have you seen Mr. Zeyu?
Mr. Zeyu…
He went out early in the morning
after borrowing thirty taels from Miss.
He probably went again to the…
How dare you, Ye Zeyu!
Big!
Another round?
Yes.
For each round you lose,
you have to take off a piece of clothing.
Mr. Zeyu, you have just taken off one,
and if you lose one more time,
you'll
be stripped naked.
So what?
You, a girl, can watch me
without feeling shy,
then why would I flinch?
Let's start.
Another round, then.
Sir, please stop.
Who are you looking for?
Ye Zeyu.
Is he inside?
What is it you want to see him about?
Tell me so I can inform him for you.
I'm here to break his legs.
[Gamble House]
My ancestors, please bless me.
I need to win once!
You don't want to see me
become a laughing stock, do you?
Big!
Open it!
My ancestors,
you guys are unbelievably hard-hearted!
Strip!
I haven't lost yet. You go!
Go!
Mr. Zeyu, are you quite unlucky today?
Small!
-Small!
-Open!
Bless me.
Open!
Small!
It's small!
It's your turn to undress!
Undress!
Go ahead!
Who the hell
dared to hit me?
You did well.
Qingyu, you are here.
Put on your clothes
and go to the ancestral hall.
Kneel there according to
domestic discipline.
Yes.
I'll go right now.
Make way.
Make way for me.
What are you looking at? Look away.
[Ye Qingyu really seems quite powerful.]
[I have to guard against him.]
[My spell skills is progressing slowly,]
[and can be found out easily.]
[It's not nearly
as useful as demonic elixirs.]
[It happens to be Spring Festival,]
[and the streets
are full of the hustle and bustle,]
[suitable for going out and hunting.]
[But Ye Xiwu definitely won't let me out.]
Tantai Jin,
let's go do Spring Festival shopping.
You are looking for trouble yourself.
Why are you dragging me along?
It's not like I'm asking you
to draw a carriage.
Why are you rejecting me?
Everyone should bathe
in the sun more, including you.
In this way, you can get stronger.
Being confined in
that little attic all day long,
you'll become a freak.
[This is just what I want.]
Let's go. Come on.
[Festivals in the mortal world
are so lively.]
[There are more people on this street]
[than the whole of Mount Changze.]
Chuntao, let's get off and walk around.
Your Ladyship, that's delicious too!
You only think about food!
[As Spring Festival approaches,]
[with people coming and going
on the streets,]
[if I look carefully,]
[I should be able to find a monster or two]
[pretending to be people.]
Wait a moment, Sir.
You forgot your cloak.
You can keep it as compensation.
I apologize for my brother.
You are not him.
He owes me,
but why are you paying back on his behalf?
He owes me a piece of clothing.
Are you, the brother,
going to strip on his behalf
in front of me?
Also, the money he owes me
is far more than the value of a dress.
It's sweet. You want some?
Then I'll eat all of it.
So many people here.
[I can distinctly sense
the demonic power nearby.]
[But where is it hiding exactly?]
Delicious chestnuts.
Take a look here.
Chestnuts!
Let's go!
Miss, would you like some chestnuts?
I'll have some, please.
I'll have some.
Alright.
-Bravo!
-Yeah!
Where are you going?
Let's watch this.
Here, have a taste.
Have a try!
OK.
Look at you,
hiding in that attic all day long.
You won't melt in the sun.
You should come out
for a stroll more often,
enjoying some good snacks
to lift your mood.
Great!
Are you saying
I can come out whenever I want?
Of course.
But I should come with you,
lest you get lost.
[This woman is not dumb.]
[She is still guarded with me.]
Your Ladyship,
there are still so many things to buy.
If we keep hanging around like this,
we won't be done even when it gets dark.
Good point.
I'll leave the carriage to you.
You can go back home
after you get everything.
I'll walk around a little longer.
Let's go.
-Good!
-Great!
Awesome!
You got rid of all of them?
Yes.
That Ye Xiwu
is inseparable from His Highness.
Those people probably
won't have another chance
to harm His Highness.
If you want to meet him
under the Ye family's nose,
you have to be cautious.
High Priestess,
Although His Highness
is the princess's son,
he is not so close with the Yiyue tribe.
Also, you had been gone for so long.
What if he refuses to recognize you?
It's not only for the Yiyue tribe,
but also for himself.
Let's go
and find a place to stay the night first.
Yes.
Tantai Jin,
Tantai Jin, what's this?
I don't know.
This is a mud whistle.
Every kid has played with one of these.
Could it be that you two are immortals
who have descended to earth
and do not partake in
the pleasures of mortal life?
[I did come to earth,]
[but I didn't expect Little Devil God
to not recognize this thing.]
[He has been living like a prisoner
since he was a child.]
[Who would buy him toys?]
Here.
[Seeing as how he's looking around]
[with an inexperienced look,]
[I think he is probably just like me,]
[coming to a temple fair
for the first time.]
Tantai Jin,
how about I buy you one?
Ye Xiwu,
were you born yesterday?
Using me as an excuse
to buy toys for yourself.
Fine, it's for me.
Hide!
I didn't expect Qingyu,
who is usually serious,
to come out shopping.
We shopped for half a day.
I think I have paid off
what my brother owes you.
Let me calculate.
The principal has almost been paid off,
but you also need to pay me some interest.
That's a lot of interest.
Of course.
Which color is the prettiest?
All good.
Buy lipstick for me,
and the debt you owe me is cleared.
OK.
Put it on for me, then.
I…
Hurry up.
I'll close my eyes
and spare you the embarrassment,
okay?
Gosh.
Did you see that?
Am I pretty?
Am I hallucinating?
Is that really our home supervisor?
Have you had enough fun?
He turned around to us.
I'll buy these two.
-These two.
-OK.
Have a good one.
Tantai Jin,
do you smell something strange?
No, not a smell.
I can't tell what it is.
No.
[This is the source
of that demonic energy.]
[I've finally found her.]
[If I can take her demonic elixir…]
Pian Ran, where are you from?
I'm not a Sheng citizen.
My hometown is remote,
and you probably haven't heard of it,
even if I tell you.
So you come from afar.
Do you have any relatives in the capital?
No.
I live by myself.
Alone and nowhere to belong.
If I encounter any trouble in the future,
I might have to go to you for help.
No problem.
You may come to me whenever you need help.
My home is just across the bridge ahead.
Mr. Ye, you have been
running around all day with me.
Would you like to come to my place
for a cup of tea?
Today is the New Year's Eve.
My grandmother is at home,
and I shouldn't stay out for too long.
Alright. No need to ramble on.
I can let you go today.
Mr. Ye, remember to retrieve the cloak
when you have time.
Goodbye.
Mr. Ye,
don't forget, now you owe me a cup of tea.
[This man is likable.]
[Never mind.]
[I'm not in a hurry now.]
[Clothing Market]
This dress is perfect for Grandma.
This one is for Dad.
I'll take this one too.
It fits Chuntao perfectly.
Shopkeeper, please pack them for me.
Let's see what else I need.
Oh, Ye Zeyu!
Come in!
What's wrong?
Try it on for me.
My size is different from Mr. Zeyu's.
I think it fits.
Sir,
I will take this one too.
You don't need to pack it.
We will put it on.
Right,
pick several sets of clothes
in this size for each season.
Choose them based on his body measurements.
Pack them all and send them
to General Ye's house.
OK.
Ye Xiwu,
is it for me?
Didn't I promise
to buy you a new one before?
I forgot for many days,
I'm sorry.
What are you standing here for? Put it on.
It's getting dark.
Dad and the others will worry about us.
Go.
Chop, chop.
Change into it.
Finally, we've finished shopping.
We can go home to have
New Year's Eve dinner.
It seems taking you with me
was a pretty wise decision.
Firecrackers. Who wants some firecrackers?
Firecrackers!
She is selling firecrackers.
Chuntao has bought some.
Buy some firecrackers!
There's no harm in buying a few more.
Ye Xiwu
Miss, please buy some firecrackers.
Sis,
I'll buy all the firecrackers
in your basket.
I made these firecrackers
with my own hands.
I'm afraid they are not very good-looking.
Don't worry. I like ones like that.
How much do I owe you?
You can pay me 30 pennies.
No,
pay me 20.
Twenty is enough.
Here.
No, you shouldn't have.
But…
Miss…
You can have this too.
Happy New Year, sis.
Miss, you don't have to…
I met a kind goddess today.
Why did you buy so many firecrackers?
I like setting them off.
You got a problem with that?
It's so cold.
The sooner she sells all of them,
the earlier she can go home
for the festival.
You bought all of them today,
but tomorrow she will still
be out in the cold to sell them.
Maybe she'll meet
another fool like me tomorrow.
Ye Xiwu,
your small bag of money
can't do much for her.
You are right.
There's no way to rid this world of misery,
and there's nothing I can do
to make a difference.
But,
at least she gets to go home earlier
to celebrate New Year's Eve today.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I’ve seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪