The translation team is working hard to replace it with the final subtitles ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 37]
Cang Jiumin has gone back to the Barren Abyss.
Devil Palace has been activated.
It won't be long
before the Devil God returns.
None of this would have happened
if both the Hengyang and Xiaoyao Sects
hadn't shielded that evil being.
It's something unforgivable.
We are a leaderless group
in the face of a very powerful enemy.
As the chief of the Chixiao Sect,
I'm happy to take on the leadership role.
All in favor?
Um…
You're absolutely right, Chief Cen.
The Great Medicine Valley
is at your service from here on.
The Resources Sect is with you too, Chief Cen.
Good.
Now, chiefs,
get back and gather your disciples at once.
I will lead you all
to the Barren Abyss in three days.
We will take out Cang Jiumin!
See? They hate you to the bone.
There is no place for you in this world
other than Devil Palace.
Chief Qu was killed.
Susu is in danger.
Why?
What are you thinking about right now?
Wonder who killed Qu Xuan Zi?
Only three were at the scene.
Qu is dead.
Li Susu is unconscious with serious injuries.
Only Di Mian knows the whole story.
All the sects are convinced that
you were hiding the Sky-Slashing Sword.
That it was you who killed the chief.
That you stole the evil bone
trapped inside Li Susu
and returned here.
It was all you.
Why?
Take a guess.
To pin Chief Qu's
murder on me.
But why did you have to hurt Susu?
Well, that wasn't us.
If we had known the bone was in her body,
we would've taken her too.
But it doesn't matter.
As long as we retrieve the bone
and fuse it to you,
His Lordship will be revived.
The Sky-Slashing Sword…
Di Mian killed Chief Qu with the sword
and then stole the bone.
You're smart.
Cang Jiumin,
my advice is to let go of the past
and move on.
You wanted to be good,
but what is meant to be
has found its way to you.
The people you care about,
the people you love,
they are all going to die because of you.
Still remember what His Lordship said?
Oh, you're pathetic.
He will join the immortal sect.
He'll mistakenly believe that
he's capable of overcoming evil with good.
And he will bask in the warmth of
friendships and emotional bonds,
only to realize it is all but a dream.
Susu has suffered terribly because of the bone.
Because of me.
Maybe Baiyu was right.
Stop.
What?
I see it now.
I will not be
pushed around anymore.
You people keep telling me that
morphing into the Devil God is my calling.
Fine, I will accept my fate.
I'm glad you came around to your senses.
With Qu Xuan Zi dead,
Cang Jiumin gone,
and all the sects focusing their attention on
exterminating the devil fetus,
I'm able to lay low
and take time to heal.
I've got luck on my side.
The evil bone has enormous power.
I can't fuse with it just yet,
or it could backfire.
Now that I have the bone
and the Sky-Slashing Sword,
I'll just have to
wait for the right time to retrieve
the Bone-refining Seal
and the God-slaughtering Crossbow.
Mr. Di Mian, Susu is awake.
She's heartbroken.
Would you please go check on her?
It would be greatly appreciated.
Right, I almost forgot about her.
Hopefully, she hasn't pieced it all together.
Susu.
Apologies, Father.
You came to see me.
It should have been the other way around.
Don't worry about it.
You're still grieving
Chief Qu's death.
I won't judge you
for being too overwhelmed to visit me.
It's perfectly understandable.
You already know what happened, don't you?
I did a terrible job
of protecting--
I, too, was stabbed by him.
Father,
only you were there.
Can you tell me
what really happened?
We were very close to
completing the array.
We were drained.
That's when
Jiumin showed up out of nowhere.
I recognized his weapon.
The Devil God's Sky-Slashing Sword.
He attacked Chief Qu.
And right before I was knocked unconscious,
I saw him cast a spell on you
and walk off with something black.
The Bone-refining Seal wasn't
the first demonic weapon I'd come across.
There was also this crossbow.
And I have both fused into my body.
Jin told me himself
about the God-slaughtering Crossbow himself.
If he had had the Sky-Slashing Sword,
he would have told me, too.
And if he did have the sword
and was truly determined to kill,
I don't think anyone could have survived it.
Are you absolutely sure
it was the Sky-Slashing Sword?
I was once a leader of demons.
I know the Sky-Slashing Sword when I see it.
I wish I were strong enough
to defend Chief Qu.
The helplessness reminds me of
my days back in the Demon Realm.
The devil fetus is the root of the Devil God.
Nothing is going to change that.
I should have known he wasn't being authentic.
I made
a misjudgment.
Susu,
you must cut him out of your life
and move on.
Don't repeat my mistake.
It's getting late.
I should probably go.
Rest well, Susu.
This is the only way
to get to the truth.
Yaoguang, I want to see you.
This place looks even more lifeless
than it did 10,000 years ago.
And you know that how?
Are you questioning me?
Susu,
it's unsafe for you to be around Di Mian.
I have to do this to keep you safe.
Are you two
all that I have?
What do you mean?
10,000 years ago, Di Mian changed sides
and worked against me
in league with the deities.
I want the evil bone returned.
And I want him to welcome me on his knees
in front of Devil Palace when I am restored.
-Absolutely.
Master,
our scouts posted outside
the Barren Abyss have reported back.
Jiumin is in the Abyss
How is he?
Si Ying and Jing Mie
were bowing and scraping to him,
as if they were serving him.
Those were their exact words.
Don't tell anybody about this.
Jiumin must have had his reasons.
But right now,
those short-sighted fools from the Chixiao Sect
are calling the shots around here.
We are the only ones
that trust Jiumin.
[Uncle Zhaoyou From Li Susu]
Oh, there's one more person.
Susu.
Father,
how is your recovery coming along?
Yaoguang told me that
you usually take care of your own injuries.
I know a thing or two about healing wounds.
I could examine yours.
I'm good.
I've been a demon for over 10,000 years.
My blood would contaminate you.
Well, I am your daughter.
I'll be fine.
I've lost one of my fathers.
All the more reason
to be there for you when you need me.
Are you sure you want to do this?
Yes.
Sure,
if you insist.
Come on in.
I'm just worried the nasty wound
will scare you.
Why? What is it
you're afraid of?
Susu,
10,000 years I've been alive.
Yet our time spent together
is less than a tenth
of your time spent with Chief Qu.
I feel so guilty.
He was a busy man.
I didn't always get his attention.
But he was noble and honest.
And he had a big heart.
Growing up
with such positive influences in my life,
it's truly the luckiest thing
to ever happen to me.
Yaoguang,
did you assess my father's wound?
Was he really stabbed by the Sky-Slashing Sword?
He said he's been a demon for over 10,000 years.
And that he would have
to heal himself with his own demonic energy.
So, no, I did not.
The cut…
It was done by Father.
Susu,
don't be scared.
They'll find you
soon enough.
Di Mian,
where do you think you're going?
So it was a ploy by you
and my daughter, huh?
That's right.
Di Mian,
you're not getting out of here today.
Hand over the evil bone!
You've found the Devil Palace?
Stop screwing around!
Hand the evil bone over,
and I'll grant you an easy death.
You think
you can get the evil bone?
Don't be stuck with this old fart.
Di Mian the bloody twit mustn't get away!
[Oh, damn!]
[Hardly has the old wound healed
when another follows.]
[No. They've found the Devil Palace.]
[I must take in the evil bone's power
right off the bat,]
[so that those two fools get nothing.]
Uncle Zhouyou!
Uncle Zhouyou.
Are you all right?
Here.
Susu.
Just now,
Si Ying and Jing Mie appeared.
They wanted to help out Di Mian?
They wanted the same things as us:
to seize Di Mian
and to take back the evil bone.
Since this failed attack,
Di Mian is certain to hasten
to consume the evil bone.
I'm afraid that'll be irrecoverable.
By the way, where is Jiwu?
He heard that Chief Cen
and company had started off,
so he summoned our fellows
to go after them.
Jiwu has been unsettled lately.
To hustle for the Barren Abyss
is nothing but to go to his death.
That's not an option.
Someone must stop him now.
Then I'll go to stop Jiwu right now.
Right. Let's split up.
I'll chase after Di Mian.
Welcome our Devil God back.
[My Lord, we hardly make it.]
[Di Mian the bloody twit got away.]
[Shall we send all the demons hunt him?]
[No.]
Instead, I'll call them all back.
I'll command all the demons and devils
and reinvigorate the Barren Abyss.
[Di Mian, together with the evil bone,
has left the immortal sects,]
[which has also kept Susu
free from the turmoil.]
[She should be safe now.]
[Master won't let Di Mian get away,
for sure.]
[The point is this pair of devils,
with the Barren Abyss.]
[If they get the evil bone back]
[and merge it into me…]
[I'll definitely not repeat]
[the advent of the Devil God.]
Oh! Tantai Jin has a screw loose.
You are my right-hand persons.
Go along with me into the palace.
[Demons are gathered.]
[Something serious might happen.]
[The cloak that
Chongyu Harp transforms into]
[can temporarily make me invisible
to common demons]
[so that I can get in the Barren Abyss.]
[Hope it's not late.]
[All the demons from Four Continents]
[have been here in the Barren Abyss.]
[Now is the right time.]
My Lord.
What's up?
For over ten thousand years,
have you ever heard of Xiaoyao Sect's
Incarnation-Abandoning Array?
Cang Jiumin,
what are you trying to pull?
Cang Jiumin.
[The runes are exclusively
harmful to demons.]
[It seems of our immortal sects.]
My feet got locked!
Abandon my incarnation
together with the Devil Realm.
If I die,
what else can you count on
to welcome your Devil God back?
[Tantai Jin,]
[what the hell are you fearing?]
[How should you idiot kill yourself?]
The one who is fearing is not me, but you.
[Ridiculous!]
[You think merely a perished incarnation]
[can prevent one more advent of mine?]
[You think too highly of yourself.]
Can't it?
Since the Devil God
can have everything under control,
why bother advise me to stop?
[Tantai Jin,]
[you choose to sacrifice your life so soon.]
[What a pity!]
[Tantai Jin,]
[why do you choose to die?]
Ming Ye.
The Heart-guarding Scale turns out
to still keep a wisp
of your divine consciousness.
[Right.]
[You've managed to awake it again
by using the divine soul]
[for refining the Heart-guarding Scale.]
[I see.]
[Incarnation-Abandoning Array
is in the nick of time.]
[It's not late if you stop now.]
My very birth comes from
the Devil God's evil thoughts.
If my destruction
can possibly save
the whole Four Continents,
my existence has been not in vain.
[All joys and sorrows of the world]
[are no more than how love lives and dies.]
[Tantai Jin, you're born for the Devil God.]
[Then what do you die for?]
I know
that life is priceless,
but since merely my death
can prevent more deaths,
I prefer to safeguard this place.
I want to safeguard everything at my side,
[just as you]
[wanted to safeguard the Mohe River.]
[You've ever asked me]
[why to select you to enter my Bo're Life.]
[So now you see?]
[At that war,]
[the sealed evil bone]
[fell into the mortal world
as the Pillar of Heaven scattered.]
[The Devil God will use the evil bone]
[to select a devil fetus
for his resurrection.]
[I've used up my divine power.]
[All I could do was to leave the Bo're Life
at the bottom of Mohe River.]
[Ji Ze had ever seen both of your illusions.]
in Sang Jiu and me.]
[I know]
[that you are certain to come up.]
[Now I've finished what I can.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[it's time you made a choice.]
[Our ten-thousand-year fate ends here.]
[Goodbye.]
♪That look♪
Sister.
What happened?
If that protection treasure didn't show up,
I'm afraid
we'd already be long dead.
Sister,
you were right.
Cang Jiumin is indeed full of tricks.
We must take back the evil bone
and awaken the Devil God soon.
Nian Baiyu,
your master has been deprived of cultivation.
I don't think he can play any more tricks.
Watch him closely.
When we return a few days later,
we'll inject the evil bone into him
and the Devil God will resurrect.
And your people
will be free.
Did you smell that?
I think I smell humans.
Over there! Go!
Further ahead is the entrance of Barren Abyss.
Sect Leader Cen,
should we keep going?
Barren Abyss is the gathering place of demons.
They know the terrains better than us.
If I send disciples into the abyss rashly,
I'm afraid we'd suffer heavy casualties.
But the evil bone and the devil fetus
have returned to the Devil Palace.
Demons everywhere are moving towards here.
If this goes on,
the arrival of the Devil God can only be nearer.
once he activated the All-in-distress Way,
everything will be too late.
Goddess Liuzhi,
you're getting a little impatient, huh?
How about this?
You let your Penglai disciples
go scout the abyss first.
I thank you on behalf of all disciples here.
You!
Back when we're on the Demon Subduing Peak,
Hengyang and Xiaoyao sects
vouched for the devil fetus.
Now the devil fetus escaped
and led to disaster.
I'm willing to lead the two sects
to enter the abyss first
and scout the whereabouts of the devil fetus.
Sect Leader Gongye,
I've felt how eager you are
to try to make up for your mistake.
Although Hengyang Sect's mistake
is irrecoverable
we cultivator always try to be magnanimous.
I guess I'll have to
give you this chance.
Thanks, Sect Leader Cen.
Inform us first if there's anything.
There are too few of you.
Don't fight head-on.
[Lord of Evil.]
Devil God?
Impossible.
I've absorbed the evil bone.
It's already mine.
I'm the Devil God now.
[Lord of Evil,]
[you didn't disappoint me after all.]
[You think you can replace me]
[and my power will be yours]
[after absorbing the evil bone?]
[All greedy ones in the world]
[will only be the container of the evil bone.]
[You're mine now.]
I'm not Si Ying.
I don't give a damn about
reviving the Devil God.
Now all your cultivation is lost
and you can't fight back,
why don't I just
eat you?
[Master,]
[it's all my fault.]
[If you'd rather die than be the Devil God,]
[I'll definitely get you out of here.]
[Without my master,]
[there will not be me today.]
[But except for him,]
there's another one who helped me greatly.
That person is you.
Back when I was still a hostage prince,
I was plotted against by my brother.
I was injured and stranded.
It's you who risked your life to find me
[and helped me return to Jing Kingdom]
[and ascend the throne.]
[Later,]
when I lost all hope because of Ye Xiwu,
it's you again
[who risked your life]
-to save me from the big fire.
-Your Majesty!
Without you,
how can I still be alive today?
How can I manage
to find her again?
[I wouldn't take the credit.]
[It's the blessing]
[that you're born with, Master.]
Blessing?
I was born as devil fetus with the evil bone.
You call that a blessing?
In this vast Mount Changze,
there's no one else but you
who can drink with me now.
Who's sneaking around here?
Such a complex smell of blood.
I haven't tasted this in quite a while.
It really tastes a little special.
Loyalty, innocence,
recklessness,
and a bit of bitterness due to guilty.
So, are you here because of loyalty,
or guilty?
I come to save my Lord.
He sees me as a friend
but was betrayed by me.
I must take him away
even risking my life.
It's the rich tastes I love.
Then, as you wish!
You are a cunning man.
A thousand-year cultivation
is hard to get.
You set his free,
then I'll let you go.
You let me go?
I'll drain all your blood.
My Lord!
[Jin,]
[you can only be me.]
[That's the whole life
of the devil fetus.]
I said, let him go.
It tastes awful.
Your blood can absorb our devil power.
Only Devil God can do this.
You are really Devil God.
Go.
But you're different from him.
Your blood is with a tiny little bit
of sweet taste
and a warm feeling of sunshine.
Just a tiny bit.
But I still can taste them.
What's that?
Go.
My Lord,
they're gonna play hardball with us.
As Si Ying and Jing Mie are not here,
you'd better run away quickly.
But they ask you to guard me.
I shouldn't believe
what Si Ying and Jing Mie said
and decided for myself for you.
It's pointless to say this.
Let's manage to get away first.
Ok.
You save me behind the back
of Si Ying and Jing Mie.
They definitly will find out.
So, what are you gonna do?
At worst, I'll die.
What about the people of Yiyue tribe?
I can't just
watch them kill you
and I can't do anything.
So, this is your plan.
Put the whole clan at stake
for my own life.
I'll protect you to leave here,
then I shall go back
to find a way for them.
If I can't save them,
I'll die with them.
I'll help you to find the solution.
Thanks a lot, my Lord.
They're
from my clan as well.
Go.
Be careful. You're hurt.
Never mind.
We're almost arrived.
The exit is just ahead.
[You, a devil fetus, get me worried.]
[I can't let them know
that he's Nian Baiyu.]
My Lord, what are you doing?
Go to hell.
You wish to kick down the ladder
even you don't get away.
The one who betrays me will never
get the chance to live from me.
Besides, he is willing
to lead the way when got frightened by me.
Such a coward like him
are not gonna stay by my side.
I was wondering
if this guy garnered his courage today.
Because he is obey
in every way for me for a long time.
It's you. You ruined a good stooge of me.
I'm sorry then.
How exactly did you get out?
Then the whole Demon Realm
is my residence.
And all devils are my subjects.
ou want to trap me with this.
Isn't it funny?
Si Ying spared your life
for the sake of the Lord,
while you ruin my plan repeatly.
Now, Si Ying isn't here.
so you may die with a whole body.
That'll be good end for you.
Go.
You killed many of our devils.
Now they will
take revenge on you.
Drain him.
Cang Jiumin,
you shouldn't be spared.
[Good.]
[Finnaly, you use the force and skill
of the Devil Tribe. ]
[That's what the Devil God
should be like.]
[I need to get out of here in a hurry.]
What a pity. He's just a husk after all.
Why don't we just kill him?
What's the hurry?
We haven't got the evil bone yet.
Let's go.
Let's pick that boy back.
Come out now and beg for mercy!
Don't waste my time.
Otherwise,
I'll break all your bones when I catch you.
Come out!
[How should I escape?]
[From the traces left by the demonic energy,]
[Di Mian may have absorbed the evil bone.]
[If he returns to the Devil Palace with it,]
[everything will be irrecoverable.]
Come out!
Give me power.
His Highness? It's His Highness's voice!
It's Di Mian.
This is
the smell of the evil bone.
Help me!
The devil energy is surging.
Did he swallow the evil bone?
Run!
Jing Mie!
Not enough.
Go!
It's the evil bone.
The evil bone is absorbing the energy.
Get out of here!
My Lord!
Si Ying,
I still need strength for my resurrection.
This is the Devil God's voice.
Di Mian is controlled by the Devil God.
My Lord…
Si Ying,
are you not willing to be sacrificed to me?
Since the day you brought me back,
I have made the decision
to live for My Lord,
and die for My Lord
forever and ever.
My Lord, wait for me.
From now on,
I am a part of you, My Lord.
Si Ying!
Di Mian now is carrying the evil bone,
and no one can stop him at all.
Is he going to the Devil Palace?
Is he going to start the All-in-Distress Way?
This is too dangerous.
No.
I have to figure out a way
to inform the immortal sect immediately.
What should I do? It would take
way too long walking like this.
This is the warning bell set by the Master.
Using devil energy to trigger
the Stone Inscription Array,
the Immortal Sect will notice immediately.
This is the fastest way.
Come on!
Send the alert now!
That's great!
It's from the warning bell
by the Barren Abyss!
There is devil energy that triggered the array.
Tantai Jin!
We finally got you.
The devil fetus has showed up.
The evil bone should not have
fused with him yet.
Everyone, start the form with me now!
The Subdueing Devil Form!
Brother Gongye…
I mean Chief Gongye,
I am willing to lead
the disciples of Xiaoyao Sect
to capture Cang Jiumin alive.
Chief Gongye!
Not allowed.
He is Tantai Jin,
who was born as the devil fetus.
He killed Master and stole the evil bone.
He is not the Cang Jiumin you know anymore.
Even today,
you still feel pity for the devil fetus.
If it weren't for your womanly mercy,
how could the sects of the four continents
be forced into such a predicament?
Why?
Where are they?
Chief Cen is right.
We can't make the same mistake again.
The Immortal Sect can no longer
be soft-hearted towards him,
otherwise the next victim sacrificed
would be other sect's fellows.
Enough said.
This is the right time
to kill the devil fetus.
Tantai Jin,
you won't get away this time!
Why is no one coming here?
Go stop Di Mian,
or it will be too late!
Chief Cen's attack is lethal!
I want him to die
and burn to the ground,
to avenge my son's death.
Go stop Di Mian!
Don't let him start the All-in-Distress Way!
Chief Gongye,
you had a good private relationship
with Jiumin.
How can you bear to do this…
Cang Jiumin never existed.
He has been the devil fetus
from the beginning to end.
He joined our immortal sect
juet to take away the evil bone.
Kill him. Kill the devil fetus!
Tantai Jin,
I want you to pay for Master's life!
Why?
Why is no one coming?
I can't believe he got away!
He can't run.
The disciples of the Hengyang Sect,
follow my order!
Follow me into the Barren Abyss to hunt.
If you see Tantai Jin,
kill on sight.
Let's go.
Get up.
Open it for me.
Open the door!
Start the All-in-Distress Way!
My plan will be fulfilled after this one step.
Si Ying!
Who killed you?
Si Ying,
wait for me.
In the blink of an eye,
ten thousand years have passed.
The evil bone has finally returned here.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪