♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 16]
Here.
What's wrong?
Feeling unwell?
Mozhu,
if a friend of yours left you
and could never make it back,
what would you do?
What if he died
instead of refusing to come back?
If you have a spare moment today,
could you buy me some wine from the town?
Your sight isn't recovered. You can't drink.
Not for me.
I want it for my dead friends.
I heard
when a mortal's relatives or friends died,
[they would offer a wine sacrifice]
[to console the dead.]
[Some of my friends,]
[who were very important to me,]
[passed away before me.]
[Where do you think]
[mortals will end up after they die?]
[Their souls will wander]
[until they get to the Nether River]
[and float to the end
of the world down the river.]
[What about gods?]
[Gods have no souls.]
[When gods die,]
[they'll be completely gone in this world]
[and can't be seen anywhere.]
[But when they're remembered,]
[they won't be completely gone.]
A new prescription?
Yes.
Maybe this one is gonna work.
If I can't recover, don't try so hard.
Just let it be.
What are you talking about?
Good medicine usually tastes bad.
Just take it.
Or what? Never get back your sight
and stay here forever for free food?
I don't know where else I can go.
I don't have relatives.
All my friends died.
My wife...
No.
She's no longer my wife.
She hates me.
I'm afraid we wouldn't ever meet again.
How...
How do you feel about her?
[I made it clear from the outset]
[we would go our own way without interference.]
Ming Ye,
when you feel any better with your eyes,
even if you can see a little bit of light,
remember to tell me.
I have to be prepared.
Prepared for what?
[I must be prepared]
[to leave here.]
Don't be so nosy.
Just let me know.
Will you always be living here?
Why did you ask?
Now, in this world,
you're my only friend.
May I visit you occasionally?
You can't.
After you get your sight back,
I'll leave immediately.
Where will you go?
I can't tell, really.
Anywhere.
I'll just travel around, leading a free life.
[If you knew it was me,]
[I'm afraid you wouldn't want to visit me.]
Be careful on the stairs.
Come on.
What a sunny day today!
Sit down and let me comb your hair.
What? Just sit down.
It's the jasmine balm I made yesterday.
You're lucky to have some.
What... What's wrong?
♪Reviewing the past years♪
♪The vivid and splendid dreams
are but a regret that won't fade, it seems♪
♪Rather than wake from this slumber
I'd prefer the dream to last forever♪
I'm fine.
Why are your eyes red?
Nothing.
Maybe the balm brought tears to my eyes.
You should have told me.
Let me check.
♪I'm never heartless♪
♪My emotions ebb and flow like the seasons♪
♪Even if sorrows never end♪
♪A fair complexion remains unafraid
of being soaked in tears♪
♪I can exchange everything for this life♪
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
♪True love is rare though♪
Any better?
♪While the fireworks of life
are short-lived and easily enjoyed♪
♪But this time, who will come and go♪
♪While waiting and enduring this bitter sorrow?♪
What?
Nothing.
I thought your eyes recovered.
Don't be too sad.
Your eyes would recover.
These herbs are very efficacious.
[So, my destiny isn't that bad.]
[I thought we wouldn't meet once more.]
[I never believed that I meet you again.]
[Sang Jiu,]
[if I couldn't recover,]
[would we always]
[stay together in this forest?]
[When I get the chance]
[to tell Sang Jiu the truth,]
[I'll take her back to Shangqing Realm]
[before I manage to refine her body.]
[I almost forgot.]
[My brother is coming in a few days.]
[I totally forgot my lessons lately.]
I've nearly recovered.
How about we switch places?
Come and sleep in bed.
No way.
Your eyes haven't got better.
Then come up on the bed.
We can squeeze up.
Don't worry. I'm a quiet sleeper.
I won't disturb you.
All right. Get to sleep.
Fine.
How come he hasn't got his sight back yet?
Tomorrow, I'll go up the mountain
for another kind of herb.
It's said to be very efficacious.
[Sang Jiu,]
[don't blame me for lying.]
[I just want us
to stay together like this for longer.]
[Even longer.]
Ming Ye.
Here. Take the decoction
before it gets cold.
Open your mouth.
So sweet.
Is it honey?
Yes.
Because you don't like the bitter decoction.
Come over.
You got a bee sting when stealing some honey?
Closer.
Still closer.
All right.
It no longer hurts.
Report, Goddess!
In a bamboo forest,
we found a trace of God Ming Ye!
Come on.
Sit here in the sun.
I'll be back before noon.
I'll bring back some bamboo shoots for soup.
All right.
Oh,
if you're thirsty,
the water is on the table in front of you.
Some leftovers in the kitchen.
If the wind rises,
you have to put on your cloak.
Yeah, right beside you.
All right.
I should go.
Ming Ye!
What are you doing in this place?
You're safe.
But why didn't you return or let me know?
I was badly wounded.
I stayed here and recuperated
just from some peace.
Sorry to have kept you worried.
You've recovered, huh?
Ming Ye,
how much longer will you stay here?
You go back without me.
The scenery here is great.
I want to stay for a few days longer.
But you've just recovered.
You need someone to take care of you.
How about I stay?
Don't bother.
Someone takes care of me here.
If you don't mind,
I'm going back for some rest.
I have to tell you something
concerning a lot of people.
What is it?
Yesterday, celestial soldiers reported
they found the Devil God's Bone-refining Seal
in a valley.
That's why I hurried to you.
If the devil energy overflows,
I'm afraid...
The Bone-refining Seal has scary devil energy.
If the air or water is polluted,
the consequences can be catastrophic.
We must not delay a single moment.
Go.
You two lead the way.
-Aye.
Hold on a minute.
Here we go.
Ming Ye,
go with them.
I'll fetch a weapon from Yuqing Palace
and then catch up.
All right.
[Sang Jiu,]
[I'm in a hurry to leave.]
[Hearing that a devil artifact appeared,]
[I have to go take care of it immediately.]
[In one to ten days,]
[I will come back]
[and explain everything to you.]
[Sorry to leave without telling you.]
[I'll always miss you.]
[Ming Ye.]
The Bone-refining Seal is there in the center.
The hole was smashed.
After the Devil God was gone,
I had our soldiers search everywhere,
and finally they found this devil artifact.
Thank you for your hard work.
To have found the Bone-refining Seal
only consumed time and manpower.
Your complete disappearance for days
actually exhausted me.
Now, the Devil God is dead.
Without a master,
the Three Devil Artifacts are less powerful.
But their devil energy still floats for miles.
If we don't stop it,
I'm afraid soon this place will be
a shelter for demons.
My father told me
among the Three Devil Artifacts,
the Bone-refining Seal has
the most inscrutable functions.
It can enhance the devil energy
and also make a seal or barrier.
When some celestial soldiers were captured,
they were deprived of their divine essence,
infused with devil energy,
and then became demons.
I really didn't dare to act rashly.
I had our men guard here
until I found you.
[Deprived of their divine essence?]
[Sang Jiu is my single daughter,]
[and the princess of our realm!]
For you, she extracted her divine essence
and could never be immortal!
[Now, you think you can move on]
[just by saying thank you?]
I'll be devoured by my demonic energy.
[If it can deprive someone
of his divine essence,]
[maybe it can also]
[help Sang Jiu rebuild her divine essence.]
I'll go check it out.
Ming Ye!
[This artifact appears to be evil]
[but is moderate inside.]
[Without any devil energy,]
[maybe it can be purified]
[and used in some other way.]
[The devil energy is stemmed
for the time being.]
[I have to get it out immediately.]
[The Seal has huge devil energy]
[and has gradually infiltrated into the earth.]
[Powerful as I am,]
[I can't easily get it out.]
[I think I have to do this.]
[Heart-guarding Scale.]
[This is]
[the hardest scale of mine.]
[With my divine power in it,]
[it can serve as a shield]
[to isolate the devil energy in the Seal.]
Ming Ye, how was it going?
The Seal crashed against the earth here.
They're nearly integrating.
For the Bone-refining Seal,
I have to exchange something.
I then exchanged my Heart-guarding Scale for it.
The Heart-guarding Scale was in your flesh.
How could you just pull it out?
The bodily pain
wasn't much of a thing.
My father died
in the fight against the Devil God.
Now, you sacrificed your Heart-guarding Scale
for the devil artifact to protect people.
You deserve to be the God of War.
If Father knew about this,
he would be gratified, too.
I conjured a heavy rain.
And the protection of my Heart-guarding Scale,
it won't be long
before this place
has abundant spiritual energy.
Surrounded by mountains,
there's no light in the valley.
Let's call it Mount Buzhao.
It's quite considerate of you, Ming Ye.
Father had many subordinates and disciples.
Only you followed in his steps
and knew his wishes best.
So, you would also protect
what my father had protected, right?
Let's go.
Back to Shangqing Realm first.
[So, this is the Fire Quadripod.]
[Before the world came into being,]
[the Quadripod's four legs
represented four seasons.]
[The fire in it was the sun.]
Burning fiercely.
When Tian Hao was alive,
he used it to purify demons.
Unfortunately, it would shorten the user's life
and cost quite a lot.
Since then, it has been sealed here.
Purifying the Bone-refining Seal
with the Fire Quadripod
would really be perfect.
If it works,
the purification can be done
in four days and nights.
Then, I can use it to cure Sang Jiu.
[In the Fire Quadripod,]
[there are four seasons.]
[They can purify everything.]
[When I burn my divine essence,]
[I can wash the devil energy off the Seal.]
[Maybe I can get some good luck.]
[And we]
[we can start all over again.]
[God Ming Ye.]
[You can call me Ming Ye.]
How about you taste one?
Taste it. Very sweet.
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
♪That's about to fall from the edge of the sky♪
♪I wanna hang a glittering butterfly there
till the snow falls♪
♪I wanna hang it in a wrong time♪
Stare at your sword, not me.
[Will you do co-cultivation with me?]
[What?]
♪Why don't we just be like this♪
♪For ten thousand years?♪
♪Let's freeze time♪
♪Before we say goodbye♪
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
[Divorce Certificate]
I'm sure I'm gonna die.
[Sang Jiu,]
[I would rather you leave]
[than stay here and die alone.]
Over all these days,
I didn't dare to say anything
or do anything.
I didn't even dare to stare at you
or talk to you.
Now, you don't even want to see me.
And will you expel me with a mere certificate?
[Have you ever,]
[even a little bit]
[or even for a second,]
[loved me?]
[No.]
[Sang Jiu.]
[Now, the Devil God is killed.]
[Stability has been achieved in Three Realms.]
[And luckily, I got this.]
[I owed you that much]
[and I'll slowly make it up for you.]
[Wait until I'm back to you.]
[Whatever it costs,]
[I will purify the Bone-refining Seal]
[and remove the devil energy from you.]
[Ming Ye,]
[how could you try
to use the Bone-refining Seal]
[to cure that clam who lost her divine essence?]
[For her,]
[you even risked your life]
[to use the Fire Quadripod.]
[Very well.]
Goddess, soldiers have assembled.
Thank you.
I lost my parents
and made no achievements in battles.
But you still take orders from me.
I'm quite grateful.
Don't say that, Goddess.
Not only I
but also everyone else here
followed your father Tian Hao
to have settled in Shangqing Realm.
Though you're young,
you're the Goddess of flying serpents
and owner of Yuqing Palace.
We don't dare to forget that.
Glad to hear that.
Ming Ye will have
entered a strict meditation retreat for days.
To find the devil artifacts
is concerned with people's lives.
It can't be suspended.
I was just reported
that one devil artifact was picked by the clams.
Please go with me to search for it.
Aye.
[Try to fight with me for Ming Ye?]
[Sang Jiu, can you even survive?]
[Where on earth has Ming Ye gone?]
[I've been looking for him in the woods]
[all day.]
[With his vision lost,
he couldn't have gone too far.]
[Did somebody take him?]
By order of Lord Ming,
you will kill the clam on sight.
Search the place.
Right away.
[It's Huan.]
[Ye has already returned
to the Shangqing Realm.]
[Kill me on sight?]
[Ye,]
[is that you trying to kill me?]
Goddess Tian Huan,
there's nobody here.
there's no one outside either.
Goddess Tian Huan,
there's been no trace of Sang Jiu.
Looks like she is one step ahead of me.
Now she's loose.
Well,
she can run,
but she can't hide.
Let's go.
[No.]
[I need to find out what that was all about.]
[What happened here?]
[These are new faces.]
Halt.
Who are you and why are you here?
I...
I'm a low-ranking immortal from the Lower Realm.
And I'm here to see Lord Ming.
But you don't even have divine essence.
You are not so much an immortal
as an imp.
What do you want to see the God of War about?
An urgent matter.
Would you please get word to him?
I need to give this to him...
What is this thing?
I'm not passing it on to the God of War.
Please just go.
I wish I could help you,
but the God of War is
in a 4-day strict meditation retreat.
He's not taking any visitors.
A strict meditation retreat? Why?
Is he not feeling well?
It's about the Four Continents and Three Realms,
of course.
He is the key to peace in the whole universe.
If something were to happen to him in training,
we would be so screwed.
Then what has Goddess Tian Huan been up to?
Being on the same page with the God of War,
Goddess Tian Huan
is leading the hunt
for devil weapons scattered around the universe.
and evil beings roaming
the Four Continents and Three Realms.
If any one of you troublemakers
is connected to the Devil God,
well, you might want to watch your back.
Mm, that's right.
[Since Ye is tied up with his cultivation,]
[I think I'll just wait it out.]
[I have to get to the bottom of it all.]
Charge.
If you want to hurt my people,
you'll have to go through me first.
Is this river a rogue-making machine or what?
You're seriously going to fight me?
What a vain, foolish man.
Come on, we've got to protect Father.
Absolutely.
Seize him.
You old clam demon
Thousands of years of cultivating,
yet you couldn't even take 100 blows
dealt from my Moon Blast.
And you call yourself a King?
That's funny.
Your son, on the other hand, was a handful.
But he, too, was defeated by me.
Tian Huan, what do you want?
To wipe evil creatures off the map.
I am told the Water Tribe of the Mohe River
is in cahoots with the Devil God
and is possessing a devil weapon.
These are crimes punishable
by familial extermination.
But... if you hand over the weapon,
only the one who leads gets punished.
The rest of you will be let off the hook.
In cahoots with the Devil God?
That's utter nonsense.
We, the people of the Water Tribe,
stay in our own lanes.
And we have done absolutely nothing wrong.
Is this the way
the people of the Shangqing Realm do things?
Framing people for crimes they didn't commit?
We offer protections to the three realms.
I don't need some puck
to tell me what to do.
So keep your opinions to yourself.
Why are you doing this to us?
Have you forgotten the kindness
we once showed you and Ye?
You're right.
There hasn't been bad blood between us.
So what makes you think it's a setup?
Because you're stone broke?
Because you're capable of evil?
Or because these crappy pearls of yours?
Goddess,
should we run this by the God of War?
Excuse me?
Well, he is...
he's the Clam King's son-in-law.
Mm, so?
This bunch of shellfish
forced Ye into
marrying that smelly clam.
He doesn't even like her.
He already dumped her.
Pretty bold of them
to set up that clam with Ye.
But... there's no sign of a devil weapon.
That's because you lot suck at your job.
Not finding any devil weapons
doesn't mean they aren't the Devil God's allies.
What?
Found your conscience
after killing so many
of the Water Tribe members?
Trust me.
They are in league with the Devil God.
We may not have found the weapon,
but they fought back,
which was suspicious.
These evil beings are cunning.
Our soldiers fought back
as an act of self-defense.
Don't worry.
Ye won't blame me for this.
We do not possess any devil weapons.
But one thing's for sure. You are bitter.
You're jealous because my daughter married Ye.
That's why you set her up.
I'm jealous of her?
A flying serpent is a spirit beast.
Why would I, the flying serpent Goddess,
be envious of
an annoying, unsophisticated
clam?
Let me tell you something.
When that b*tch of a clam
had an episode the other day,
I offered to look after her.
I added some freshwater to the spring water.
And I told her that was some Refining Spring.
That dumb woman actually took my word for it
and soaked in the water despite the pain.
Tian Huan,
how could you be so heartless?
Whatever you do
will come back to you, you hear me?
Old fool,
you and your kind will be wiped out today,
all thanks to your daughter.
Getting involved with my Ye,
she's bitten off more than she can chew.
[Sang Jiu,]
[this is what you get for pissing me off.]
[By order of Lord Ming,]
[you will kill the clam on sight.]
[Search the place.]
[Right away.]
[Why isn't this Reflection Pearl
working anymore?]
[It runs on Sang You's demonic power.]
[Oh my.]
[Did something happen to Sang You?]
[You're still new
to the demonic cultivation method.]
You aren't stable yet.
You need to avoid mood swings,
or you could slip into madness.
[No one else in the Mohe River]
is fairer than you, Princess Jiu.
I'm sure
[you'll marry the right man someday.]
[Oh, you.]
[You are one to talk.]
[Ming Ye has divine essence.]
[And you do, too.]
[He is the God of War.]
[But you?]
[You follow me and Sang You everywhere]
[and do nothing all day.]
[Have you no shame?]
[Remember,]
[your wish will come true.]
[It really will.]
[You just have to pray hard enough.]
[All right, sweetheart,]
[you should go to bed.]
[I'll see you in the morning.]
[I am told the Water Tribe of the Mohe River]
[is in cahoots with the Devil God
and is possessing a devil weapon.]
[These are crimes punishable
by familial extermination.]
[We do not possess any devil weapons.]
[But one thing's for sure. You are bitter.]
[You're jealous because my daughter married Ye.]
[That's why you set her up.]
[I'm jealous of her?]
[Let me tell you people something.]
[When that b*tch of a clam
had an episode the other day,]
[I offered to look after her.]
[I added some freshwater to the spring water.]
[And I told her that was some Refining Spring.]
[That dumb woman actually took my word for it]
[and soaked in the water despite the pain.]
[Old fool,]
[you and your kind will be wiped out today,]
[all thanks to your daughter.]
[Getting involved with my Ye,]
[she's bitten off more than she can chew.
I'm sorry... This is... all my fault...
I shouldn't have fallen for him...
I shouldn't have saved him...
and then married him...
Everything is my fault...
I should've known better,
Father.
I'm unworthy to be called your daughter.
Or Princess of Mohe River, for that matter.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
And suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
Covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
While on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
Our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
Leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
Of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
As flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
Come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
As gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪