♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 9]
[Father,]
[Gongye,]
[I'm so useless.]
[I couldn't save
the Four Continents and Three Realms.]
[And I didn't stop
the Devil God from resurgence.]
[This is…]
[The ancient divine artifac,
World-alluring Jade?]
[Martial Uncle once told me,]
[it's an ominous object]
[lost tens of thousands of years ago.]
[It's forged by a witch]
[with tens of thousands
of immortal bones.]
[Why is it at the bottom
of the Mohe River?]
[And why would it save me?]
[Enough.]
[I'll just keep it]
[and get out of here first.]
Congratulations, Your Highness!
This time we wiped out Tantai Jin
because of Your Highness's leadership.
I'm willing to die for Your Highness
without hesitation!
What's your name?
Qi Shuang.
I used to be the deputy leader
of Moonshadow Guards.
The demonic elixir Tantai Jin taken
was arranged by me.
Qi Shuang.
I will remember this name.
And you just said
you're really willing to…
I'm willing to die for Your Highness
without hesitation!
Good.
Your Highness, what are you…
Someone, take him away.
Feed him to my pets.
Yes.
No, Your Highness!
Your Highness!
At least I worked hard for you,
-I won't raise a dog biting its master.
-Your Highness!
Wise decision, Your Highness!
Those freshly caught demon creatures
are starving right now.
By the way,
you must raise them properly.
Someday they'll be of great use.
I shall do my best.
Tantai Jin can manipulate demon power.
It is possible for me
to use demon power.
Wise decision, Your Highness!
Commander,
I heard this Tantai Minglang
enjoys torturing people.
Just now, Qi Shuang was dragged out.
He's probably been executed.
His Highness needs some Yiyue girls.
Yes.
All of you, raise your head!
It's your blessing
to be selected by His Highness.
This one and that one. Take them.
Get up!
Come on.
Move!
Come on!
Faster!
Go!
Come on!
Sister.
Baiyu.
You two
go save the other girls.
You go find our weapons.
Go.
Let's go.
We've been running for a night.
Everyone, take some rest.
Go.
Commander,
the priestess betrayed us,
and His Highness was missing.
What should we do?
I have sworn
to serve His Highness with my life.
I'm going to find him.
We'll follow you.
We'll go wherever you go.
Yes!
My brothers!
Sister,
you take them back to Yiyue Tribe first.
Leave the rest to Moonshadow Guards.
I guess there's no other way.
Baiyu,
you must be safe.
Moonshadow Guards, listen!
Yes!
You four
escort the girls back to Yiyue Tribe.
The rest of you,
come with me to find His Highness!
Yes!
I'm freezing.
Tantai Jin,
just wait.
[But where should I go next?]
[Back to Sheng Kingdom?]
[No.]
[Tantai Jin has clearly gone astray.]
[I gotta stop him from becoming a devil.]
[If he goes to Jing Kingdom,]
[I must follow him there.]
[Dear Grandma and Father,
wish you are well.]
[Xiwu is safe.]
[Everything goes well for me.]
[I have enough food and money.]
[Grandma, don't worry about me.]
[Jing Kingdom is a beautiful place.]
[When I finish sightseeing,]
[I'll go back home.]
[From Xiwu.]
Hi, mister.
How long does it take to transport goods
to the capital of Sheng?
Less than three days.
Rest assured. I'll deliver it
personally to your mansion.
Thanks a lot.
My dad will reward you when he gets it.
Little girl,
why are you hanging around all alone?
Why don't you go home?
There's something important
that I must do.
[Another hundred miles along the river,
and then I'll be in Jing Kingdom.]
[The evil bone
is still in Tantai Jin's body.]
[If he degenerates into a devil,]
[or dies accidentally,]
[everything will be in vain.]
[Someone's there.]
Are you alright?
Tantai Jin?
Stop playing dead.
Don't try to fool me.
No matter how poor you look,
I won't fall for it!
Tantai Jin?
He's so cold.
Tantai Jin!
Tantai Jin, wake up!
You can't die.
Tantai Jin, you mustn't die!
Tantai Jin!
Wake up, Tantai Jin!
Karma comes so quickly.
You were alive and kicking
when you tried to capture me.
Only a few hours later,
you're in my hands half-dead.
What are you looking at?
If not for the sake
of my father and my family,
I just wanna slap you to death
and bury you right here.
You'd better move as little as possible.
When pressing water out of you,
I accidentally broke a few of your ribs.
How come it's you?
Why did you save me?
None of your business.
Tantai Jin, I'm telling you.
Now you're in my hands.
I can save you,
and I can also kill you.
If you let yourself die
without my permission,
I'll tear you to pieces
and throw you into the wilderness.
[As expected, I can't see.]
Alright, now it's my turn.
Whether you like it or not,
you must answer my questions honestly.
What questions?
We're just apart for a few hours.
What exactly happened on the ship?
Why have you washed ashore
and lost one eye?
Are you gonna answer or not?
I was ambushed by Tantai Minglang.
Tantai Minglang?
Your elder brother from Jing Kingdom?
Why would he do that?
You should ask him about it.
Fine, next question.
Only you escaped from there?
Where's Jing Lan'an?
Isn't she with you?
She's dead.
Tantai Minglang killed her?
I killed her.
Tantai Jin,
this punch
is for those who died because of you.
This is both for Jing Lan'an and me.
I tried to treat you sincerely,
save and protect you,
but now I really regret it.
Jing Lan'an saved your life.
She brought you up.
You drank her blood
and were taught by her.
But you killed her!
Auntie,
let me ask you.
Do you regret betraying me?
My child,
I don't regret it.
Yeah.
You've gone insane.
You're right.
She brought me up.
She gave me life.
On that new year's Eve,
when she came for me,
I really wished
she didn't abandon me.
What?
Of all the things she did,
she shouldn't have returned after leaving.
She gave me hope
but then discarded me like trash.
What did Jing Lan'an do?
Nothing.
It's just betrayal.
She and Yingxin did the same.
She betrayed me.
[Turns out she let me go]
[in order to kill Tantai Jin.]
[Did she collude with Tantai Minglang?]
Tantai Jin,
I'm gonna escort you
back to Sheng Kingdom.
And then put you in prison
to keep you from the outside world.
I'll be watching you
every second of every day.
As long as I'm alive,
don't ever think
of devouring demonic elixirs
and killing.
What are you laughing at?
Ye Xiwu,
your stupid words
were both strange and funny.
Why don't you just kill me?
Why do you try
to be bound with me forever?
Your life and death
are not up to you now.
What are you doing?
Roasting fish.
Found it!
Here's blood!
Tantai Jin really survived.
He's such a pain in my neck,
just like that witch.
Your Highness,
although Tantai Jin isn't dead,
he's already a spent force.
Please let me tie up this loose end.
Your Highness may return to the capital
and wait for my good news.
No.
I must see Tantai Jin dead
with my own eyes.
Search farther away.
Even if we have to dig three feet deep,
we must find Tantai Jin!
Your Highness,
we'll be entering
the Jing territory ahead.
Still no news about Tantai Jin?
Your Highness,
we have a visual on Jing soldiers.
Are you sure?
From both their clothes and weapons,
they're absolutely from Jing Kingdom.
But we're not sure
why they are here in large numbers.
Lead the way.
Yes.
I didn't expect you
to be helping a little.
You have so many schemes,
but you're a good cook.
I've been doing this since little.
Didn't you grow up in the palace?
You roasted fish in the palace?
Red fish from the Taiye Pond.
Sparrows from the imperial woods.
Rats from the imperial gutters.
All these can be my food.
You just need a few grains of rice.
They'll bite the hook
and get themselves killed.
[This is Tantai Jin.]
[Both pitiable and detestable.]
[Fate has been cruel to him.]
[He also fought back with cruelty.]
[Li Susu, you gotta see clearly.]
[This is the Devil God.]
Eat.
You eat it.
When you finish, we'll hit the road.
We don't have time for you to heal.
It's not poisonous.
I know that.
Otherwise, why would I let you eat it?
Ye Xiwu,
I wonder why you don't wish me to die?
Don't worry.
One day I will tell you.
You'd better pray that day comes later.
[When I destroy the evil bone]
[and kill you,]
[I will tell you.]
What's wrong?
[Without the antidote,]
[I'm probably gonna be dead soon]
[when the poison kicks in.]
Nothing.
Tantai Jin.
We got company.
Hurry!
They haven't gone far. Split up and chase!
Yes!
They can't run far.
Search carefully!
Anyone who captures Tantai Jin
will be rewarded!
Yes!
It's Tantai Minglang's men.
Just hand me over to them.
You can both live and get rewards.
Shut up.
Go in the opposite direction.
Don't get caught.
Ye Xiwu.
Over there! After them!
After them!
Come on!
[Tantai Jin,
I really owe you in my last life.]
[I'm surrounded.]
[No.]
[I haven't found the way
to destroy the evil bone yet.]
[I can't die here.]
Split up.
Yes.
D*mn.
How come it's a woman?
You must have seen Tantai Jin.
Where is he? Say it!
Oh, that dead guy is called Tantai Jin?
He's dead.
Dead?
Then why were you running?
I stole something from him.
I thought you were here to catch me.
For a d*mn woman like you,
I chased half a day for nothing!
Go hell!
This way! After her!
Don't let her get away!
Be quiet.
All of you split up and go search.
Yes!
Didn't I tell you to run
in the opposite direction?
Wanna get killed?
I'm worried that if you get caught,
you'll sell me out.
Now it's perfect. Neither of us gets away.
What's that noise?
Go now!
If you tell me honestly
why you came here,
I'll spare your lives.
We're here
to hunt down Tantai Jin.
By whose order?
Is it Tantai Minglang? Where is he?
His…
They're all dead.
Your Highness,
since they're here for Tantai Jin,
he should be around here.
Please give orders to Dragon Guards to…
Go back.
Your Highness.
Tantai Jin is…
Get on the horse.
Take these bodies back to the city.
No one saw Tantai Jin today.
Understand?
Understand!
[Tantai Jin,]
[this is as far as I can get you.]
This place is concealed enough.
Let's spend the night here.
Why didn't you leave just now?
Why did you distract the soldiers
and save me?
That's just because…
Better to talk about it till we're safe.
No soldiers are chasing us for now.
Give me back my charms.
If we run into them again,
at least I have something to defend us.
You drew so many sketches?
You only taught me this type.
These are useless
for the current situation.
And they were soaked
in water for too long.
There's no magic on them.
Meeting you is the unluckiest thing.
Tantai Jin,
why is your blood black?
What exactly happened to you?
[Once the poison in your left eye]
diffuses to the rest of your meridians,
you'll be dead
after spitting blood three times.
What's going on? Just tell me!
I was poisoned by Tantai Minglang.
Maybe later, I'll be dead.
You prick!
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
Would it help if I did?
Are you a doctor?
Do you have the antidote?
There must be a way to save you.
Wait here. I'll be back soon.
Ye Xiwu!
Where are you going?
Report!
The men we sent out to search
haven't found Tantai Jin yet.
Useless!
Your Highness,
urgent news from the capital.
Something happened in the palace.
They need you to handle it.
Please return to the capital first.
I'll take care of it.
Fine.
I've been out for too long this time.
My third brother,
when I find you,
I'll crush the bones of you
and Yue Ruanruan into powder.
I'll make you disappear for good.
Go.
Tantai Jin,
you can't hide much longer.
You must be eliminated.
You're awake.
You're back.
Of course.
You think I'll leave you alone here?
You're badly injured
and slept for hours.
I gave you some simple treatment.
Have some fruit first.
You're in luck.
I picked some herbs back.
They can stop the poison from spreading.
I'll apply them on you in a sec.
Well.
You should not try
to run around out there.
You got so many injuries and almost died.
You really scared me.
I must owe you in my previous life.
Ye Xiwu,
you don't need to try so hard to save me.
You gotta live on.
Are you injured somewhere else too?
Come on.
What are you doing?
You still mind this when you're dying?
What's more,
we're already married.
Nothing to be shy about.
Ye Xiwu,
you said it on the ship.
From now on,
we will have nothing
to do with each other.
When we get out of here,
I will settle scores with you properly.
But now your life is in my hands.
I will decide whether you live or not.
Understand,
Tantai Jin?
Okay.
What is this?
Give it back!
It looks like some kind of treasure.
Why haven't I seen it before?
I found it on the road.
I don't know what it is, either.
Probably worthless.
Give it back to me.
Since you found it,
technically, it's not yours.
Since it's in my hand,
it's mine now.
No! You can't hold it.
Ye Xiwu, be honest with me.
What exactly is this?
It's a lost divine artifac from ancient times.
It's called World-alluring Jade.
World-alluring Jade?
You'd better not
have any funny ideas about it!
This Jade was forged by a witch
ten thousand years ago.
[She killed tens of thousands
of immortals,]
[and withdrew their immortal bones.]
[Making this Jade was an evil deed.]
That's why its users
were doomed to end badly.
They'll be short-lived and die violently.
Bad endings… Violent death?
Guess you are thinking if you devour it,
it'll be more useful
than devouring elixirs?
You'd better give up this idea,
or you'll die a horrible death.
I'm already deeply poisoned.
The poison might kick in any second.
I can't even keep my life now.
Why would I be afraid of death?
Why would I be afraid of some curse?
There's no difference
for me
whether to die now or later.
I won't let you die here.
Time to change your medicine.
Don't move, okay?
Otherwise, I might break some more ribs.
Done. Time to sleep.
I'll take you to Sheng Kingdom
tomorrow morning.
There must be a way to save you.
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up♪
♪And suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers♪
♪Covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly♪
[You saved me because of love?]
[What is love exactly?]
[Love is you don't want him to die.]
[You wanna stay with him.]
[You'll be worried if you don't see him.]
[You'll be happy if you do.]
♪Blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
Almost there.
When we go through the woods ahead,
we'll find somewhere to rest.
Tantai Jin,
you're really not fully dead.
Seems like you also made up with Miss Xiwu.
Who's this?
Tantai Minglang's subordinate.
She's able to use demonic hex.
Be careful.
[Tantai Jin is too weak to take any risk.]
[If he dies,]
[everything will be in vain.]
Tantai Jin,
her target is you.
Find a good chance to run first.
I'll think of a way to stall her.
What?
So deeply poisoned
that you can't use any hex?
Seeing me
means you two lovebirds' tragic ending
has come.
What are you going to fight her with?
Just leave it to me.
Shatter!
Tantai Jin!
Are you okay?
Tantai Jin,
you can even kill Jing Lan'an
who brought you up,
but care so much about this woman?
You're dying anyway.
I'll catch you back alive
for His Highness to vent his hatred.
Ye Xiwu.
Ye Xiwu!
She was hit by my Heart-gnawing Spell.
She'll be dead in no time.
Undo this spell right now!
Or I'm gonna smash you to ashes!
You can barely keep standing.
How can you afford to save her?
You might as well just surrender.
[Ye Xiwu,]
[we have a lot of unfinished scores
to settle.]
[I can't just let you die here.]
The World-alluring Jade.
[This Jade was forged by a witch
ten thousand years ago.]
[Its users were doomed to end badly.]
[They'll be short-lived
and die violently.]
[As long as I can live now,]
[why should I fear death afterward?]
You demon.
I'll eliminate you for His Highness
to spare all later trouble!
Tantai Minglang can't kill me.
One day, I'll go to him!
Ye Xiwu!
[What happened to me?]
[Tantai Jin saved me?]
Tantai Jin!
This glow?
It's the World-alluring Jade!
You j*rk!
You devoured the World-alluring Jade!
You'll die violently! Don't you know?
[Chongyu Harp, help me.]
[I must take the Jade out.]
Get out!
[Do you want to save this man]
[who tried
to possess the World-alluring Jade?]
Who are you?
You're the witch who forged this Jade?
Do you want to save this man?
I have to save him. He can't die!
But the World-alluring Jade
has chosen him.
Misfortune will fall upon him very soon.
He will have a violent death
in a foreign land.
No!
I'll help him get the Jade out.
Whatever method I must use!
Well, there is one.
[But is this man worth it?]
[Take a good look]
[at what kind of person he is.]
You are a monster.
[Whoever gets near you will be doomed.]
[Look,]
[this kind of person…]
You've never ever deserved
to have the most normal human emotions.
[isn't worth your sacrifice.]
If someone has to die,
I'm sure anyone will choose you.
That's not true!
[He can't die.]
[If there must be someone
to carry his curse,]
let it be me!
[But before the curse lands upon me,]
[there's one task I must complete.]
Do you know how to destroy the evil bone?
I know what you are after.
Maybe you can find the answer
in Barren Abyss.
[But now the power
of the World-alluring Jade]
[has condensed into his eye.]
[If you want to take it back,]
[you have to trade it
with one of your eyes.]
Fine.
I'll do it.
How ridiculous.
In this world,
[someone's actually willing
to die for others.]
Tantai Jin,
you won't die.
Only if you're alive,
more people will be able to live.
You two, go check over there!
[It's Nian Baiyu.]
Your Highness!
He's still breathing.
[They're indeed Moonshadow Guards.]
[Seems like they won't hurt him.]
Someone!
Take His Highness
to the camp for treatment!
Yes!
[I couldn't go to Barren Abyss]
[with Tantai Jin heavily sick.]
[I can only leave
Little Devil God to you.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[when I found the way
to destroy the evil bone,]
[I'll be back for you.]
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪