♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 10]
Lin,
this time,
you checked the national treasury
and warned the local tycoons.
Well done.
You didn't let me down.
But I still let Tantai Jin get away.
Since you're already back,
I'll have Ye Xiao released.
Thanks for your generosity, Father.
The Ye family lost Tantai Jin,
but whoever the new King of the Jing is,
with the Ye's reputation in the army,
they can still be useful to me.
Dad,
His Majesty has given orders
to let me return to Jia Pass immediately.
We couldn't find Tantai Jin,
but His Majesty still let me go.
Qingyu,
this is not as simple as it seems.
I understand.
The rabbit hasn't been caught.
How can you kill the hound first?
Let's not talk about this.
Where's your grandma?
I didn't dare tell her
what happened to you.
I just said you went out
on a business trip.
You did right.
Let's go home.
Lords, please hold on.
I ran into a young lady in the north.
She asked me to give this family letter
to the Ye family in the capital.
[Capital of the Sheng]
Thanks a lot!
That's my Xiwu. I told you!
She'll definitely be safe.
She's fine, thank god.
God bless.
Thank goodness, our buttercup is fine.
[I've only read in
Geography of Four Continents]
[about the rough direction
of Barren Abyss.]
[But I don't know where the entrance is.]
[When can I finally get there?]
[Why do I feel familiar with this smell?]
Fox Spirit!
Small world, huh?
You're a powerful spirit with seven tails.
How come you look so weak now?
This is all thanks to you!
Tantai Jin's blood
is truly something else.
My vitality was badly damaged.
I couldn't recover for days.
It's your own fault anyway.
You tried to
get my younger brother's spirit.
[But after all,]
[this is a crime
committed by Little Devil God.]
[If World-alluring Jade
can undo my spell,]
[it should be able to cure her, too.]
Alright, I'll treat your injury.
Your hex is not bad.
Thanks.
I've never suffered like this
since I got out of Barren Abyss.
You came from Barren Abyss?
What's the fuss about?
My parents are both mighty demons
who followed the Devil God.
Naturally, I was born in the abyss.
But hasn't the abyss been sealed?
How did you get out?
I remember when I was little,
the barrier of Barren Abyss
was indeed something impenetrable.
But the power of the guardian has faded
after being there for ten thousand years.
Many demons seized the chance to get out.
I've always longed for the outside world.
So I took my chance
and here I am.
Who's the guardian of Barren Abyss?
I haven't seen him.
Seems to be called Ji Ze.
[Ji Ze, the God of Cosmos,
rules the time itself.]
[The Mirror of the Past]
was transformed from Ji Ze's divine eye.
His power can travel through time.
If we use this array to return to the past
and kill Tantai Jin
before he became the devil,
we'll be able to stop the destined arrival
of the Devil God.
[All gods]
[should have long fallen]
[in the battle of god and devil.]
[He's actually in Barren Abyss?]
[No wonder the witch told me]
[I could find the answer there.]
Why are you so excited?
Do you know where Barren Abyss is?
Why should I tell you?
Why are you like this?
I just helped you.
Aren't demons
said to be the most grateful?
I won't need you to marry me.
If you just help lead the way,
we'll be even. Sounds fair?
Alright then.
I'll be kind for once
to lead the way for you.
Thanks, little fox spirit.
Let's go.
Who are you calling a little fox spirit?
Sister Fox.
Good girl.
That way.
[Tantai Jin,]
[you must stay alive.]
[Wait for me to come back.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[you're so useless!]
[No need to agitate me.]
[Wait.]
Am I dead?
Where's Ye Xiwu?
[You're not dead.]
[You're just abandoned once again.]
What exactly do you mean?
Where on earth is Ye Xiwu?
[You're pathetic.]
[She already abandoned you.]
[You're still thinking about her.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[how does it feel to be abandoned
over and over again?]
[Who did this to you?]
[Don't you wanna revenge yourself on them?]
[Your enemies are]
[all over the Jing palace.]
[You are abandoned and hurt,]
[but they are unharmed]
[and live in luxury.]
They do deserve to die.
But there's nothing I can do.
[Nothing you can do?]
[You were just
accepting everything passively]
[from the beginning to the end.]
[Over the last twenty years,]
[have you ever asked yourself,
what your inner desires are?]
[Inner desires?]
[All your miseries and sufferings]
[were just helping you]
[to walk toward your destiny.]
[Why can't you be the Emperor Jing?]
[Why can't it be you
to tread them underfoot?]
[Haven't you ever thought]
[the throne of Jing belongs to you?]
[Fate has never wanted you]
[to live in this shabby house.]
[It will not leave you
alone in the darkness.]
[Can't you see]
[where your fate should belong?]
[Rather than live on in degradation,]
[why not put up a fight?]
[All your enemies
who should've be skinned by you]
[and that highest throne…]
[Think about it.]
[What is it that you should do
and that you deserve to own?]
What's wrong with your eye?
Nothing.
Just a little dust.
Hey, Little Fox.
I told you several times,
call me sister.
Sister Fox,
we've been out for days.
If we keep hanging around like this,
when can we get to Barren Abyss?
What's the hurry?
I'm badly injured. I need to rest.
When you were
flirting with someone just now,
your complexion looked great.
For the sake of our friendship,
here's a piece of advice.
You'd better not absorb mortals' vitality
to improve your cultivation.
When you become a demonic cultivator,
you'll eventually
be struck dead by lightning.
I didn't do that for my cultivation.
I simply thought those men were funny.
They can't take a little flirting.
Funny?
Is that how you think of
my second brother?
But I think he's serious about you.
Playing with people's emotions seems fun,
but what if they take it seriously,
or you take it seriously?
Love is something
that often goes out of control.
Little girl,
do you know what love threads are?
All intelligent beings have love threads.
Only with love threads
can you love someone.
But my love threads are lost.
Without them,
I can no longer love anyone.
How did you lose your love threads?
Why would I tell you?
How long exactly
can we get to Barren Abyss?
Going in
or getting out of the abyss isn't easy.
I used to be a nine-tailed fox spirit.
I cut off two tails to get out.
I had to abandon
thousands of years of cultivation.
It's so difficult, even for a demon.
Much less a mere mortal like you.
Even if you get there, you'll die in vain.
Why must you go there?
I'll go even if it may kill me.
Maybe only in there
can I find the way to save them.
Who are you saving?
A lot.
Quite a lot of people.
You won't necessarily save them
even if you made it there.
You could probably
lose your life for nothing.
Do think twice.
If I could save them all,
my life would mean nothing.
Either by your help
or any other way,
I must be there.
Fine.
I wanted to
stop you
because you saved my life,
but since you're so stubborn,
let's hit the road when the day breaks.
[Capital of Jing]
[Memorial tablet of Queen
of the Great Jing]
Mother,
you gave up your life for father.
But I won't do the same.
Those who laughed at me and insulted me,
I've killed every last one of them.
[Memorial tablet of Queen
of the Great Jing]
[Memorial tablet of Queen of the Great Jing]
Mother, you should be happy for me.
Your son has become the Emperor Jing!
No one in this kingdom
can hurt me anymore.
Everybody respects and fears me.
Guards!
[All you big rats,]
[don't eat my millet.]
[Go drink the king's blood,]
[and eat the king's flesh.]
[All you big rats,]
[don't eat my millet.]
[Go drink the king's blood,]
[and eat the king's flesh.]
All you big rats,
don't eat my millet.
[Go drink the king's blood,]
[and eat the king's flesh.]
[All you big rats,]
[don't eat my millet.]
[Go drink the king's blood,]
and eat the king's flesh.
What nonsense are you singing about?
Where did you learn that?
Go home!
[Justice Will Prevail]
[This is the payback for tyranny.]
[A cruel monarch has lost his territory.]
[His lack of virtue has angered gods.]
[Hence the punishments.]
It's you!
These are your demonic hexes!
It's me.
I told you,
from that day on,
you'll never have a day of peace.
[But a king's consequences of misconducts]
[are often suffered by his people.]
[Oh, how sad!]
Sir,
is there a way
to end this heavenly punishment?
Tantai Jin!
I will haunt you even when I'm dead!
One day,
I'll crush you
and that demon woman into dust!
Tantai Minglang,
your soul dies with your body.
Just rest in peace.
This symbol represents a hidden dragon.
The kingdom will be saved from the crisis
if the new King ascends the throne.
[Capital of Jing]
[But the Tantais
have no male descendants.]
[Who else can inherit the throne?]
[Fortune doesn't lie.]
[Maybe in a few days,]
[that chosen one will appear.]
[So this is our new king?]
[Have you heard?]
[This morning,
thousands of snakes and rats]
[went out of the city gates]
[without hurting anyone.]
[Does he really have some magic power?]
[Don't you know it yet?]
[Everybody's talking about it!]
[This new king]
[is the late King's
youngest and favorite son.]
[He's also the son
of the Princess of Yiyue tribe.]
[It's just that
he's been a hostage in the Sheng,]
[exchanging peace for us
with his very life!]
[What great contributions to the country!]
[The chosen one.]
[The new King inherits the throne.]
[Please enter the sacred hall]
[and listen to the sacred order]
[from heaven.]
[The ancestors in this ancient relic
have once again blessed us]
[by sending us a saint from above.]
[He shall end tyranny
and relieve disasters.]
[Now the tyrant is dead.
The new King shall rule.]
[May this wise King benefit us on and on!]
[May this diligent King shine on and on!]
[Jing Kingdom,]
[I have returned after all.]
You killed your mother
the moment you were born.
You left the capital at six.
Now you're back for no reason at all.
You don't deserve to be our king!
You don't deserve it!
You're the son of a demonic Yiyue woman
who could control demon creatures.
Now you're back to the Jing.
You must have an evil plan!
-That's right!
-Yeah.
Evil plan!
If we surrender to you,
how will the history books describe us?
-Yeah!
-Exactly!
How will the history books write about us?
Answer us!
Have you said enough?
Kill us if you want!
Even if we die here today,
we won't take you as our new king!
-Yeah!
-That's right!
You're not our new king!
-Kill us!
-Yeah!
Come on!
Just kill us!
-Kill me!
-Come kill us!
Come on, kill us!
Ministers,
please calm down.
What should I kill you for?
Serve it.
Could it be some demonic creature?
This is…
Soup?
Are we having dinner?
After talking for quite a while,
you must be hungry.
I specially prepared dinner for you.
Let's talk while dining.
Guards.
Treat them properly for me.
Yes.
Is this even the time to have soup?
All of you are so loyal to the late king.
I'm so touched.
Certainly I should treat you
to the best cuisine.
Make sure you drink it all in one gulp,
so as not to let
my admiration for you go in vain.
Why are you not eating?
Does my food not suit your taste?
I have to admit that
the meat soup
from Yiyue Tribe tastes great!
This…
This soup could be poisonous!
Poisonous!
You!
You're so wicked!
What now?
Spit it out!
I'm not into the idea of poisoning.
Your old king is already dead.
You're all patriotic ministers.
I returned as the new King timely
to save the people
of the Jing from disasters.
Shouldn't you all be delighted about it?
Guards.
Another bowl
for those who haven't had enough.
Whoever willing to
share this soup with me,
I will treat you well.
I won't force you to stay
if you still don't change your mind.
I'll grant your wish
to be the tomb keepers
of the late king until you think
you've missed him enough.
What should we do?
Forget it.
He's the only Tantai left.
The kingdom cannot be without a king.
Everyone,
are you satisfied with my treatment today?
I'm satisfied.
I'm willing to share this soup with you.
Thanks, Your Majesty!
Escort my ministers back to rest.
Yes.
Thanks, Your Majesty!
Let's go, come on.
Tantai Minglang is dead.
The new King of the Jing
is Tantai Jin?
Tantai Jin
has been a hostage here for years.
A helpless prince like him
inherited the throne
just days after returning?
What a big joke!
This shows the end of the Jing is near.
Now he hasn't established his authority.
This is
our perfect chance to attack Jing.
War spends blood and treasure.
Yeah.
There's a flood in the south.
People are starving.
We haven't had disaster relief food yet.
Our national treasury is empty.
Father,
I think we'd better not go to war.
We just fought
for three months in Jia Pass.
Now our soldiers are tired.
Our provisions are running low.
Building up strength is the better choice.
Also, if he can seize
the throne as a hostage prince,
he's probably capable of more.
We can't underestimate Tantai Jin.
Yes, Prince Lin's words make sense.
Back then, when General Ye
crushed Jing Kingdom,
and we took Tantai Jin our hostage.
So that the Jing bowed it head to us.
Now the Jing made him their King,
isn't it god's will for us
to defeat them again?
Only if I cut off Tantai Jin's head,
will I not fail god's good plan.
Father, please think again.
What?
Do you doubt my judgment?
Then why don't you replace me now
and sit upon my throne?
I dare not.
No more discussion.
I've decided.
Pass down my order:
Send troops to Jing Kingdom!
Yes, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
[Chenming Hall]
Tantai Minglang's remnants are still out there.
Now Sheng Kingdom is invading our borders.
They're trying to destroy us
while you have
less control over the country.
Yes.
Your Majesty just came to power,
your ministers still have concerns
and your people still have doubts.
This is when we're the weakest.
That's right.
The Sheng is known for their strong troops
and battle-wise generals.
We can hardly
have the upper hand against them.
Why don't we retreat first
to a natural barrier
that's easy to defend?
This is the best strategy.
Minister Zhang's right!
He's absolutely right!
[Jing Kingdom is my homeland.]
[It's also where my mother's tribe lives.]
[This throne decides my fate.]
[As long as Jing Kingdom
thrive under my rule,]
[no doubt that
my power will be unparalleled.]
[And I can say goodbye to the fate of]
[slavishly dependent on others for good.]
I understand.
Your Majesty,
then where should we retreat to?
Now our kingdom is so weak.
How much territory can we defend?
Yeah.
If it's the late King,
we'd be retreating to the capital.
Retreating
isn't a good strategy.
Now the Emperor Sheng started this war.
Let's fight him with everything we got.
I will personally go lead on the borders.
This is not for defending our land,
nor for taking cities southward.
What I want is to take him by surprise
and defeat him with one blow.
Please reconsider!
We've arrived.
Farther ahead
is the barrier of Barren Abyss.
I don't wanna get near it.
Thanks for walking me here.
Alright,
I've done what I promised you.
It's up to you whether you can get in.
We'll go separate ways from here.
Sister Fox,
thank you.
You can thank me
after you get out of there alive.
[I finally made it here.]
[Li Susu,]
[if you see the God of Cosmos,]
[you may be able to save
the Four Continents and Three Realms.]
Report!
Your Majesty,
as for what you've ordered previously,
the scouts have returned.
What have they found?
They haven't found the girl
you described along the road.
But farther south
will be the territory of Sheng Kingdom.
Keep searching.
She must be found, dead or alive.
How are we doing on the frontline?
Ye Xiao is quite valiant.
Their morale is high.
We have been defeated.
Call all generals here for a meeting.
Yes.
[Ye Xiao's elite soldiers
are good at fight.]
[If I can use a Firewing Army
consisting of demon creatures,]
[I may be able
to fight against heavy odds]
[and reduce casualties at the same time.]
[Ye Xiwu,]
[you'd better not die.]
[Wait for me to catch you back.]
[This is the Barren Abyss Barrier.]
[With my mortal body now,]
[I'm afraid
I can't take the barrier's power.]
[Oh right.]
[Maybe I can try to]
[control Chongyu with the power of]
[World-alluring Jade.]
Chongyu.
I can only take my chances.
[This feels exactly
like in the time array.]
[Susu.]
Who are you?
Come to me.
Why do you know my name?
[Why is there a child here?]
Get away!
She's mine!
[They're too close to the child.]
[Using a charm
may hurt the child as well.]
Get away!
Another human!
We're so lucky today.
Come on, catch me if you can!
After her!
Go now!
[Li Susu.]
[This voice sounds like]
[that immortal lord
in the Mirror of the Past.]
Greetings, Senior.
Li Susu,
we meet again.
Are you waiting for me to come?
I am Ji Ze, the God of Cosmos.
The Light-breaking Array
and the Mirror of the Past
were both left by me.
I stayed here and held on
for ten thousand years.
Just to wait for your arrival.
I've found that person with evil origin.
But I still can't find a way
to destroy the evil bone.
Please enlighten me.
I can tell you how.
To destroy the evil bone,
you'll need three keys
to unlock the rules of karma,
stop what is destined to happen
and change everything.
What keys?
A dream.
A teardrop.
And a thread.
What dream?
This dream should be coming soon.
The teardrop is the first drop of tear
the Devil God shed for love.
It's called Soul-slaying Teardrop.
And what does "a thread" refer to?
The thread is connected to the teardrop.
If you can open Devil God's heart gate,
the Soul-slaying teardrop
will turn into nine spikes.
When you stab them into his heart,
you'll be able to destroy the evil bone.
But I'm barehanded.
I can only try my best.
I know it's difficult too.
Sorry for putting you through this.
The time has come.
I'm about to fall.
Senior!
After I fall,
the Barren Abyss Barrier
can still hold for 300 days.
Within 300 days,
if you can't destroy the evil bone,
demons will be out of Barren Abyss.
Everything will be irrecoverable.
I understand.
I
can finally join my fellows.
The Mirror of the Past.
[The Mirror of the Past]
[was transformed from Ji Ze's divine eye.]
So he waited here
just for this.
[A dream, a teardrop,]
[and a thread.]
Luckily, protected by the divine power,
The foul energy didn't invade her deep.
Little girl.
You're awake.
Come.
[Could she be Jing Lan'an's daughter?]
Who… who are you?
I'm Ye Xiwu.
Just now
I ran into you down the cliff.
How are you feeling?
I remember I fell into a
hole that's very, very deep.
How did I get out?
Do you still remember who took you here?
It's a man with scars on his face.
He's quite mean.
Come.
[Scars on the face?]
[Should be Tantai Minglang.]
Come, let's go down the mountain first.
Little girl,
what's your name?
My name is Yue Fuya.
I'll take you downhill first.
Then we'll see what to do, alright?
Let's go.
Why is it suddenly so hot?
[I entered Barren Abyss in winter.]
[Why do the grasses
turn green so quickly?]
Hi, mister.
Could you tell me
what month it is now?
What month?
It's already April.
Miss,
how come you forgot which month you're in?
We went into the mountain to pick herbs
but were lost in the woods.
We spent quite some time there.
Miss,
you'd better not pick any herbs.
Just go home as soon as possible.
The world is in chaos now.
What happened?
Haven't you heard?
Since the new king ascended throne,
Sheng and Jing have been at war
for three or four months.
The new Emperor Jing?
Who is he?
I heard it's
the youngest son of the old king.
The one back from Sheng Kingdom.
[Tantai Jin.]
[He fought on the battlefield personally]
[by commanding demon creatures.]
[The Sheng army
suffered defeats one after another.]
[Their casualties are heavy.]
Welcome back, Your Majesty!
I heard General Ye fell off his horse
and still hasn't woken up.
Now General Ye's son is leading the army
[to defend the Jia Pass.]
[Jia Pass]
[Dad is on the brink of death.]
[Qingyu is also in a dangerous place.]
[Tantai Jin actually
became the Emperor Jing.]
Your Majesty,
none of the scouts sent out recently
have found the whereabouts of Miss Xiwu.
According to the prisons from the Sheng,
Miss Xiwu hasn't returned to the Sheng.
She's vanished.
It's my fault
for failing to finish the job.
Keep searching.
Leave no stones unturned.
Yes.
Baiyu,
how are we doing in Jia Pass?
I heard their provisions are running low.
Your Majesty,
according to spies,
the Emperor Sheng is prone to suspicion.
He's not satisfied
with Ye Xiao being injured.
This time, Ye Qingyu is only allowed
to attack and charge.
Their soldier's pay and provisions
are barely enough.
Deputy Liu,
how many provisions do we have?
We can't sustain three days, General.
The Jing invaders attack us every day.
We are running out of
provisions and medicine
very quickly.
A lot of our brothers
can't hold much longer.
[Your father lost three cities
and disgraced us all.]
[Too many provisions have been used.]
[Now the national treasury is empty.]
[You're responsible
for your own provisions.]
[If you lose the Jia Pass,]
[I shall execute your whole clan.]
give out the food to our men.
I'll think of a way tomorrow.
Yes.
Ye Qingyu is just
struggling to fight.
The foolish Emperor Sheng
actually has such a good general
to lead the army.
Have you hunted
any powerful demon creatures?
I heard there's a Heptatail Fox
in the nearby mountains.
I've sent hands to hunt.
But now we haven't got it yet.
Sorry to disappoint you.
[Seem like an acquaintance.]
It's fine.
I'll go personally.
How can you
catch me with these stupid tricks?
Oh no, she's getting away!
What a surprise
for today's demon hunt.
What a coincidence
to meet you again.
Move, and I'll cut off your tail.
Tantai Jin,
where's Ye Xiwu
who used to be with you?
You've seen her?
So you care for her.
I don't know where she went.
That's why I asked you.
I don't feel like killing you today.
You may be of some other use.
This is a secret drug of Yiyue tribe.
Eat it.
Be loyal to me. Work for me.
And you'll be safe.
But if you ever betray me,
you will endure the pain
of getting bitten by thousands of bugs.
Then you will explode and die.
So?
Are you gonna eat it
or…
Am I going to have another fox-fur robe?
Hold on.
I'll do it.
General,
there's a woman outside
who wants to see you.
She said she's your old friend.
Let her in.
Pian Ran?
Pian Ran.
It's been a long time.
I thought you already forgot me.
I thought back then you were already…
Why are you here?
You should go.
Tantai Jin
is hunting demon creatures outside.
Be careful not to get caught.
It's too late.
By order of the Emperor Jing,
I'm here to ask you to surrender.
Just go.
I knew it would be like this.
Don't drive me away so fast.
Take this as catching up with me.
Jia Pass needs provisions urgently.
We can only sustain three days.
Please allocate provisions to us.
I shall do everything I can
to defend Jia Pass.
How many of these letters have you sent?
Has any provision come?
Emperor Sheng is such a shrewd person.
He wants you to fight without food.
Or shall I say,
he doesn't care about your lives at all?
He only cares
if this city is his or not.
Do you know how many
Firewing Army does Tantai Jin have?
Before I got out of there,
he gave his men an order.
If Jia Pass can't be conquered,
he'll lead the Firewing Army
and fight by himself.
By then,
how many people will die?
In this case,
go persuade Tantai Jin to kill less!
It's only because he didn't start the war
that I came to persuade you.
Ye Qingyu,
will there be peace
if Tantai Jin stops killing?
How naive of you.
This war was started by Emperor Sheng
simply because he's angry
to see the hostage prince
who once begged for his mercy
can now become a king.
You're not a foolish one.
You also know
your entire army
will perish with you if this goes on.
Emperor Sheng is too stupid
to even see this.
Instead of working for a stupid king,
why don't you follow a wise one
to keep your soldiers alive?
My family is the guardian of Sheng.
If I surrender,
how can I face my ancestors?
Ye Qingyu,
do you actually think
your reputation
is more important than the lives
of thousands of soldiers?
Enough talking.
Leave!
I'm just a fox.
How can I understand state affairs?
Tantai Jin is willing
to see you alone tomorrow.
If you really don't want to surrender,
[Stone carving, Mount Mituo, at 07:45.]
just kill him to end the war.
It's a great opportunity.
You actually came. One man, one sword.
You have some courage.
You're wrong about it.
I didn't carry a sword.
Just a few days apart,
you have become a king.
That's impressive.
The last time I saw you,
you were still as lively as a tiger.
Just a few days later,
you looked worn out.
If I kill you now,
or take you back alive,
my family will have
another military merit.
Then go ahead and try.
See if you'll get a promotion
or if your king will dread you
for being a threat to his throne.
That's irrelevant for now.
If I kill you today,
I would be killing
a malicious man for the world!
Ye Qingyu,
I've been a hostage in the Sheng for years.
We both know how paranoid
Emperor Sheng is.
The Ye family
is on the brink of destruction.
Be it punishment or reward,
I'll thank my king.
Our Ye family is and will be Sheng people.
I won't be incited
by a few words from you.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪