The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 38]
[Mo Nv.]
[You're here to take revenge for your sister.]
[You're a demon]
[while now I'm a Devil God.]
[With your pathetic skills,]
[how dare you challenge me?]
[How about you submit to me]
[as your sister did?]
[Then, you two can reunite.]
[Si Ying.]
[I'm coming to keep you company.]
Shatter!
Miss, run!
Another one to be sacrificed.
All of you, come and submit to me
and the All-in-Distress Way.
You should feel honored.
I can't believe he's devouring
demons' powers of the whole Barren Abyss.
The All-in-Distress Way.
What's that?
It's the All-in-Distress Way.
Tantai Jin has opened the All-in-Distress Way.
[It's the All-in-Distress Way.]
[How come?]
Look
at the sky!
-What's that?
-I have no idea.
What's that?
I don't know.
Look!
What's that?
Gosh!
The All-in-Distress Way is opened.
The All-in-Distress Way. What to do?
What to do?
Since the All-in-Distress Way is opened,
the disciples of the Chixiao Sect,
stop searching
and return to the sect with me right away
to build a barrier
and preserve your capabilities.
Go.
Hurry up and go back to open
the Sect Protecting Formation.
Yes.
The All-in-Distress Way is opened,
so there are no safe places in the world.
Exactly. You have somewhere to hide.
What about the others?
Di Mian, stop!
Who also has a death wish?
[Di Mian has been completely
controlled by the Devil God.]
[He stopped at nothing
to open the the All-in-Distress Way.]
[I must first think of ways to awaken Di Mian.]
Run!
Hurry up!
Everyone,
Now the Devil God has come back to life
and the All-in-Distress Way been opened.
The Four Continents are doomed to be destroyed.
Whether we fight or not, we'll die.
Any one of you will
enter the Barren Abyss with me
and fight with the Devil God to the death?
I will go with you.
I will.
I will too.
We will.
I will fight with the Devil God to the death.
I will also go with you.
Tantai Jin is cunning.
Now he's become the Devil God.
He's dangerous.
Once you find any trace of Tantai Jin,
immediately write to your fellows for support.
We'll work together to kill him.
You must never act rashly
or be fooled by him.
[Devil God.]
[You failed to destroy my disciple.]
[Now you're controlling Di Mian]
[to open the All-in-Distress Way.]
[Before you become stronger,]
[I'll now wipe out your cave!]
Di Mian.
Stop him!
You want to destroy the All-in-Distress Way.
I'll let you be buried with it, then.
[What happened?]
[Just now, I was controlled by the Devil God.]
[The Devil God has disappeared.]
[And the devil energy backfired on me.]
The All-in-Distress Way is actually opened.
How lucky I am!
It's been ten thousand years.
At last it's my turn!
I'll become the new Devil God.
[How come the power
of the All-in-Distress Way is so weak?]
[The All-in-Distress Way opened
by the Devil God ten thousand years ago]
[wasn't like this.]
[Could it be
that there is not enough resentment?]
[Resentment.]
[I need to collect more sadness and resentment.]
[Sure enough, without the Devil God connected]
[to the All-in-Distress Way,
it can't unleash its biggest power]
[I see.]
[It turns out
that the chance of all these things]
[are like this.]
[Zhaoyou.]
[You can't possibly escape!]
[Since the All-in-Distress Way is opened,]
[no one can close it.]
[When I collect enough resentment]
[and continue to stimulate
the All-in-Distress Way,]
[I'll rule the Four Continents
and Three Realms.]
Mo Nv.
You…
What are you doing here?
The Devil God has come back to life.
It's quite dangerous here.
Leave now.
[I've finally found it.]
[This place should be the center
of the the All-in-Distress Way.]
[I'm meant to stop the Devil God
from being alive again.]
[Now the All-in-Distress Way is opened.]
[No matter who the Devil God inside is,]
[I must fight with him to the death.]
[Mother.]
[Father.]
[You must protect me.]
Susu,
I'm so happy you are here.
Thanks to you, my father,
I did not lose my life.
Susu,
whether you believe me or not,
whether you hate me or not,
I had my difficulties.
Apart from sealing the evil bone,
I have never deceived you
or intended to harm your life.
Then I'll have to thank you.
It's great now.
The All-in-Distress Way has started,
and now I own the power of the Devil God.
As long as enough sorrow, grief,
resentment and hatred are sacrificed,
I can become
the one and only God in the world.
Susu,
your father is the master of the world,
and you are my most beloved daughter.
That's exactly
what I've been hoping for.
You are doing a stupid thing.
I have done a more stupid thing,
which is trusting you,
and because of that, my dad died.
I am your real father.
I gave you life!
Then I will give you my life back!
Let's die together today!
You dared to attack
your own biological father for an outsider.
Shut up!
Father went all over
the four continents to find me,
gave me life,
raised me to adulthood,
taught me to know right from wrong
and love all people.
His whole heart is devoted to me,
risking his life to protect my life.
In this life and this world,
I have only this one father.
And you,
you are only
the enemy that killed my father.
You and your mother
are truly of the same temper,
straightforward and stubborn.
Then she must
regret that she didn't kill you back then.
For ten thousand years,
I have endured endless
humiliation and suffering,
and finally I succeed today.
Not only do you not know
to congratulate me,
but you are also so rebellious.
I am too sad
and too disappointed.
Di Mian,
you are so pathetic.
In that case,
I have no choice but to
put you out of your misery.
Your sorrow, grief, resentment, and hatred
will be sacrificed to All-in-Distress Way.
In this way, you have repaid me
for the grace of your birth.
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Argue and refute♪
Tantai Jin,
you are still alive.
That's awesome.
Tantai Jin,
as the devil fetus,
you actually gave away the evil bone.
After I kill you,
I will be the one and only Devil God.
Die!
♪In the void of life shared with you♪
Tantai Jin!
♪Craving your pearl between your brows,
your armor of scales♪
♪Putting away armor and falling together♪
♪If only I could start over with you♪
♪Just like when we first met, how would it be?♪
♪In each other's dreams♪
♪As the moon shines its light♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
How is that possible?
Tantai Jin…
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
How are you worthy of
using the Sky-Slashing Sword?
My Sky-Slashing Sword!
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
No!
I can't die…
I haven't become
the master of the Three Realms.
You should have died long ago.
Dad…
You can rest in peace now.
Jiumin has avenged you.
♪Boundless night, drawing close♪
♪Darkness staining silhouettes♪
♪Countless whispers of wind♪
Tantai Jin,
what are you doing!
Di Mian has died!
Everything is over.
♪The hidden moon covers our eyes♪
Susu,
sorry.
♪In an instant♪
♪Bright or dark, it's ever-changing♪
♪Looking back, I see my fate unfold♪
No!
♪I'm not afraid of being burnt like a fire
and be extinguished like smoke♪
♪One thought, our first moonlit meeting♪
♪A dream spanning lifetimes, unceasing♪
♪Fated to part, if we'd change it♪
♪Heart-ties boundless, my inner world fill♪
Susu, leave now!
Tantai Jin has fallen as the devil.
He killed Zhaoyou!
♪The hidden moon covers our eyes♪
Tantai Jin,
you didn't do that,
did you?
You're wrong.
I did kill him.
I am the Devil God, don't forget.
♪I want to break free
from the endless night♪
♪If my wish is granted, I'm not afraid of
being burnt like a fire and be extinguished like smoke♪
♪In an instant, reminiscing old dreams
our pact in the mortal world♪
♪Futile love is locked
in the furrow between the brows♪
♪If no one is spared the woes of love♪
Li Susu,
you are too stupid.
♪That capture our hearts♪
If it weren't for you,
I would have become the Devil long ago.
If it weren't for Zhaoyou,
I would have returned
to the Demon Realm long ago.
I don't understand what you are saying.
Are you Tantai Jin
or the Devil God?
Alright then.
I might as well just
explain everything clearly.
All the entanglements between you and me
are like this thing.
Everything you have done
is in vain.
Are you happy?
Channeling the mystical arts
of Heaven and Earth:
Retreat!
Susu,
Tantai Jin's nature is hard to change.
Just now he devoured Di Mian,
as you have seen.
Before this,
he also killed Master Zhaoyou
in front of everyone.
He is full of evil,
so you must not
have any more illusions about him.
Cang Jiumin,
you animal!
What have you done? Cang Jiumin!
Does your ungrateful heart still remember,
if it weren't for Master bringing you back
to Xiaoyao Sect back then,
you would have died outside
and turned into a pile of mud?
How could you!
Tantai Jin!
Why did you do this?
What did Zhaoyou do wrong to you?
No reason.
I was born this way.
And
I have killed you once 500 years ago.
Now, I can kill you again.
Master!
You can't trust him whatsoever.
Tantai Jin,
what is going on?
Farewell, Li Susu.
Now there is no one else left
in this Devil Palace.
You all want me dead.
Jiumin,
go!
Jiumin!
Master!
You saved me again.
Silly kid,
don't forget, I'm your master.
Master,
why are we back to the Xiaoyao Sect?
I used Xiaoyao Sword-play
to set up a boundary here.
As long as I'm still alive,
this boundary can protect you.
Do they still think
that I stole the evil bone?
Yes.
Do you still want to believe in me?
Of course I do.
In the world,
no matter who covets the evil bone,
it can't be you.
It was Di Mian. He has the evil bone.
Jiumin,
promise me
that you have to live well.
Master…
Master!
Don't go.
Don't go alone.
Remember my words,
live well.
Master!
You…
Jiumin,
I don't have much time left.
Di Mian has become the Devil God,
and the All-in-Distress Way has started.
When negative energy
fills Heaven and Earth,
the Three Realms
will be filled with suffering.
How?
Why?
Every formation has a weakness,
the All-in-Distress Way cannot be endless.
The All-in-Distress Way can be ended,
but only
the Devil God can do it.
The Devil God…
When the Devil God exists,
the All-in-Distress Way will exist.
When the Devil God perishes,
the All-in-Distress Way will perish.
Jiumin,
Do you know
why I gave you this name?
So, that's it.
When I found you near the Ruo-River,
I knew you're a jinx,
destined to be alone in your life.
I get it
that you've already know that
I'm the biggest disaster
back then.
But Jiumin,
you should know
that none is supposed to live
in the dark forever.
[You knew]
[I'm the devil fetus.]
[Yet you'd rather]
[give me a chance to re-choose my life.]
Jiumin,
help me up.
I wish to take another look
of our Xiaoyao Sect.
Master.
I have tainted by the power
of All-in-Distress Way.
No matter what living creature you are,
as long as you're infected by it
and your will gets weak,
you'll become a devil.
Jiumin,
I need you to do one more thing for me.
Kill me.
Not making me turn into a devil.
Master, please don't say like that.
I'll take you back for treatment.
Let's go.
Master.
Jiumin, kill me now.
Jiumin, I'm almost a devil.
Jiumin, a weapon can kill one
and it can also save one.
It's up to the good or bad purpose
of the one who uses it.
I can't do it, master.
Jiumin, quick to kill me.
I can't.
Or it'll be too late!
Master, please don't force me.
Kill me to save the others.
Tantai Jin,
just do it!
Kill me!
Master.
[Jiumin,]
[it's not your fault]
[to being a devil fetus.]
[Everyone should have the righ
to choose.]
[However,]
[All-in-Distress Way has been opened.]
[No one can turn it off]
[in Three Realms,]
[expect the Devil God.]
[Cang Jiumin,
a deciple of the Immortal Sect, ]
[is incapable to save the common lives.]
[But Tantai Jin, the Devil God can do it.]
[Jiumin,]
[the All-in-Distress Way]
[is binded with you]
[and the Devil God.]
[All three live and die together.]
[I know it's unfair to you.]
[But it's the only chance]
[that can stop the Devil God
to destory the world.]
[I get it.]
[Now that]
[it's the only road,]
[I'll take the road.]
[No matter what I'll be like,]
[I'm Tantai Jin,]
[and Cang Jiumin forever.]
Master…
Cang Jiumin,
scum!
Good.
I killed him by myself.
Now,
it's a battle between us.
I will
take it all away.
♪Even if there's only a glimmer of hope♪
♪Even if there's only a beam of light♪
♪I'm never forgotten by the winds♪
Mo Nv, what are you talking about?
How come I don't understand it?
I'm a devil originally.
It's natural for me to go
across the heaven and the earth freely.
What's so strange for me to come
to the the Demon Realm?
No, no way.
How could it be?
How could you be…?
Gongye Jiwu,
let me tell you a story.
To restore her spirit, the Monstert of Drought
was sent into the man's world
for sufferings five hundred years ago.
She became the eldest daughter
of a country's grand general.
And her name is Ye Bingchang.
Then,
she married with Prince Xuancheng,
They're the Two of a Kind.
Xiaolin.
But nothing gold can stay.
Ye Bingchang
betrayed Xiao Lin
and led to his death.
But Xiao Lin still
loved her,
tolerated her
and protected her
until the last minute of his life.
Ye Bingchang very regreted till her death.
The
the Monster of Drought regreted as well.
Later,
she woke up.
She still loved the life in the human world.
So she returned to the human world
and opened anembroidery workshop.
But
the fate is a teaser.
She met a fool
who looked exactly like Xiao Lin.
So she decided to cheat
and have fun with him.
Right?
I thought
I can make up the regret to Xiao Lin
on you.
But, Gongye Jiwu,
I want to say thank you.
You make me understand
that Xiao Lin will never come back.
I hated be cheated on
before,
But just now
I'd rather you cheat me.
Even you cheat my the whole life.
Why you don't do that?
You likes
very much
like him,
Gongye Jiwu.
You're a good person as well.
Too bad,
you're not him.
[I tried every mean,]
[All-in-Distress Way still
can't be closed.]
[Now it is spead,]
[I don't have much time left.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[you need to find a way for this.]
[In Bo're Life,]
[with the help of the magic weapon,
the All-in-Distress Way]
[the Devil God's evil bone was taken out.]
[If I have them,]
[I can do it like that]
[to take out the evil bone.]
[If it goes well,]
[I can be killed]
[just like the Devil God back then.]
[Since the All-in-distress Way
lives and dies with me,]
[it will be ended]
[along with my death.]
Thank you, Devil God,
for avenging Si Ying.
Ye Bingchang?
I see.
After twists and turns of 500 years,
in the end,
no one can escape from fate.
I thought losing Xiao Lin
was like losing my life.
And I thought having a sister
who truly loved me
was a blessing from heaven.
But I didn't expect
it was meant for me to lose her again.
Why do you come to see me?
Ten thousand years ago,
the Devil God also saved my life.
Besides, what Si Ying wanted the most
was to follow the Devil God
and see his arrival with her own eyes.
Now she can't fulfill this wish.
As her elder sister,
I'll watch this till the end for her.
Tell me,
how can we make you the ruler of three realms
like ten thousand years ago?
As far as I know,
the three artifacts haven't returned yet.
The God-slaughtering Crossbow
and the Bone-refining Seal
are in the immortal sects.
But this is my own business.
What's between us has already finished.
Mo Nv,
you can go live your own life
even without Xiao Lin and Si Ying.
Tantai Jin,
you seem
different from the Devil God
I know.
It's a big world out there.
You can always find a place you like.
Qu Xuan Zi is dead.
Zhaoyou is dead, too.
What wonderful news!
Now there's only my seal
on the God-slaughtering Crossbow.
If it's heaven's plan
to take my son's life
but send the God-slaughtering Crossbow to me,
how can I give this treasure
to those clowns from Hengyang Sect?
I must put your power to good use.
From now on,
I am
the ruler of all sects!
I return the Devil God's eye
to you.
Sect Leader Cen was murdered.
[Glow and Thrive, Tao Is the Highest]
The God-slaughtering Crossbow was stolen.
Now all the leaders
of the three major sects are dead.
Only the Bone-refining Seal
of the three artifacts
is in our Hengyang Sect.
But who knows for how long we can keep it.
Tantai Jin really went too far.
Who exactly killed Sect Leader Cen?
According to disciples of Chixiao Sect,
it's done by a woman demon in red.
She looked a bit like
Si Ying the she devil.
[You completely changed me.]
[You gave me]
[a chance to live again.]
[I will never be contaminated
with the Devil God's power.]
[For you,]
[I'll keep this promise.]
[Tantai Jin!]
[What are you doing?]
[Tantai Jin has devilized.]
[He killed Sect Uncle Zhaoyou.]
[Now, everything you've done]
[is wasted.]
[However the fate may be like,]
[I can choose]
[between good and evil by myself.]
[I]
[shall never become the Devil God!]
[Only by killing the Devil God for good]
[can they feel rest assured.]
[And only in this way]
[can I really walk down this road with you.]
Susu,
come back with me.
Since the All-in-distress Way is activated,
it's not safe outside the sect.
Senior Sect Brother, just leave me alone.
Now that I've left the sect,
I'll be responsible for my own life.
What are you going to do?
Looking for Tantai Jin?
What's the point of it now?
He killed his own master,
murdered people and snatched the crossbow.
He's probably in cahoots with Di Mian.
He's a monster with his hands full of blood.
You're still unwilling to believe it?
Li Susu,
use your reason.
You'll get yourself killed if you go.
Let go of me first.
What if he really had a reason?
I must be there whatever you say.
I must hear the answers from him.
What's the difference between living in the dark
and death?
At least I must know
whom I should hate.
Fine.
If you're so resolute,
I'll let you go.
Thank you.
[But from now on,]
[you will no longer be one of Hengyang Sect.]
[And you will no longer be my Sect Sister.]
[I'm sorry, Senior Sect Brother.]
[The God-slaughtering Crossbow?]
[Mo Nv did what she shouldn't do after all.]
[Never mind.]
[I'll just be this Devil God properly,]
[so that Susu can give up on me completely]
[and the sects will kill me without mercy.]
Welcome back, Master!
I've kept you waiting.
From today on,
I am your master.
I want everything in chaos
and everyone in distress.
Everything in chaos!
everyone in distress!
[I've obtained the Sky-Slashing Sword
and the God-slaughtering Crossbow.]
[The Bone-refining Seal]
[is still in the hands of Hengyang Sect.]
everyone in distress!
[As long as I unite the three artifacts,]
[All-in-distress Way will unleash
its maximum power.]
I heard that
they cast many spells
around the Bone-refining Seal,
and they wanted to get me injured
with the might of heaven and earth.
That's just wishful thinking.
Kill them!
Take the seal back!
I'm in a good mood today.
No need to kill anyone.
Why don't I just play a magic trick?
The Bone-refining Seal.
Cang Jiumin actually activated
the array to summon the demonic artifact.
Sect Leader,
what should we do?
The demons already own two artifacts.
We can't let him take the last piece.
Everyone back off!
Overextending ants,
stop wasting your strength.
What's that sound?
It's the Devil God.
Tantai Jin!
How dare you take the
Bone-refining Seal without even showing up?
Gongye Jiwu,
do you still rebel against me now?
[Tao Is the Highest]
Do you still rebel against me now?
Take my advice.
Bow to me.
Bow to the absolute power.
In your dreams!
[Tao Is the Highest]
Senior Sect Brother.
Sect Brother.
Everything in chaos.
everyone in distress!
Everything in chaos!
[So,]
[this is the All-in-distress Way.]
[It's beyond the limits of senses.]
Everything in chaos!
everyone in distress!
[This is the power of All-in-distress Way.]
[Evilness.]
Everything in chaos! everyone in distress!
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪