♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 3]
[Ye Mansion]
He talks to birds?
Yeah.
And flies and mosquitoes!
When he passed by the lake the other day,
a frog was sitting on the shore,
and they chatted for a while.
[Mr. Tantai is so weird.]
[He can hold a conversation with a frog.]
[Talking to himself?]
[The servants passing by the lake]
Indeed.
[were all snickering at him.]
You, stop being naughty!
[What is this quackery?]
[Haven't I told you?]
[Forget about tracking anyone else,]
[your only job is to watch Tantai Jin.]
[If he does anything suspicious,]
[especially if he gets up to any tricks,]
[report right back.]
[Also, keep a close eye on him.]
[Don't let him freeze, starve,]
[or get beaten up.]
[He's not allowed to leave Ye Mansion.]
[His every movement is being watched.]
[It's utterly impossible]
[for him to play any tricks.]
[He also talks to]
[sparrows, butterflies and whatnot.]
[Basically, he talks to all animals]
[except humans.]
[Miss,]
[do you think]
he can actually talk to animals?
You must've overworked yourself.
Why don't you take a few days off?
Miss,
I really saw them talking!
Maybe it's because
no one in this mansion ever talks to him.
Anyone would go crazy
without someone to talk to
all year round.
Now that I think about it,
Mr. Tantai is quite pitiful.
[Could it be that he became the Devil God]
[because he was isolated for too long?]
[This won't do.]
[I need to have a word with him.]
Miss Xiwu,
You've followed me around for days.
Do you have something to say to me?
You guessed right.
I've been so bored lately.
So I wanted to have someone to chat with.
Go ahead.
Nice weather today, huh?
It's freezing!
Tantai Jin.
Tantai Jin!
You're always getting bullied.
How does that make you feel?
I don't.
No way.
Anyone who gets insulted
would be angry or resentful inside.
Haven't you thought of
doing something about it?
Like…
Killing me?
You want me to kill you?
No.
That's not what I meant.
I just wanted to know
what you're thinking inside.
It doesn't matter what I think.
You all insult me
not because of what I've done,
but simply because you enjoy it.
I can't change all of you.
As for whether I hold
resentment or grudges,
none of it matters.
I'm just a hostage prince from Jing Kingdom.
To be alive is exhausting enough.
I can't afford to think
about anything else.
[This was five hundred years ago.]
[The Little Devil God
truly hadn't done anything bad.]
[Or shall I say,
he hadn't had his chance yet.]
[Instead, people were the ones
doing bad things to him.]
[Maybe he only became the Devil God]
[due to the series of tragedies.]
[If someone was willing to help him,]
[to show him kindness and cared about him]
[would he have fallen
on this devilish path?]
Tantai Jin,
life is indeed tough,
but you still have to live on.
Come find me if you ever feel bored.
Not socializing for too long
can turn you into a psychopath!
Like you?
You looked good when you smiled just now.
There're so many people in the mansion.
I'm sure someone will like you
and want to talk to you.
No one will ever like me.
And I don't need to be liked.
Miss!
Miss, look!
I visited all the clothing stores in town,
and got some nice
and thick winter clothes.
Pick one for Mr. Tantai.
This one's too thin.
This works.
The color looks good too.
But it's too big.
He can't wear this.
How am I supposed to know his size?
Go fetch me some sewing tools.
Miss,
I'm not sure if I should ask you this…
Then don't.
Why are you being so nice
to Mr. Tantai now?
Because I'm afraid.
Afraid? Of what?
I'm afraid one day
when Mr. Tantai freezes to death,
he'll drag us along to hell.
And what if
after all the constant ill-treatment,
he finally snaps one day,
decides he's done being a punching bag,
turns into a big tiger
donned in a black robe,
and eats us all!
Why would a big tiger
be wearing a black robe?
[Don't freeze to death]
This coat is for me?
A kept man who lives off a woman
actually affords a new coat?
Stop right there.
Tantai Jin?
What is it?
You just slit my coat.
Slit?
Now that's a slit.
Are you getting mad?
Are you starting to have a temper
because Xiwu hasn't beaten you lately?
How dare you glare at me?
Our Ye family
has given you such a good life
that you've gotten brash
with your masters now?
I'm gonna beat you up right now!
Why are you getting violent?
I'm not. Why did you pull me away?
I just helped you
slit that kept man's coat.
Look at him showing off.
Ye Zeyu,
pay for it.
Hasn't Father taught you
an eye for an eye, a coat for a coat?
What?
What's wrong with you, Xiwu?
You paying or not?
Don't make me go to Father.
I'll pay.
Here!
Trollop.
Just ignore him.
This slit is too big to be patched.
Forget it.
You can't wear this anymore.
I'll get a new one.
You gave this to me.
It's mine now.
Alright. You keep it.
I'll have Chuntao buy you a new one.
Miss!
It's a royal edict!
Mr. Tantai is to have
an audience with the King.
[The Little Devil God still
has ties within the palace?]
[I must follow him to find out.]
[In case something fishy is going on.]
I'll come with you.
Tantai Jin is here to meet His Majesty!
Greetings, Your Majesty.
Miss Xiwu,
His Majesty will only
meet Prince Tantai alone.
If you have nothing to do,
how about having a chat
with the Empress Dowager?
It's okay.
I'm pretty familiar with the palace.
I'll just take a walk.
Sure.
[The Devil God was raised in this palace.]
[What on earth did Tantai Jin go through?]
[How did he spend his days?]
[Why choose him as the Devil God?]
[If I saw the place he lived,]
[maybe I can find some clues.]
You there.
Miss Xiwu.
Do you know where Tantai Jin used to live?
Tantai Jin,
here's a letter from Jing Kingdom.
It was sent from the palace.
Do you want to read it?
No.
Any normal person would want
to hear from his family.
When you say no,
it sounds like a lie.
For me, Jing Kingdom
is a thousand miles away,
to which I shall never return.
Emperor Jing is someone
I knew twenty years ago,
whom I will never reunite with.
He is but a foreigner in a foreign land.
I don't care.
Nor do I wish to care.
Do you mean that?
Do you know Emperor Jing Tantai Wuji
is about to die of an illness?
Your elder brother Tantai Minglang
has been made crown prince.
[I see.]
Noted.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Tantai Minglang is an ambitious one.
He's been waging wars against us,
and never bothered to care
about his younger brother's wellbeing.
Is he truly not afraid
that I might cut your head off
as sacrifice?
Tantai Minglang and I
are just strangers
who share the same blood.
He wouldn't care if I lived or died.
If you were to behead me as sacrifice,
I'm afraid that may be
exactly what he wishes.
He shows no mercy for you.
Have you never thought of
going back to Jing Kingdom
and taking back all that belongs to you?
[I see he's trying to play me
against my own brother.]
Your Majesty,
I've left my country for over a decade.
I am but a wanderer.
The people of Jing Kingdom
only acknowledge Tantai Minglang.
There's no place for me back there.
Besides, fate has a plan for us all.
The throne, the mortal land,
I'll leave these for others to compete.
This is my fate.
To be able to breathe is enough for me.
It seems
I was overconcerned.
You may leave.
This man has a heart of stone.
He baffles me every time I see him.
No wonder his old man
does not care for him.
Since he refuses to work for me,
he's useless now.
Have someone keep an eye on him.
He'll cause trouble as long as he's alive.
About what I mentioned before,
get it done quickly.
Yes, Your Majesty.
I've made arrangements.
Do be careful.
Find someone
of similar appearance and age.
Don't make any mistakes.
When the time comes,
I can give the Ye family a surprise
and disrupt the Jing Kingdom as well.
Wise move, Your Majesty.
Miss Xiwu, we're here.
This was where Prince Tantai had lived
before being sent to the Ye family.
You're after His Highness!
Ma'am,
it's a cold day.
Why are you on the ground?
Miss Xiwu,
this is nanny Yingxin.
I heard she's the one
who brought up Prince Tantai.
She followed His Highness here
from Jing Kingdom.
You're after His Highness!
Do you mean Tantai Jin? Who's after him?
I'd never cause him harm.
Your Highness, please hold on.
Chief Wu.
I haven't had the chance
to congratulate you on your marriage.
Congratulations.
Chief Wu,
let's drop the pleasantries.
I heard
that although you've married Miss Ye Xiwu,
the one you love is Miss Bingchang.
As we all know,
Miss Bingchang and our Prince Lin
see eye to eye with each other.
And General Ye
has long regarded him as his son-in-law.
Since you're now at the Ye Mansion,
this is rather convenient.
Could you keep an eye out for me?
What do you mean?
For proof of their collusion, of course!
Collusion?
You want me to help you frame
Xiao Lin and Ye Xiao?
What a poor choice of words.
I'm His Majesty's close attendant.
Certainly, I should share his worries.
If you're willing to help,
not only can I guarantee you'll live long,
but I may also help you
marry your one true love.
[In this vast capital,]
[Xiao Lin is the only one
who has been sincere with me.]
[We're not close enough
to meddle in each other's affairs,]
[but there's no reason
for me to do him harm.]
I'm afraid I won't be able
to help you do that.
Don't ask for the hard way.
Don't forget what happened to Yue Yingxin.
How did she become like this?
This cold palace
has few visitors all year round.
We don't know when she went crazy either.
I just heard that
she's been like this
ever since Prince Tantai
left for Ye Mansion.
I didn't harm His Highness.
It's not me.
No. I didn't harm His Highness.
I didn't harm His Highness.
Don't you forget
where this place is.
Don't forget I'm in control of her fate.
It's up to me
whether she lives or dies.
Don't think you can live in peace
by being a docile son-in-law
with no say
in the Ye family.
I'll kill Yingxin if you don't comply.
But I won't let her die so quickly.
I thought
you were just Xiao Liang's loyal dog.
I didn't expect
you to be a talkative one too.
Tantai Jin, you…
His Highness wants you back.
Understood.
The hostage prince Tantai,
as for what I just said…
Chief Wu,
you were just catching up with me.
You're getting better at this, huh?
Alright, listen.
If you dare
tell anyone else about what I said,
I will make you regret being born.
A lowly son of a lowly mother!
[That Chief Wu talks too much.]
That Tantai Jin
thinks too highly of himself!
Godfather,
don't let anger consume your health.
About the one you told me to find,
I've got him.
It'll surely be enough
to fool those of Jing Kingdom.
No.
I just shared too many secrets with him.
If he is of no use to me,
I can't let him live any longer!
Tantai Jin must be killed tonight!
If he won't listen,
replace him with someone who will!
Godfather!
He's dead!
Lin,
you said you had
something important to discuss.
What is it?
Father,
many civilians of late
have gone missing in their sleep.
I suspect a demon has entered the capital.
I sent Chen Xian to lead the Dragon Guards
to investigate on the missing civilians
as soon as I heard the report.
I've arranged day-and-night patrols
in and out of the capital
to look out for the demon.
Father, please be careful
in the palace too,
in case the demon causes trouble.
Of all the princes we sent
to Mount Buzhao,
you're the most promising one.
You excelled the fastest
in your cultivation.
You've made great progress
in just three years.
But faced with demons like this,
I'm afraid you can't win for sure
with just three years of cultivation.
Sorry to let you down.
It's fine.
I happen to have someone
who can be of use to you.
Prince Lin, we meet again.
Junior Martial Uncle!
So Master sent you here?
My sect brother said
the opportunity of my lifetime
would be in the capital.
He told me to spend
a few years here before returning.
What opportunity is that?
Well, I don't have a clue.
But at least I can help while I'm here.
The Barren Abyss Barrier
has weakened recently,
and demons are slipping through,
wrecking havoc in the mortal world.
You also know
that our Xiaoyao Sect
loves minding irrelevant things like this.
This is not irrelevant.
It's a big deal concerning people's lives.
Since Father appointed you
as Senior Chamberlain,
as an official,
you ought to protect your people.
Now that we are under attack by demons,
please help me subdue them right away.
Look how the tables have turned.
Back in Mount Buzhao
I was your Sect Uncle.
Now that I'm in the Sheng,
I've become your subordinate!
But the salary of a Sheng official
is simply too low.
I can't even feed my own mouth.
Let alone my family members.
Junior Martial Uncle,
you're adopting cats again.
You know me best.
[Little Devil God
had a hard life in the palace,]
[that's why he's so down and pessimistic.]
[The evil bone feeds on hatred and pain]
[to accumulate strength.]
[That's why Tantai Jin suffered so much.]
[Is this the fate of the Devil God?]
Buttercup.
It's late.
Why are you out on this windy night?
Aren't you cold?
Father, why are you home so late?
You must be tired.
Are you worried about me?
You've really grown up.
By the way,
if you got nothing important to do,
don't hang around outside.
Why?
The capital isn't safe.
Some civilians have disappeared
in their sleep.
Seems it's a demon's doing.
And another strange thing
happened in the palace.
His Majesty's loyal advisor
Chief Wu had an accident.
He chatted a little with Tantai Jin,
and died soon after going back.
His ears were bleeding.
The way he died was bizarre.
A wasp even crawled out of his ear.
[A wasp?]
[He talks to birds?]
[Yeah, and flies and mosquitoes.]
[and they chatted for a while.]
I won't say more,
in case my darling daughter
becomes too frightened to sleep.
Go to bed.
Miss, are there really
demons in this world?
Not only demons,
but also devils.
[Even when I left the palace
and hid in Ye Mansion,]
[they still wouldn't let me go.]
[I must find a way
to get out of Sheng Kingdom.]
Chief Wu,
you've lived long enough.
Go.
[With my current abilities,]
[controlling a couple of small creatures
is the best I can do.]
[I barely got out of danger this time.]
[Next time might be more challenging.]
[How do I know if he has awakened?]
[Little Devil God
doesn't have much power now.]
[If it was him who did it,]
[he must have used a curse or a charm.]
[If you murdered someone,]
[you'll definitely leave traces behind.]
Miss Xiwu?
[There's nothing on him.]
What are you dissatisfied with?
[I'll just have to trick it out of him.]
Chief Wu from the palace
suddenly died today.
Did you know that?
I heard that he stopped you
before you left the palace.
What did he say to you?
Nothing.
[So calm.]
[Is he really innocent?]
From today on,
I'm gonna search you before you go to bed.
I'm warning you,
don't even think about
playing tricks on me.
Miss Xiwu's interests
are getting more and more intense.
Don't you start with me.
Who knows if you might have told
one of those wasps or bugs
to kill for you.
I don't wanna end up like Chief Wu,
dying for no reason at all.
[How did she find out?]
In this case,
searching my body doesn't seem enough.
How about
I take off all my clothes
so that you may be rest assured?
Go ahead.
Not my loss.
We're husband and wife after all.
I've already seen it all.
Go on.
You're not gonna do it?
Shall I do it instead?
[When did she become so much smarter?]
Be wary of your candles
during this hot summer!
[Grudge, hatred…]
[Fear, remorse…]
[You're the one!]
Help!
[East Capital Gate]
[As expected,]
[nowhere else has more nightmares]
[than this palace does.]
[With the aid of these nightmares,]
[I can cultivate more nightmare blossoms.]
The red string is up to your neck.
[You really look like a miserable one.]
[Why don't you leave here with me?]
[I sense a unique scent]
[outside of these palace walls.]
[It's not yet dawn anyway.]
[I'll go take a look.]
[It's right here.]
[It was worth the trip.]
[This scent is truly unique.]
It was mine to begin with.
Your Highness, don't go.
[Little sweetheart,]
[you're obviously a mortal,]
[but there's something demonic in you.]
[How very interesting.]
What a fruitful night I got.
Why don't you come back with me too?
[With the nourishment
of these miserable souls,]
the nightmare blossoms
will soon be everywhere.
[As long as they bloom
all over the woods,]
[I can evolve from a demon to a devil!]
[Ye Mansion]
[A demon in the capital…]
[Chief Wu's violent death…]
[Do they have anything to do
with the Little Devil God?]
What are you looking at?
There better not be leftovers.
Finish them.
Ye Xiwu,
you're so capricious.
Yeah.
Lately, I find myself enjoying
watching people eat.
Is there a problem?
When this month ends,
and you don't put on three pounds,
I'll give you a good beating!
[Her psychopathic ways
are becoming more unpredictable.]
Miss!
Bad news! Miss Bingchang is missing!
What?
She was perfectly fine last night,
but she was suddenly gone this morning.
I'm afraid…
It's t-t-that… demon
His Lordship mentioned.
What should we do?
Calm down. Tell me in detail.
His Lordship sent
for the Senior Chamberlain
to exorcise demons in the mansion.
I hear Prince Lin is here, too.
I'll go take a look.
[She's still interested in Xiao Lin.]
[Good.]
[This way, no one will care]
[about Chief Wu's death.]
Butler Liu,
bring Jiahui back to have a good rest.
Yes.
Brother,
who's this guy?
He's the new Senior Chamberlain,
Pang Yizhi.
I heard
he's the direct disciple
of the Xiaoyao Sect,
and also the sect uncle of Prince Lin.
Catching demons is his specialty.
Then do you know who his master is?
I heard it's Immortal Qingxu
from Mount Buzhao.
[Never heard of him.]
[Could he be Uncle Zhaoyou's
great-grand master.]
No demon can escape from his eyes.
He can identify one in an instant.
When he strikes,
every demon dies in his hands.
[Oh, no.]
[He's a senior disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.]
[If he finds out Tantai Jin's evil bone]
[and executes him,]
[that would be bad.]
[What now?]
Scholar Pang, anything I can help you with?
Junior Martial Uncle, what's wrong with him?
Scholar Pang, he…
This young master
has a charming face.
He's bound to be rich and famous.
When you're rich, don't forget me.
Don't forget me, yeah?
Thank you for your blessing.
[The Xiaoyao Sect five hundred years ago]
[must've been lenient with admissions.]
Scholar Pang,
you've walked in circles for a while.
Have you found anything?
General,
for now I haven't seen anything yet,
but everyone in your mansion
should be fine.
Please allow me
to cast an array in your mansion
to search for that demon's traces,
and get Miss Bingchang back.
Sure, I'll be counting on you.
You mean
that well-cultivated demon
took them to Mount Banzhen
in the southern outskirts
and used these people
to plant flowers?
Yes.
Ye Bingchang and Yingxin
were both taken by that demon.
But it seems like that demon
doesn't plan on killing these people yet.
Why don't we share these clues with them
and have them rescue the kidnapped?
Got it.
You go check what Ye Xiwu is doing.
[Ye Xiwu's especially smart lately.]
[She's suspected me
of controlling animals.]
[If I tell her these,]
[it's no different from pleading guilty.]
[Forget it.
Why bother getting into trouble?]
[The demon-locking array]
The demon-locking array?
[Demon-locking Array]
It's here.
Next step…
What's the next step again?
Where should this flag be planted?
The white flag corresponds
to the metal element.
I've tried this spot.
That one's wrong, too.
This doesn't make sense.
Not here.
[Will this poorly constructed array work?]
[Never mind.]
[I'll do it myself.]
[Thankfully, dad forced me to learn]
[how to draw spells for a few years.]
[Since I don't have any powers,]
[I can use this
for desperate times like now.]
[Scholar Pang,]
[I'll borrow some
of your incantation slips.]
[It's for the good of everybody.]
[Surely you wouldn't mind.]
[The misery in the mortal world]
[is indeed nightmare blossoms'
best fertilizer.]
[Traveling thousands of miles
from Barren Abyss]
[was certainly worth it.]
[Aren't these two]
[the ones I brought back just last night?]
[Their nightmare blossoms
have bloomed so quickly.]
[My judgment was right.]
[Let me see what's special]
[about your experiences.]
[So you're a maid from Jing Kingdom.]
[You followed a hostage prince
to Sheng Kingdom.]
Let go of me. Your Highness!
Let go of me!
[Who is this?]
[There's someone
with such a twisted fate?]
[He hasn't had a hint of warmth]
[or a glimmer of light in his life.]
[If I plant a nightmare blossom with him,]
[it'll definitely be
the best of its kind.]
[It can surely help me devilize.]
[Order]
[This demon-locking array]
[is like guarding
by a tree stump for a hare.]
[If the hare doesn't show up,]
[he won't catch a thing
in ten thousand years.]
Shoo!
Miss Xiwu,
are you alright?
I'm okay.
I was just startled
by this bird.
I think
if you don't tell them where the demon is,
they won't find a trace till dawn.
Who'd have thought Ye Xiwu
who fears nothing and no one,
would be afraid of a bird?
Please keep a distance from her.
Fine.
This woman is usually so mean
yet she somehow fears me.
[Nighttime is the best time.]
[I smell it.]
[Right there. He's the one.]
[I've never smelled such a sweet scent.]
[He can definitely grow]
[the most beautiful nightmare blossom.]
[Someone from Xiaoyao Sect is here.]
[I better be cautious.]
What was that?
The edict of the Heavenly Lord
reveals all hidden evil.
Demon-binding charm, purge all darkness!
Seize!
Prince Lin,
we caught it, didn't we?
Oh, no.
This black fog is a deceit.
It was a distraction!
That's…
Tantai Jin's chamber!
[Ye Bingchang is on the southern outskirts
of Mount Banzhen]
[Now they can't tell who wrote it.]
[I have to think of a way]
[to slip this note to Xiao Lin.]
[Let him play the hero.]
[I can't arouse
Ye Xiwu's suspicion again.]
You're the one I've been looking for.
You will certainly flourish into
the most beautiful nightmare blossom.
By the light and power
of the mystic thunder,
strike!
You've overestimated yourself.
Tantai Jin, hold on to me.
Ye Xiwu, are you a fool?
You'll get yourself killed!
I can't let you die!
[What a pair of lovebirds.]
[Then you can come along.]
Miss Xiwu!
I'm doomed.
She is General Ye's precious daughter.
He's gonna rip my head off!
Prince Lin,
nothing must happen to Miss Xiwu!
Miss Xiwu was kidnapped by the demon.
Ye Bingchang is in Mount Banzhen
in the southern outskirts.
I'm going to save her.
Could this scribble be some kind of trap?
It's our last resort.
I have to give it a try.
Bring the Dragon Guards. Let's go.
Okay.
[What is this place?]
[Susu,]
[that Devil God came like a storm.]
[You must stay and guard the gate.]
[I'll help the Sect Leader.]
[What?]
[Why is Sect Brother here?]
[And why am…]
[Listen to me.]
[Hengyang Sect's mantle
must be passed down.]
[Hengyang Sect…]
[But it's clearly…]
[Susu, wake up!]
[clearly…]
[Tantai Jin has been
killed by the succubus.]
[The Devil God has awakened.]
[You're about to fail.]
[Susu, wake up!]
[Tantai Jin has been
killed by the succubus.]
[Susu, wake up!]
[Tantai Jin has been
killed by the succubus.]
[Father.]
[-Sect Sister, wake up!]
[-Sect Sister…]
[Devil God… Tantai Jin…]
[Succubus…]
[-Sect Sister, wake up!]
[-Sect Sister!]
[Where is this place?]
[The demon's den.]
[What was that dream I just had?]
Tantai Jin.
Thank goodness, you're not dead!
Why are you still standing there?
Help me get down!
Nightmare blossoms.
It all makes sense now.
What's a nightmare blossom?
I've read about it in books.
The succubus brings people to her den,
then uses the dark memories
within their heads as seeds
that grow into vines
and bind them in place.
Trapping them in endless nightmares
flourishing the nightmare blossoms
that she feeds on.
It's like raising livestock.
Ye Xiwu,
you've been reading?
Have you seen my elder sister?
She should be here too.
Over there.
Let's go.
Here she is.
Yingxin?
Why is she also here?
How do you know her?
I saw her when I was in the palace.
You were investigating me?
No, I wasn't.
I was just…
Passing by a remote and cold palace,
and saw a crazy woman.
So what if I did?
You're always being so mysterious.
Have you seen the demon?
The night's still young.
I guess she's still hunting.
She captured so many people.
And she's got her own barrier.
She's quite a mighty one.
No wonder Pang Yizhi couldn't catch her.
The deeper you sleep,
the tighter the vines will twine.
Tantai Jin,
why weren't you bound?
Because I never dream.
Let's rescue them.
Be careful.
[This is the land of the Yiyue Tribe.]
[But we were just in the woods.]
[This…]
[This isn't reality.]
[Tantai Jin?]
Greetings from Yingxin, Princess.
♪My empty heart has nothing to yearn for♪
I see.
Thanks for telling me.
But I'm the princess of Yiyue Tribe.
For the tribe, I have to go.
Let's go.
♪My regrets♪
Princess.
Yingxin and Lan'an are born to serve you.
Wherever you go,
we will follow.
[Seems like this is Yingxin's dream.]
[Which means Yiyue Tribe's princess…]
Yiyue Tribe has become our subordinate.
[is Tantai Jin's mother.]
Princess Yue Ruanruan,
known for her gentleness and virtues,
is hereby granted
the title of Concubine Rou.
She will be welcomed and greeted
with a grand wedding ceremony.
A nationwide celebration.
May Your Majesty and Her Highness
love each other forever,
and may your descendants thrive on and on!
♪Broken, rebuilt, destroy, reconstruct♪
♪I don’t care about my tears of sadness♪
♪I won’t follow the destined path of my life♪
♪When the mystic bird returns
who will it be then?♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I’ve seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪