♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 15]
Ming Ye.
You can't take it away.
Is that so?
Chu Huang.
You should be on my side.
You'd better think it through.
You keep getting in my way.
I'm gonna skin you alive!
Then bring it on.
In order to buy time
and finish sealing the evil bone soon,
Ming Ye summoned the Venerable Twins.
This may boost his power
for a short period of time,
but if we don't seal the evil bone soon,
this world will
no longer have a God of War
when his divine essence burns out.
[Almost there.]
[I must hang on.]
I can't let them go help the Devil God.
Chu Huang.
I can't hold much longer.
Before the space completely closes,
let's combine our power
to implode the Demon Realm.
But what about you?
No.
Ji Ze.
Being a god in this life.
I've fought with demons till the end.
Since there's nothing else I can do,
I don't mind
falling into the endless abyss
with demons and the Demon Realm.
Ji Ze.
Ji Ze,
you may end your
demon-slaying journey first.
Chu Huang, stop!
♪Brightness and warmth♪
♪Leaves me judging by intuition♪
♪How funny, I used to be in shackles♪
♪Sealed alone under the dome of destiny♪
♪Loneliness for tens of thousands of years♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
Old friends,
Ji Ze is going to leave first.
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
I shall subdue
the Barren Abyss with my body!
Seal!
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
The immortals are trying to trap us here!
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
♪A slight thought
Tells the difference between god and devil♪
Ji Ze sealed the Barren Abyss
with his divine essence.
♪I'm dreaming, I'm baffled
I try to fight with this burning fate♪
Ming Ye,
you failed.
The Navagraha Heavenly Spirits Array
can't be activated twice.
Ji Ze is dead.
Your divine power is running out.
And I have made it to the Heavenly Pillar!
You can't stop me!
Don't even think about it!
Chu Huang, leave the battlefield now!
Your spirit is draining.
Don't force yourself!
You still have time to worry about others?
Ming Ye,
the God-slaughtering Crossbow
is transformed from my eye.
The demonic arrows will shoot
whoever I want to kill.
This time,
you'll have no chance of survival!
[Once it locks on me,]
[there's no way I can dodge.]
[If I can seal
the evil bone with my life,]
[I will]
[have no regrets.]
[The demonic arrows are too many.]
[This space prison can't withstand them.]
[Ming Ye,]
[forgive me.]
Chu Huang!
Chu Huang.
How touching!
How many more companions do you have
that can die for you?
[You won't]
[die in vain.]
♪Meteors as loud as fire♪
My evil bone!
♪Heartbeats from the abyss♪
Just die!
♪Slash the darkness and embrace the dawn♪
♪Against the glowing of all stars♪
Still trying to escape?
♪Tear open the wounds of clouds and sky♪
♪We fight in songs till the universe darkens♪
♪Till everything sinks into cinder♪
♪Life or death is as common as a smile♪
♪Go ahead and use my body to block the enemies♪
♪I won't regret burning in fire
or broken into pieces♪
♪Even if there's only a glimmer of hope♪
♪Even if there's only a beam of light♪
♪I'll burn out this little energy in me♪
This is for killing my war mates!
♪Against the glowing of all stars♪
Today,
Mount Changze
will be your burial ground.
Desperate struggles.
How funny and pathetic!
♪Tear open the wounds of destiny♪
♪Let them reflect our shadows♪
♪I'm not afraid to burn all my blood♪
♪This is a tribute to my past pride♪
If you try to seal my evil bone,
I'll make the immortal realm die with it!
♪I won't regret burning in fire
Or broken into pieces♪
♪Even if there's only a glimmer of hope♪
♪Even if there's only a beam of light♪
♪I'll burn out this little energy in me♪
♪Go ahead and use my body to block the enemies♪
Alkaid!
♪Even if there's only a glimmer of hope♪
♪Even if there's only a beam of light♪
♪I'm never forgotten by the winds♪
[This is the Devil God's sword.]
[Is the Devil God dead?]
The Celestial Punishment
is about to be ready.
[Everyone,]
[I've decided
to use all of my divine power]
[to die together with the Devil God.]
[When I die,]
[I'll leave the rest to you.]
Little Ming Ye!
Ming Ye!
Jiu,
why are you so restless today?
Come.
I don't know why,
but I'm quite unsettled.
Immortals are different from spirits.
You'd been practicing immortal arts
for hundreds of years.
Now you're a beginner
in demonic cultivation.
It's normal that you can't change so soon.
There's no need to hurry.
[Ming Ye!]
[Ji Ze.]
[Sang Jiu,]
[you must
take care of yourself in the future.]
No one can resist me!
Not even you, God of War!
I said I wouldn't kill you,
and I won't break my promise.
But I will turn you
into a demonic flood dragon
for me to command.
And I'll let you
slaughter the three worlds.
And kill all of your associates!
What a pity. Your wish won't be granted.
I said you couldn't escape.
Activate the array!
Is this all you can do
with the gods' skills and the celestial power?
Why do you betray me?
You promised me you'd spare her.
Now she's dead.
So you're just as foolish as them!
I will seal you
for eternity!
The Devil God is finally killed!
Worth exhausting all of our powers.
[Everything]
[is over.]
You stole my evil bone.
You used
the Celestial Punishment to kill me!
I won't have mercy on you!
When heaven and earth collapse,
when the three realms return to chaos,
I wonder how
your Shangqing Realm would become?
The God of War has lost his power,
but the Devil God is still alive.
Now the Heavenly Pillars
are collapsed and all lives are doomed.
Looks like,
we can only use the last resort.
All gods return to the ruins
to protect Heaven and Earth!
Fall!
[Little Ming Ye, wake up!]
Everyone,
where is this place?
[Ming Ye,]
[this is your nirvana realm.]
Have I fallen?
[No.]
[We're going to fall.]
[As your war mates,]
[we're here to say goodbye.]
What?
[Although we part from each other today,]
[one day we shall reunite,]
[in the form of snow on the mountaintops,]
[or pebbles in streams
and willows by the water.]
[We'll leave
the holy halberd, Yize, to you.]
[Yize.]
Thank you all.
[I will return.]
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Report!
Your Highness!
Sang You,
what happened?
Nothing,
You stay in
the bamboo forest to cultivate.
Don't go anywhere.
I'll go back to Mohe to help father.
Okay.
Hold on!
Princess.
What's going on?
Well…
Just say it.
Your Highness,
news just came.
The gods and demons
fought at Mount Changze.
They fought fiercely
and neither would give in.
Then what about Ming Ye?
They fought quite a bloody war.
God of War must be at the head of his men.
[The gods killed
the Devil God and his army,]
[but they have all fallen.]
[Ming Ye, the God of War,
and Ji Ze, the God of Cosmos]
[were both missing.
[Where is Ming Ye now?]
[Even the war armor
couldn't withstand it.]
[I'm afraid it's going to melt very soon.]
[Goddess Chu Huang.]
[This divine power
can connect you and Ming Ye.]
[As long as you wish,]
[you may see him across time and space.]
[But you can only use it once.]
[Chu Huang,]
[help me.]
[Please send me to find Ming Ye.]
[Wherever he is,]
[I must bring him back.]
[Bank of Ruo River]
[Ming Ye,]
[where exactly are you?]
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
♪That's about to fall from the edge of the sky♪
♪I wanna hang a glittering butterfly there
Till the snow falls♪
[Ming Ye,]
[I'll get you out of here.]
[Just hold on for a little more time.]
[We're gonna leave together.]
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
♪Do you know a wise man does not fall in love?♪
♪Even when my heart is torn in two
I won't fly away♪
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
♪Like blessing, like suffering
It can't be settled♪
Ming Ye,
we're home.
Report!
Goddess,
we still haven't found him.
How could it be?
So many celestial soldiers
searched the Four Continents
and couldn't find Ming Ye?
[Ming Ye is badly injured.]
[Now he's back to his original form.]
[I gotta take good care of him.]
[Will he be able to adjust to this place?]
[Oh right,]
[the water of East Sea seems to be salty.]
[Ming Ye,]
[you're such a pain in the neck.]
[You're cuter to be like this.]
[According to books,]
[these spirit herbs are good nourishment.]
[They can help you
recover your human form.]
[Ming Ye,]
[transform back soon.]
[Curling in the shell like a little loach]
[doesn't feel like you at all.]
When you're back to human form,
you'll leave, right?
[You'll never forgive me]
[for doing that to you that day.]
[Ming Ye,]
[just wake up soon.]
[Don't worry.]
[I won't badger you.]
[I'll leave when you're recovered.]
[We won't owe each other anything.]
[Oh no!]
[I forgot Sang You would come.]
Sang You!
Jiu, you're back.
You went to pick herbs?
Are you feeling unwell?
No.
I've been reading medical books recently
and picked some tonics
that are good for cultivation.
[Even if I don't say,]
[Jiu will hear about
Ming Ye's death eventually.]
[But she's at
a critical time in her cultivation.]
[What if she gets too emotional]
[and steps in the wrong way?]
[Never mind.]
[I hope she won't
hear about it from others.]
[Instead, I'll find a way to tell her.]
-Sang You.
-Jiu.
Have you seen the pot
I put on the table?
I saw there're ingredients in it
and there's also salt.
So I cooked it in the kitchen for you.
If I'm one minute late,
I'm afraid you'll become tonic soup.
Jiu, what happened?
What's going on?
Nothing.
I suddenly remembered there were still
ingredients that I didn't put in.
I planned to cook in a few more days.
Sang You,
let's go out.
Sang You, what are you gonna teach me today?
I haven't finished talking.
You're improving so fast.
Soon, I won't be
qualified to teach you.
Then let me protect you, Sang You.
Sure.
It's getting late.
If I go back a little later,
my father will find out.
I'll come to visit you ten days later.
Sang You,
now I can learn by myself.
It's a long trip.
You don't have to come often.
You're getting independent so soon?
Fine then.
Then let's make it fifteen days.
I'll be back to check your training.
Ming Ye.
Ming Ye!
Have you ever loved me?
[No.]
[I never have.]
Oh, Sang Jiu,
what the hell were you thinking?
You even saved him.
Now he's transformed back.
When he wakes up and sees me,
he'll think that I'm badgering him again.
Why don't I take him
back to Yuqing Palace?
Just throw him at the doorstep?
Forget it.
I'll let you stay for a few more days.
When you wake up, you'll leave anyway.
Why is it so dark?
Bed?
[Did someone save me?]
[It's a human.]
Hey.
Wake up.
Don't be afraid.
I'm not a bad guy.
Did you save me?
Are you there?
Wh… What are you doing?
[His eyeballs don't look injured.]
[Maybe his wounds haven't healed]
[since he just
transformed back to human form.]
[Let me take care of him
for a little longer.]
That's right.
I'm the one who saved you.
Where did you find me?
I…
I cast the net to catch fish,
and caught a white loach.
I wanted to cook it with tofu,
but you turned into a living person.
You even blew up my pan.
I'm sorry.
I'll pay for that.
What are you doing?
Your wounds haven't healed yet.
You're blind and limping.
Where are you going?
[Yeah, where should I go?]
[The Devil God is dead,
and my mind is empty.]
[I couldn't fall together with them.]
[But this world]
[no longer needs Ming Ye, the God of War]
Little loach, you still don't know, huh?
Now the Devil God is killed.
The world has peace now.
We don't need to hide or run.
♪The more you try to hide it♪
Why don't you stay and work for me
as payment for me saving your life?
I don't know how to work.
You can learn.
How about this?
You do odds and ends for me.
And I'll help cure your eyes.
I'll let you go
when your eyesight recovers.
How's that?
This is obviously a better deal for me.
Why do you have to let me stay?
♪The more teardrops will fall when looking back♪
Because…
♪Keep quiet until the eyes look deep♪
♪Peach blossoms fall on your mountain of brows♪
Because there's only me here.
I'm too lonely.
I just need someone to talk to.
Even if it's someone I don't know.
[Yeah.]
[Now all of my war mates are gone.]
[Even Sang Jiu…]
[I'm also alone, aren't I?]
So?
Okay.
I promise you.
Then you go to bed now.
When the day breaks,
I'll try to find medicine for your eyes.
Wh… Where are you going?
I only have one bed.
I'll let you, the patient, sleep on it.
By the way,
you haven't told me
what your name is.
My…
My name is Mozhu.
I'm a bamboo spirit in this forest.
Are you scared?
My name is Ming Ye.
I used to live in the East Sea.
Thank you for saving me.
[This is the last time.]
[When his eyes recover,]
[we will]
[never see each other again.]
I've changed your medicine.
These are all skin traumas.
They'll recover in a few days.
Thanks.
♪So many lovers can't be together♪
♪My mood is like the tides pulled by the moon♪
♪I can't touch my memories♪
♪I speak silence when I open my mouth♪
♪I'm trapped within your one thought♪
♪I have colored bitterness and happiness now♪
♪Nothing escapes from the rules of the universe♪
♪Even when my heart of fire is covered in ice♪
♪Actually, the sun and the moon
can shine together♪
♪Light and darkness can overlap with each other♪
♪Love and hate has blurred boundaries♪
♪The most difficult wish
Is worth the longest dedication♪
♪Maybe only by turning love into sword♪
♪Can I change pain into gain♪
♪And cut through the horizon of fate♪
♪I'll love him bravely
And say goodbye in the same way♪
Don't worry too much.
I know some medical skills.
I'll find a way
to cure your eyes eventually.
Thanks.
These are herbs.
Help me pick the leaves
and put them in the basket on the left.
And put the stems
in the basket on the right.
Then grind the leaves
and break the stems
into short segments, okay?
Okay.
Thanks.
No need to say thanks so often.
You'll have a lot more to thank me for.
Okay.
♪Your eyes, if one inch closer♪
♪I'll fall for you without even realizing it♪
♪A sky full of stars♪
♪Quietly fall on your brow♪
♪As my heart sets its direction
Time passes and deepens♪
♪Let the galaxy be my pillow
and let the moon be my kiss♪
♪I wanna be in the dreams♪
♪To explore the spring in your eyes♪
♪We devoutly turn the wheels♪
♪Just to see one person in one life♪
♪From love at first sight
to affections too many to dismiss♪
Wait here for a sec.
♪Let me draw your palm print
with the load on my mind♪
Smell this.
♪For this life, I'm only willing
to meet one person♪
♪I wish my falling in love♪
Let's go.
♪Let me borrow the evening wind
To write our story♪
♪You'll know this is the best romance♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
And suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
Covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
While on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
Our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
Leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
Of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
As flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
Come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
As gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪