The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 34]
I was worried.
That I'd be exposed.
That the other members would find out
I was the devil fetus
they wanted to eradicate so badly.
But now that
things have been clarified,
I feel a sense of relief.
Funny,
right?
You know, now I see why
you launched the nails into my body then.
It wasn't me that you hated.
It was him.
I've gotten rid of the evil bone.
That means not having
to turn into the Devil God.
You changed me.
You gave me
a second chance in life.
Never again will I taint myself
with evil forces.
I will keep this promise
I've made you.
I haven't
had a chance
to thank you,
whether as Tan Taijin
or Cang Jiumin.
I did not change you.
Forbidding evil was my duty.
Anyway,
I got to go. I have a parade to watch.
[I knew you would pass through here]
[to move on.]
[That's why…]
That's why you're out here
waiting for me?
You're hurt?
Nothing serious.
Oh, come on.
You're bleeding badly.
I do have some wound care knowledge.
Please pardon the indecency.
I just couldn't bring myself
to leave an injured person unattended.
So it was you who subdued the demon
that plagued the capital of the Jing?
That was impressive.
It wasn't me.
Might have been a peer younger than me.
You told me you wanted to search for answers
in the capital of the Jing.
Did you?
Sort of.
Well, did it
put your mind at ease?
Miss Mo,
wh-what…?
Where is she?
She isn't out trying
to take her own life, or is she?
Miss Mo!
[She fixed the hole]
[by sewing a camellia?]
You're up early, Mr. Gongye.
Leaving for the convent?
Your robe,
I left it out here overnight.
Should be pretty much dry now.
It's very kind of you
to mend the hole.
My pleasure.
I'm glad you like it.
Miss Mo,
last nigh we…
I went to the woods this morning
to pick some wild mushrooms.
Would you care for breakfast
before you go?
I hope you don't mind
the simplicity.
It's mushroom-filled.
Growing up at the Hengyang Sect,
I was fed and clothed
by the clan.
No one ever made me breakfast
or fixed clothes for me.
What I'm trying to say is that
you're benevolent, Miss Mo.
They are just some basic life skills
that I've learned in the past.
In the past?
Mm, I've been married before.
I gave up everything for him,
but now he's out of my life.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I live alone.
I have long moved on.
He and I were once a family.
What we used to have,
they're memories I hold dear.
And I always will.
Life is full of challenges, Mr. Gongye.
If you ever need someone to talk to,
you're welcome over here for a meal
or a cup of tea.
I'm always here.
[CLEANSING AND HEALING]
Whoo!
Hmm,
the Water-splashing Festival
is still full of smiles and excitement
after all these years.
Whoo!
[The witch pointed at him.]
[She chose him as the Devil God.]
Bravo!
Move along.
Come on.
It's Teleportation Array.
Young Chief.
Shoot.
Chief brought
some disciples to Hengyang Sect today.
The disciples who went said
Li Susu and Cang Jiumin from Xiaoyao Sect
are not there.
I was told that they'd gone to Jing.
They didn't bring anyone else.
Cang Jiumin and Li Susu?
Good.
How dare they play me like a monkey?
Pick some men
with higher level of cultivation.
Bring enough artifacts.
And come with me.
All right.
How dare you monsters
manifest yourself in broad daylight?
These mortals can neither see us
nor hear us.
So?
Isn't it interesting?
What do you want?
Relax.
We just want to have a chat with you.
Okay.
I'll chat with you.
Shall we go to another place?
No.
Let's do it right here.
If we go somewhere else,
I'm afraid you will slip off.
Young Chief,
what's the matter?
Something's wrong.
I feel something.
Cang Jiumin,
you get too comfortable
of being an immortal sect disciple.
Come with us.
The Demon Realm is your home.
After becoming the Devil God,
you'll know
what real power is.
I don't need
that kind of power.
You don't need it?
I forgot you're not the Devil God yet.
You have no idea
that your immortal sect lover
was almost devoured by us last night.
Without the Devil God's power,
you're just like them.
Tiny ants others can trample upon at will.
Are you going to make us kill her
before you regret
not accepting the power
of the Devil God sooner?
Give me the Shadow Pearl.
This look in your eyes
is kinda like him.
You came
just to tell me this?
Cang Jiumin.
There are only two paths before you.
If you're willing
to leave the immortal sect
and return to the Demon Realm,
we'll honor you as our lord
and pledge loyalty to you.
If you insist on staying
in the immortal sect,
your devil origin will expose
sooner or later,
By then,
you'll be on the chopping block,
subjected to their punishment.
Pledging loyalty to me?
Okay.
Since you want to regard me as your lord,
show me your sincerity.
What do you want us to do?
Kneel down.
It seems that
you don't really want me to be your lord.
After you return to the Demon Realm,
we'll naturally pledge loyalty ot you.
Really?
Just you wait patiently.
My lord, please come back
to the Barren Abyss with us.
Cang Jiumin, how dare you.
You're meeting demons in secret.
Stay put.
I'm going to catch him red-handed today.
I'll make my own decision
which path to take.
I appreciate your intention.
You may go now.
When the time comes,
I'll go to the Barren Abyss myself.
When the time comes?
When will it be?
Are you questioning me?
Did he pop out of nowhere?
Is it some kind of magic?
He suddenly appeared.
Out of the way.
Move.
Cang Jiumin,
I've got you.
If I tell the immortal sects
what happened today,
not only will you be ruined,
but you'll also be taken
to the Demon-subduing Platform
and beaten until your soul disperses.
What a useless Xiaoyao sect genius.
Be my dog.
Maybe I'll spare your worthless life.
Go away!
Murder!
Murder! Run! Run!
Run!
Go away now!
Go back to report it.
Go now.
I'm helping you.
If I don't kill them,
you'll be the one to die.
You're pushing your luck,
forcing me to deal with you the hard way.
Chief Cen,
thank you for sealing
the Bone-refining Seal.
This is Mi's magic weapon.
Why is it here?
Chief!
Bad news!
Young Chief was killed by Cang Jiumin!
Run! Run!
[Speed up the formation.]
[Dodge the devil sound.]
This immortal is protecting us!
Quickly hide behind the formation!
Stop.
Cang Jiumin,
do you really want to watch them die?
Si Ying.
My child.
Stop it.
Let go of her.
What do you want?
We can talk it out.
What?
You want to talk now?
It's too late.
My child.
Give it up.
You won't be able to stop us
with your cultivation prowess
and the speed of you wielding the sword.
The immortal sect disciple Cang Jiumin
whom you long to be
won't be able to save her.
Mother!
Besides,
she's not the only one
you need to save today.
Please let go of my child.
Now,
do you still think
you don't need that power?
Help!
On the count of three,
these people will all die.
Can you continue to be Cang Jiumin
with peace of mind
and watch them die?
[Since I joined the immortal sect,]
[I've always heard]
[people talking about the Devil God.]
[I'm worried that the person
they're talking about is me]
[And the person mentioned
in the prophecy is also me.]
Three.
[I'm scared.]
[I'm scared that I'll be exposed.]
[And they'll discover]
[I'm the devil fetus]
[wants to get rid of
in the immortal sect.]
Two.
[But you've changed me completely]
[and given me a chance to start over.]
[I'll never be contaminated
by the Devil God's power again.]
[I'll keep my word]
[for you.]
My child!
Mother!
One!
[Sorry.]
[I broke my word.]
♪Looking back, I see my fate unfold♪
♪All alone with my own obsession♪
♪I want to break free
from the endless night♪
♪If my wish is granted♪
♪I'm not afraid of being burnt like a fire
and be extinguished like smoke♪
♪In an instant,♪
♪Bright or dark, it's ever-changing♪
♪Looking back, I see my fate unfold♪
♪All alone with my own obsession♪
♪I want to break free
from the endless night♪
♪If my wish is granted♪
♪I'm not afraid of being burnt like a fire
and be extinguished like smoke♪
♪An instant♪
Run!
♪Reminiscing old dreams,
our pact in the mortal world♪
♪Futile love is locked
in the furrow between the brows♪
♪If no one is spared the woes of love♪
♪We don't regret the glance we exchanged♪
♪That capture our hearts♪
Run!
Mother, help me.
My child.
Let's go.
Come on.
[First, it's Bone-refining Seal,
then the God-slaughtering Crossbow.]
[You still want to deny
you're His Lordship's devil fetus?]
Si Ying,
hurry.
Instill devil energy into him
while his power is disintegrating.
If we can energize the evil bone,
His Lordship will come back.
[This is weird.]
[Why can't I feel the response
of the evil bone?]
[I won't let you have your way.]
Susu.
[Why?]
[Why is it in your body?]
[Ye Xiwu,]
[you risked your life]
[to seal the evil bone in your body.]
[No one]
[can know this secret.]
Let go of Lady of Spirituality.
He killed Chief Cen's son.
[Devil God,]
[You carried out a massacre
on four Continents and three Realms,]
[causing my wife to die miserably]
[and locking me in the Barren Abyss
for million years.]
[Your devil fetus is born into the world.]
[How can I believe he's innocent?]
[I won't be bewitched easily]
[by the devil fetus like Susu]
[and watch her made a grave mistake.]
[For Susu's sake,]
[I'll eliminate your devil fetus]
[at all cost.]
Blast it.
He clearly is His Lordship's devil fetus.
Why didn't the devil bone respond
after we instilled
our thousands of years of power into him.
Did we make a mistake?
Even if we did,
would His Lordship's Bone-refining Seal
and God-slaughtering Crossbow
make a mistake?
But
so many mortals have died.
Cang Jiumin will definitely get
into big trouble.
Why don't we go to Hengyang Sect
to find out what happen.
Let's go.
It was a sunny day.
But the minute we set foot on
Demon Subduing Peak, dark clouds gather.
That you don't know.
Demon Subduing Peak
gets a lot of thunders all year round.
Look, that Demon-subduing Pillar
will direct thunder to the offender.
What crime did Cang Jiumin commit?
It's such a big fuss.
I heard he colluded with demons
to slaughter mortal people
and killed Chief Cen's son.
As an immortal sect disciple,
isn't it a heinous crime
to collude with demons?
Isn't Cang Jiumin
Immortal Zhaoyou's favorite disciple?
Does Chief Zhaoyou have something
to do with it?
I don't think so.
I heard from the seniors of Xiaoyao Sect
that Brother Cang is an upright person.
Perhaps it's a misunderstanding.
Maybe.
Yeah.
Jiumin.
Master.
Jiumin,
I just want to ask you.
Did you do it?
No.
Okay.
I trust you.
Chief Cen loses his son in his old age.
He is devastated.
He wants to convict and punish you.
I'm afraid he won't spare you.
Master,
I've caused trouble to Xiaoyao Sect.
I'm sorry.
There's justice in the world.
I believe
truth will speak for itself.
Master.
How is Susu?
[She's attacked
by a large amount of evil energy.]
[She hasn't woken up.]
Susu has pure spirit body.
Why is there so much evil energy
accumulating in her body?
Lady Susu is unconscious.
And Chief has been summoned
to Xiaoyao Sect.
Master,
what should we do?
She is fine for now.
But the evil energy in her body
can't be expelled.
I don't know when she'll come round.
Those stupid Taoists.
As expected, they started blaming him
without investigating the truth.
He brought it upon himself.
Had he minded his own business
at the Water-splashing Festival,
he wouldn't have ended up like this.
Cang Jiumin,
you killed my son in Capital of Jing,
injured my disciples,
and hurt innocent people.
Do you admit to your crimes?
I didn't kill him.
The murderers are Chixiao Sect disciples,
demoness Si Ying,
and the evil cultivator, Jing Mie.
Cang Jiumin is determined
to be an immortal sect disciple,
We should just let him suffer
so he'll know that
he's taken a wrong path.
You unrepentant lad.
What's done is done,
yet you're still arguing.
This is the proof.
I'll see how you're going
to defend yourself.
Everyone,
please watch.
[My lord,]
[please go back
to the Barren Abyss with us.]
[To go or to stay,]
[I'll make my own decision.]
[I appreciate your intention.]
[You may go now.]
[When the time comes,]
[I'll go to the Barren Abyss again.]
[When will the time comes?]
[Cang Jiumin, how dare you?]
[I've got you.]
[If I tell the immortal sects
about what happened today.]
[not only will you be ruined tomorrow,]
[but you'll also be taken
to the Demon-subduing Platform]
[and beaten until your soul disperses.]
[Go away!]
He really killed Cen Mi.
It's really Jiumin.
He killed Young Chief.
It's him.
He colluded with demons
and killed his fellow disciple.
What's going on?
Is that really Jiumin
in the Shadow Pearl?
I feel so bad for Young Chief.
We can't let go of the culprit.
Did you all see it?
If my son hadn't exposed him today,
I'm afraid the immortal sects
would've been in the dark,
unaware that Xiaoyao Sect
is harboring a demon.
In the Immortal Sect Competition,
I thought it was strange that
the two demons were able
to sabotage our plan
which was only revealed
to the Chiefs of different sects.
It turns out that
there's a mole in the immortal sects.
Chief Cen,
before the truth is uncovered,
How could you assert
my disciple is a devil?
Jiumin.
Don't let this bother you.
What was happening
at that time?
At that time,
[Si Ying and Jing Mie stopped me in the city.]
[They wanted me as their leader.]
[I rejected them.]
Nonsense.
The two devils are second to none
in the Demon Realm.
Why would they degrade themselves
to take you, a beginner,
as their leader?
Does anyone believe it?
No…
I don't believe.
It's impossible.
Who would believe it?
We don't.
We don't believe it.
If the immortal sect
wouldn't tolerate him,
we can take him back to Barren Abyss.
Look at this!
the god of heaven is
getting justice for me!
Cang Jiumin.
Today,
I'll make you pay with your life
for my son's death.
Stop.
We're interrogating him today,
not punishing him.
Don't be so domineering.
Chief Qu.
Your daughter is injured by the bastard
and is still at stake.
How could you speak for him?
Of course, I'm heartbroken for her injury.
But today we need to find out the truth
and then make the punishment
fit his crime.
It might be a long time before Susu wakes up.
We can't just wait, doing nothing.
I'm here to take care of Susu.
You go to Demon Subduing Peak
to see what the situation is.
Yes.
Yue Ya.
Why did that happen?
I heard about an attack
by a devil weapon in Capital of Jing.
They caught Cang Jiumin
and is punishing him
on Demon Subduing Peak.
Demon Subduing Peak.
[It's bad.]
[My Lord's identity has been known.]
We've witnessed
him doing the crime.
What do we need to investigate for?
Seeing is not believing.
There are only traces of his shadow
in Shadow Pearl.
We don't know the whole story.
There were many citizens present.
We can find them and ask them about it.
We'll see if the truth is as Chief Cen thinks.
That's right.
We can't be so arbitrary.
It's a matter of life and death.
We have to be careful.
Yeah.
I feel sorry for your loss of your son.
But you can't
convict my disciple of death,
based on this evidence.
It's a vain hope.
You…
[Sorry, my lord.]
[I didn't expect to get you into this.]
Who may you be?
It's bad.
Di Mian has come.
This old bastard
might have known the devil fetus is here.
What do we do?
Should we get him back?
You and I have not yet
recovered our energy.
They're too many
for us to fight.
Let's wait.
Chief Qu.
[Why did he come?]
It has been years.
How have you been?
Thank you for your concern.
I'm fine.
Everyone.
This is Lord of Evil
who helped to destroy Devil God
and made great contributions
thousands of years ago,
Di Mian.
When I was injured
and fell into Barren Abyss,
he saved me.
Lord of Evil is actually still alive.
After Devil God was destroyed,
I had been sealed in the Barren Abyss
and been tortured.
The barrier has loosened recently,
so I got away
with all my strength.
What can we do for you?
Lord of Evil.
I had gone wrong before,
having followed Devil God for many years.
As a result, I lost my wife.
Since then,
I swear to be sworn against Devil God.
I came here
to prevent Devil God from being reborn
and bringing disasters.
Boy.
Your identity as the devil fetus
has finally been known.
What?
Did I hear that right?
How can it be?
The devil fetus?
Cang Jiumin is the devil fetus!
No wonder the two devils
want him as their leader.
Yeah.
How can it be?
It makes sense now.
He's actually the devil fetus.
I'm not.
Of course, you're not Devil God,
because Devil God has died.
You shouldn't be alive.
Only if you're dead,
Devil God will never be reborn,
and all disasters will come to an end.
I found the firm evidence
that you're the devil fetus.
Just as I thought,
everyone,
God-slaughtering Crossbow
is on him.
What?
God-slaughtering Crossbow has showed up!
God-slaughtering Crossbow!
It's a devil weapon that didn't appeared
in the past ten thousand years.
God-slaughtering Crossbow!
Why is he keeping the weapon of Devil God?
It's really unexpected.
Who's he on earth?
God-slaughtering Crossbow!
I detected it!
It's God-slaughtering Crossbow!
God-slaughtering Crossbow is on him!
Jiumin.
This is no trivial matter.
You need to be honest
Don't be forced a confession.
Master.
God-slaughtering Crossbow
is on me indeed.
How come God-slaughtering Crossbow is on Jiumin?
He admitted it himself.
This is awful.
Is he really…?
Whether he's guilty or not,
dispose of him before he becomes
a real problem.
Yes.
Kill him…
I won't become Devil God.
I didn't kill anyone
with God-slaughtering Crossbow.
I didn't kill anyone.
Devil God still exists.
Devil God won't be dead forever
unless all the lives are killed and
hatred and bitterness disappeared.
[Ruo Water is where
all the primordial spirits return to.]
[That's why Devil God picked Yiyue Tribe.]
He made a contract with them
and gave them the responsibility
of bearing and raising the demon fetus.
You
tell us.
What's your relationship
with the Yiyue Tribe?
Yiyue Tribe
is my home tribe.
What?
He admitted it!
It's really terrifying.
Right.
How are you to explain yourself now?
I don't care whether Devil God
made a contract with Yiyue Tribe.
Whatever my destiny is,
I'll choose to be
righteous or evil on my own.
I
will never become Devil God.
Won't you?
Let me tell you another secret.
On the day when Devil God
made the contract with Yiyue Tribe…
Lord.
If that day has come,
how can we identify the devil fetus?
Evil Bone is a secret
and not easy to be detected.
[My fetus]
[will surely be out of the ordinary.]
[I heard the mortal people like
to make up stories.]
[I'd like to learn from them]
[and make up his fate.]
[Jin.]
[He'll kill his mother before birth.]
[He grows in an imperial palace]
[but is left out and be bullied.]
He's a monster.
Bark, like a dog.
Bark…
Coward.
You don't dare to resist.
Beat him.
Even a dog can bite and fight.
You good-for-nothing.
[He'll be a king.]
Your Majesty.
[and be on top of everything.]
[When he's riding high]
[and experience the world,]
[he'll hit the bottom]
[and face betrayal and resentment.]
[Although he has ascended to the throne]
[and expanded the territory,]
[he'll face a fratricidal struggle]
[and his wife turning on him.]
[He'll taste all bitterness.]
[Tantai Jin.]
Kill me now.
[I'll curse you and laugh at you]
every day.
Ye Xiwu!
Kill me!
No.
Stop saying that…
[They're the closest people in your life.]
[Whatever he does,]
[it'll be in vain.]
[All beautiful things]
[in his life are illusions.]
[What he loves or pursues for]
[will disappear.]
[Suffering is the truth for him.]
Ye Xiwu.
Speak!
[He'll lose everything.]
[It's not enough.]
[He'll join an immortal sect.]
[He thinks he has taken a right road.]
[He feels the warmth
from his master and fellows]
[but he'll find it's an illusion.]
[In the end,]
[he'll kill his master
and become a devil.]
[What do you]
[think of]
[the story? Di Mian.]
No.
Tantai Jin.
Are you still
insisting you're not the devil fetus?
It turns out
all that I've suffered
has been arranged.
Everyone.
He doesn't deny it.
We can conclude
that what I've told
is true.
Do you want to see him
kill his master and become a devil
and to regret later?
Whether it's true or not,
he must die if he's a devil.
Yes, he must die!
We must kill him.
Will he really bring a terminal disaster
as predicted?
I can't believe
the devil fetus has been
around us.
There are inarguable proofs.
[Taintai Jin.]
[Have you felt that?]
[Suspicion.]
[Fear.]
[Hatred.]
[Disappointment.]
[Are you feeling cold?]
[The coldness extended to your fingertips.]
[Do you find it hard to explain?]
[I made you experience in mortal world]
[and made you learn to love]
[just for today,]
[because I want you
to better experience all of this.]
The thunder is booming more frequently.
Is the thunder
attracted by the demon fetus?
It's the will of Heaven.
It's the will of Heaven!
Demon-subduing Pillar of Xiaoyao Sect
has been standing for hundreds years.
Today we'll use it
to judge you, Cang Jiumin.
We'll see
if it'll let go of you, the devil fetus.
Come here.
Take Cang Jiumin up there.
[Look at these people.]
[Would anyone]
[really care who you are?]
[In their eyes,]
[you're always the devil fetus.]
[You tried to fit into them]
[and imitated them,]
[but in the end,]
[what's your result?]
[How pathetic you are!]
[Would they let go of you because of]
[any word you said]
[or anything you did?]
You rebellious disciple.
You've lost control of yourself.
Now.
Kill them first.
Don't hesitate,
or they'll kill you.
Immortal Zhaoyou.
Are you still protecting your disciple?
Kill him!
Kill him and save the three realms.
This is a winning trade.
Trade?
Chief Cen is talking about a trade.
Is Chief Cen
Jiumin is our brother.
avenging his son's death?
-I can't do this.
-Yeah.
Let's stop and get this clear.
The evidence is certain.
What are you hesitating about?
The fact is a fact,
but you're still protecting the devil fetus.
What's your purpose?
Everyone.
Facing the devil,
we can't be soft-hearted!
Help me kill the devil!
Cang Jiumin.
I still have trust in you.
Control your mind.
[Master.]
[Right.]
[I have my master.]
[My master still trusts me.]
[I can't let him down.]
Demon-subduing Pillar is moving violently.
You have nothing to say now, don't you?
You've witnessed this.
Cang Jiumin is the devil fetus.
Kill him…
Don't let go of the devil fetus.
Kill him.
Kill him…
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪