The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 39]
The world is in turmoil,
all ages share the same sorrow.
[Why did you come back?]
[Interesting.]
[The sweetheart of his bitter life came.]
Are you here to kill me?
No.
I am here to listen to you
tell me the reason for doing these things.
At first you swore to me that
you would not become the Devil God.
I believed it without doubt.
But why have things become like this now?
Tell me.
[Because I hate you.]
Five hundred years ago,
I married you,
and I was willing to
share the world with you,
but you betrayed me on the wedding day
and wanted to kill me.
Later,
I searched for you
in the Nether River for 500 years.
Day after day,
my body was eroded beyond recognition
and I felt pain all over my body.
As for you,
you became an immortal
in the Heaven Lake on Mount Changze,
indifferent to the affairs of the world.
In the end,
you just said lightly that
you deceived me,
concealed from me,
hurt me and tried to kill me,
all for the sake
of the people of the world.
Do you think
I can forgive you just like that?
Do you think this is fair?
Didn't you say
you wanted to reverse destiny
and prevent the Devil God
from destroying the three realms?
Look at all this now,
these are all your retributions,
as well as Ye Xiwu's.
You once said that
I was born as the Devil God.
In my heart,
hatred is always deeper than love.
Tantai Jin,
you are lying.
Li Susu,
stop acting smart.
[Kill her!]
[And then you can end this damned destiny.]
[And then you can truly become me!]
[Tantai Jin, go ahead!]
[The Devil God…]
[My hand!]
She is the daughter
of Di Mian and Chu Huang,
A stupid woman and a traitor
wouldn't make a good breed.
Tantai Jin,
she used the Mirror of the Past
to come to your side
in order to kill you.
She's here to save me.
You are already the Devil God,
and why do you need salvation?
Kill her!
Kill her
and you won't feel any pain anymore.
[Kill her! Do it!]
[What are you hesitating about?]
[Kill her!]
She's about to die,
but you are still trapped here by me,
not able to do anything.
Tantai Jin,
since your birth,
anyone who had anything to do with you
all became unfortunate.
What were their names again?
I don't quite remember.
The Yiyue woman that gave birth to you,
your father that hated your guts,
the lowly maids that served you,
and your friend.
Of course,
there was also that grey-haired old man
who taught you boring stuff.
I think he was the most interesting.
Do you know what's so interesting about him?
I think his donkey was the most interesting,
and I really wanted to ride it.
They were all tiny ants.
How could they compare with me
and be worthy of your high regard?
Their misfortune was destined.
The world never really loved you.
Only suffering and misfortune
are your eternal destination.
Come here, Tantai Jin.
Come to me,
and then you can rule everything.
No.
Susu,
wait for me for a little longer.
You are wrong.
My mother was beautiful and kind,
but unfortunately she was chosen by you
and gave birth to the devil fetus.
But she loved me selflessly,
even more than her own life.
My father
gave me flesh and blood.
Although he had abused me
because of my mother's death,
I still believe that
when I was in my mother's womb,
he must have sincerely
looked forward to my birth.
All his life,
he deeply loved my mother.
Jin Lan'an and Yingxin
did their best to protect me
and take care of me growing up
under the most difficult circumstances.
Xiao Lin
was my enemy in political affairs,
but as a friend
he never let me down.
I had always owed him.
My master
Immortal Zhaoyou
saved me in Ruo Water.
Knowing my unfortunate background,
he still taught me day and night,
giving me rebirth.
Needless to say,
Susu risked her life to save me
and pull me out of hell.
It was she who taught me how to love
and feel all the emotions.
It was she
who broke through the darkness
again and again
and helped me to see the light.
You see,
although I did not receive much love,
I did not receive none.
The only one who pities himself,
resents himself
and wants to destroy everything
had always been you.
Tantai Jin,
you are so ridiculous.
You have already ascended to the top,
yet you are still lingering
in the dust and weeds of the mortal world.
Since you are
so unwilling to become the Devil God,
then
I can only do it myself.
You are me.
This is your only destiny.
Is the Devil God getting stronger again?
I… I think so.
This oppression,
I'm almost breathless.
[Looks like he is about to
become the Devil God.]
♪Meteors as loud as fire♪
♪Heartbeats from the abyss♪
♪Break through the torment
in the long night♪
♪Slash the darkness and embrace the dawn♪
♪Against the glowing of all stars♪
[What?]
♪Burn everything
to pierce the obstruction♪
♪Tear open the wounds of clouds and sky
We fight in songs till the universe darkens♪
Now,
it's my turn.
♪Go ahead and use my body
to block the enemies♪
No way.
They are my heart,
my bones, and my eyes.
Why don't they respond to my summons?
♪Even if there's only a glimmer of hope♪
♪Even if there's only a beam of light♪
♪I'll burn out this little energy in me♪
I have experienced the three lives
of man, god and demon,
but you,
you are stuck in the karma of the past.
There will always be
one and only Devil God in this world.
Now,
I am the Devil God.
[Tantai Jin,]
[no matter you become me]
[or I become you,]
[the result is the same.]
[You are the only Devil God now.]
[Only the true God
can destroy the Devil God.]
[And the true God…]
[My betrothed wife is Chu Huang,]
[the last god of the Phoenix Clan.]
[The Phoenix clan is naturally suitable
for cultivating the Heartless Way,]
[which is a shortcut to becoming a god.]
[Susu…]
[Heartless Way…]
I understand now.
So,
this is the only way out.
Announce to the four continents,
three days later
I will marry
the most pure and flawless
Lady of Spirituality from Mount Changze.
Tell the various immortal sects
that if they want to come
and congratulate me,
I will open the gate of the Demon Realm
and let them in.
Congratulations, the Devil God!
[Groom: Cang Jiumin
Bride: Li Susu]
The Devil God forcibly marrying Susu
is clearly to humiliate our Hengyang Sect
and the immortal sects.
However, at that time,
the gate of the Demon Realm will be open.
We can take advantage
of the Devil God's arrogance
and join forces to kill him.
Yes!
We cannot stand by and watch
Lady of Spirituality be so insulted.
Chief Gongye,
Our Xiaoyao Sect will fully support you
to organize immortal sects.
That's right, Gongye.
The elders of the immortal sects
have all been murdered.
Only you can reunite the immortal sects.
We have no time to hesitate any longer.
If we miss this opportunity
to go deep into the Barren Abyss
and kill the devil,
[Calm The Mind, Clarify The Spirit]
there will be no chance
to turn the table around in the future.
[It is only three days before]
[Tantai Jin forcibly marries Susu.]
[With my current strength,]
[I am no match for him at all.]
Master, is this the Demon-Sealing Cliff?
Since the founding of the Hengyang Sect,
the ancestors have laid out formations here
to imitate the Barren Abyss
and seal and refine demons.
Master,
if we use the evil way
to counter the evil,
will it work?
The power of evil
destroys your mind and spirit.
We must not be contaminated by it.
Even if the original intention
is to use evil fight evil,
after going awry,
one will not be able to distinguish
between the enemy and the ally.
In this way,
one will be otherwise bewitched
by the devil energy
and become a puppet of the devil.
[I can't care so much anymore.]
[Tantai Jin,]
[you are my sworn enemy.]
[I will die with you and drag you to hell!]
Susu, when you wake up,
you will surely hate me to the bone.
I promised you
that I would not let
your nightmares happen again.
But now
I have no choice.
At the wedding 500 years ago,
you pierced soul-slaying spikes
into my heart with your own hands.
This time
I hope you can be
as resolute as you were back then.
[Nian Baiyu,]
[I once promised you
to save the Yiyue tribe.]
[Now]
[I can finally fulfill my promise]
[to you and the tribe.]
[As the chief of the Yiyue tribe,]
[this is the only]
[and the last thing I can do for you.]
Lord!
[Judging from the situation
outside the barrier,]
[the negative energy
has become heavier again.]
[This is…]
[Lord's messenger crow.]
Come out!
Now that the Devil God is revived,
do you have any way
to help me kill the Devil God?
Someone asked me to give you this
Celestial Punishment Great Array.
[Celestial Punishment Great Array?]
[Everything is settled well.]
Stop struggling.
Where are you?
I am already the Devil God,
so everywhere, of course.
Congrats, Li Susu.
Tomorrow you will ride this Dragon Float
and become the Devil God's wife.
The Devil God's wife?
Yes.
Five hundred years ago,
we had gotten married twice.
In Bo're Life, Ming Ye married Sang Jiu too.
But this time, it will be different.
The one who marries you
is the Devil God himself.
To marry you,
this treacherous and traitorous devil,
would be the shame of my eternal life.
I would rather die now.
I am the Devil God.
Li Susu,
as long as your primordial spirit lives on,
the entanglement of us will never end.
Li Susu,
why don't you just save your strength?
Never mind.
The wedding is near.
From now on,
you will no longer have your freedom.
Before this,
is there anywhere that you want to go?
Let me think.
Is it this place?
Why do you bring me to the Mohe River?
No reason.
We are here
when I think of here.
Sit with me for a minute.
Do you still remember Sang Jiu and Ming Ye?
I've been thinking lately.
The war of gods and demons were so grand.
Compared with it,
the love between the two of them
was so tiny.
If not for the Bo're Life,
I'm afraid no one in the coming generations
would remember this forgotten memory.
Such heart-wrenching love
perished so easily in the sands of time.
This shows
how insignificant
and ridiculous
love is.
But,
I'm different from Ming Ye.
I'll be on the highest peak soon.
You have to
stay by my side.
Stop using fancy words on yourself.
Ming Ye is a legitimate God of War
in the Shangqing Realm.
Although he did fail Sang Jiu,
he countered the ancient Devil God.
He did enough for the world
and for everyone in it.
Compared with him,
you're too greedy
and indifferent to others' lives.
A person like you
doesn't get to comment on their love at all.
Never mind.
Now that we're here,
I'll take you to see another thing.
This is…
Ye Mansion from capital of Sheng.
That's right.
It's been 500 years.
Now in the ruins of the capital of Sheng,
this mansion doesn't exist since long ago.
You can take it as my Bo're Life.
A barrier created by me.
A place that doesn't exist.
Tantai Jin,
if you really have nothing to hold dear
and decided to be the Devil God,
then why do you…
I just think it's interesting.
Look.
The Mohe River flows on and on.
It seems to be changing all the time.
But it seems to have never changed, too.
I'm thinking,
when love perishes,
hatred perishes,
and our physical bodies perish,
how can we prove that these emotions
really existed once?
Will the story between us
be known by posterity?
You're already the invincible Devil God,
why fear perishing anyway?
Of course I don't.
I'm just curious.
If others become you and me in the Bo're Life,
how would they feel?
For Ye Xiwu and Tantai Jin
from 500 years ago
the Devil God and Li Susu
have already become your so-called others.
Really?
Seems to make sense.
Come on.
Go watch with me.
Miss, there you are!
I've been looking for you.
Chuntao,
I…
Miss,
you're wearing so little on such a cold day.
If grandma knows about it,
she'll definitely scold me.
-Take this thermal jug to warm your hand.
-Sister!
Sister!
Brother, where are you going like this?
I'm gonna go hunting with Cui Shisan and others.
If dad asks about me,
tell him I went to school.
The rabbit fur is the softest in this season.
I'll make fur gloves for you and grandma.
They're gonna be super warm.
Go ahead. Be careful.
Got it!
[Dad.]
[Qingyu.]
Great spear moves!
Of course. You're still too young.
When you can undertake a military task alone…
Sister.
Buttercup.
Dad.
Why aren't you home until now?
Grandma…
Grandma's been waiting for you.
Nobody's words worked on her.
She won't eat without you.
Do you know how many times we warmed the dishes?
Look at you.
Buttercup!
Grandma.
Look at you.
You didn't eat your meals properly.
And you're still wearing so little.
It's gonna snow outside,
but you're still running around out there.
Grandson-in-law, you're to blame, too.
He can't just let you do whatever do like.
You've been like this all year round.
Yes, Grandma.
I'll definitely take good care of Xiwu.
That's more like it.
This is my most precious daughter.
She's been my everything since little.
You gotta take good care of her.
Don't let her suffer a tiny bit at all.
Understood.
General Ye,
after I marry Xiwu,
I'll definitely see her as my precious
and I will never let her feel wronged.
That's what I'm talking about.
No, I'm just…
Knock it off.
Stop scaring him like this all day long.
No, I'm just teasing him.
You…
Come on.
You two, come inside and have dinner.
Come.
Let's go.
Come on. Let's eat.
What exactly are you up to?
In this Ye Mansion,
there's no evil bone
nor Devil God.
I'm just your husband.
How do you like it?
This is the Bo're Life in your mind?
What?
You don't like it?
You're the Devil God,
but why would you like this happy mortal life?
You're not me.
How do you know what life the Devil God likes?
These are the poor quality firecrackers
from the new year's eve of that year.
You know what?
I made a wish to the fireworks,
hoping that you wouldn't be the Devil God.
But now I regret loving you.
I even regret wasting that sketch.
That sketch?
It's worth wasting one for the new year.
I was being naive.
I actually believed a stone-like person
will grow a heart.
It's just a sketch.
With the power I have now,
I can show you any wonderful scenery
in this world.
Ye Xiwu.
Are you this happy on every new year's eve?
This year is a bit different.
But I'm still happy.
Don't worry. With me by your side,
nobody's gonna bully you again.
We can be happy like this every year.
Li Susu,
it was clearly me
who was lied to.
When you taught me to draw the sketch,
you knew it clearly.
My words count.
I'm here to do what I promised you of course.
What should I teach you?
The type that can repel crows
like you used at Xiao Lin's mansion.
Not that one.
You're an amateur.
What if you blow up the house
when you accidentally draw it wrong?
Whatever the case,
I won't be able to draw it,
right?
What the sketch sees
is the purest and most beautiful things.
Your body, heart and will are the three keys.
When the three unite, your cultivation is good.
Keep your heart humble,
keep your body quiet,
and keep your will steady.
This is how you unite them.
You can only make it
when you're free of evil intentions.
I knew this was very difficult for you.
But I did hope that
you could make it.
♪I've searched endlessly
in hopes of meeting you in this life♪
Does it look pretty?
What a shame. The nice sceneries
are just like this firework show.
Splendid but short.
♪A journey ends in an instant♪
♪Life is short, but a dream lasts forever♪
♪I've searched endlessly
in hopes of meeting you in this life♪
After tomorrow's wedding,
will you kill me?
♪A drop of tear♪
♪But a dream lasts forever♪
That depends on my mood.
There is
really no turning back,
is there?
We're already here.
How do you want me to go back?
Then tonight,
I should bid farewell to you.
♪Writing to someone from my past
the twelfth spring has passed♪
♪All things flow away♪
[Sang Jiu,]
[you have something to say to me?]
♪A path longer than time♪
[Before I leave,]
[you still owe me something]
[that should be mine.]
[What is it?]
[It's the wedding night that you owe me.]
♪Now I know what my dream means♪
♪Wandering from place to place
not knowing where I belong♪
♪I have no place to call home♪
♪Nothing lasts forever♪
♪I can't ask for more♪
♪It's an ordinary life♪
♪It's an ordinary song♪
♪We can only understand that
we will never understand it♪
♪Homeless but shows nothing on the face♪
♪How many people are laughing♪
♪While staring at their wine cups in silence♪
♪Nothing lasts forever♪
♪I can't ask for more♪
♪It's an ordinary life♪
♪It's an ordinary song♪
I know.
What I'm gonna do next
will be extremely cruel to you.
But Susu,
don't blame me.
When all of this ends,
at least you still have the dream in the pearl
for you to think of
from time to time.
[The day's about to break.]
[There's still time to do something useless.]
Tantai Jin?
Stop running!
Why do you come here?
Are you here to take me back to the demon realm?
Why are you crying?
I just suddenly thought
from the first time I saw you
to leaving the Sheng Kingdom,
it's actually always winter.
And there's only winder in this memory barrier.
What a shame.
Goddess Yuling,
there's no time for you to pity the season.
Let's go.
The hour of the wedding is arriving.
Everyone,
since Tantai Jin is so arrogant
as to open the gate of demon realm
on the day of his wedding,
then we can't waste this chance.
Has anyone heard of
the Celestial Punishment Array?
Is it the array the gods used to injury
the Devil God in the war of celestial pillars
from 10,000 years ago?
But his array has long been lost.
It's only been used once
in the war of gods and demons.
But Sect Leader Gongye, how did you get it?
Yeah, Sect Leader Gongye.
Please don't forget
Hengyang Sect is the No. 1 sect.
There's nothing strange about it.
The twelve gods all fell before activating it.
How can we do the same?
This won't be a problem.
As long as you're willing to join hands,
I'll have a way to activate the array.
Sect Leader Gongye,
whatever the outcome,
Xiaoyao Sect is willing to work with you.
Great. Then please inform the other sects
about what we discussed today.
It's purely up to them as to whether they're
willing to participate in the rehearsal.
When tomorrow comes,
I will go to the demon realm with you all
and fight with the Devil God!
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪