The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 35]
You've witnessed this.
Cang Jiumin is the devil fetus.
Kill him.
Kill him…
[Tantai Jin,]
[you may have gotten rid of the evil bone,]
[you may have chosen a virtuous path,]
[but none of that made any difference.]
[You were born evil.]
[The Demon-subduing Pillar won't spare you!]
[There's no place for you here!]
[No matter what you do,]
[you cannot escape your fate!]
Jiumin,
wake up!
Stay focused!
Immortal Zhaoyou,
are you seriously
still defending him?
Most of the mortals were injured
by the demonic weapon.
It would take more than
Si Ying and Jie Mie for that to happen.
If it wasn't him who summoned the weapon
and unleashed hell on the mortals,
who else could it have been?
His companion, Li Susu?
[Xiwu…]
[you actually went out on a limb]
[and trapped the evil bone in your body.]
[No one]
[can know about this]
[Susu…]
Jiumin,
I'm going to ask you again.
Was it you who wounded the mortals
using the demonic weapon?
I…
[They can't find out that]
[the evil bone is inside Susu's body.]
[I'm destined for suffering.]
[And I should be the one to bear it all.]
Yes.
With the God-slaughtering Crossbow.
That's absurd!
How did an evil man like him
end up being part of the Xiaoyao Sect?
Why did you do that?
I thought…
Cang Jiumin, the immortal cultivator,
can't save this little girl.
And there are more sufferers to come.
I could take control of myself…
I thought…
One!
I could change my destiny…
You can't save them.
and choose my own path in life…
[If the Devil God is the only one
who can make this all stop…]
[Xiwu,]
[I'm sorry…]
I overestimated myself.
I couldn't control my instincts.
[My baby girl!]
[I'm sorry.]
[If I am fated]
[to become the Devil God…]
Just…
go on and kill me.
Cang Jiumin,
you will pay for my son's death with blood!
Hang on.
He is a cunning liar.
He still has the demonic weapon
and the evil bone.
We'll have to have them removed
and locked away with magical seals
before he can be annihilated.
Otherwise, killing him
will cause the evil bone's energy to peak,
which will then revive the Devil God.
My fellow chiefs, we,
as highly accomplished cultivators,
could combine our powers
and force the crossbow out of him.
I'll do it.
No, I'll do it.
I'm in.
I want to be part of this.
Will Jiumin be able to hold out against them?
[It is the Devil God's Eye,
the God-slaughtering Crossbow.]
[What is this place?]
[It's thick with devil energy.]
Susu,
wake up!
[Why am I back to being Xiwu?]
[The evil bone has absorbed
a large amount of devil energy.]
[Now it's fighting
against your pure spirit body.]
[You've got to contain it]
[before it goes out of control.]
[That was Chongyu.]
[It woke me up.]
[I did not kill anyone with
the God-slaughtering Crossbow.]
[I'm innocent!]
[That was Jin.]
[The devil energy seems to be able]
[to sense him.]
[It's so foggy here.]
[I can't even see what's ahead.]
[I have hard evidence
of you being the devil fetus.]
[Oh no,]
[Jin's true identity has been revealed.]
[He's in danger.]
[I am not the Devil God.]
This is a mistake!
It wasn't him!
[Gosh,]
[I have to get
to Demon Subduing Peak to save Jin.]
[He's been wrongly accused.]
[Chongyu,]
[what do I have to do to wake up?]
They're trying
to seize His Lordship's evil bone.
We must act now!
They will get their hands on it
over my dead body!
[Hang in there, Jin.]
[I will not let you die like this.]
Another one is coming.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪How funny, I used to be in shackles♪
♪Sealed alone under♪
♪The dome of destiny♪
♪Loneliness for tens of thousands of years♪
Susu.
♪Ah, living without love♪
[Great.]
[You're safe.]
Susu,
what are you…
Li Susu,
are you trying to defend this devil fetus?
Chief Cen,
Susu hasn't said anything yet.
Don't judge too soon.
Li Susu,
what exactly are you up to?
My fellow chiefs,
Cang Jiumin
can't become the Devil God.
Li Susu,
the identity of Cang Jiumin has been confirmed.
Considering that you're young and innocent,
I'll tell you again.
He is the devil fetus.
He secretly possesses
the God-slaughtering Crossbow.
Even if he's not the Devil God now,
he will some other day.
Even his admission into the sect
and changing of identity
are planned by the Devil God.
Susu,
Chief Cen is telling the truth.
Let me tell everyone another story.
Cang Jiumin,
formerly known as Tantai Jin,
is the king of Jing Kingdom from 500 years ago.
What?
Really? How could this be?
He's even a king?
Is that true?
He was indeed the devil fetus.
He's also the owner of the evil bone
chosen by the Devil God.
But whatever happens,
he will never become the Devil God.
Susu,
how do you know?
Li Susu,
you speak with such confidence.
How dare you jump to conclusions in front of us?
Aren't we all here
to find out the truth about this?
It won't hurt to listen to her.
Because 500 years ago…
No.
I've personally
extract his evil bone.
What?
Nonsense!
You think extracting the evil bone
is as easy as that?
Yeah.
You have no proof.
Why should we trust you?
Yeah, why should we trust you?
Why should we trust you? Never!
It's okay.
My fellow chiefs,
I know I can't persuade you
without presenting the proof.
I heard Chixiao Sect has an artifact
called the Truth Jade Slip.
It can extract the true memories
of anyone.
I beg you to use this artifact
to tell if I'm telling the truth.
No.
Susu,
don't do this.
This is the only way to tell
what I've been through
to everyone here.
I'd like
to have a try.
Li Susu,
let me see what excuses you can give us.
No.
Susu.
[Susu,]
[we're running out of time.]
[You have to go back now!]
[Then thousand years ago,]
[God of Time left the Light-breaking Array]
[for Xiaoyao Sect chiefs to inherit.]
[I will send you]
[back to Sheng Kingdom 500 years ago.]
[Going back]
[is our only chance.]
[Remember,]
[whatever you see, don't look back.]
[The four continents and three realms
are counting on you.]
[Understand?]
Tantai Jin,
I will definitely
kill you!
[So the truth is really like this.]
[So that's the truth]
[you wouldn't tell me all along.]
[You're most afraid of my death.]
[Yet you wanted me dead the most.]
[That's why you approached me]
[and tried to kill me.]
[Susu,]
[you've done so much for me]
[But I didn't know anything.]
[I didn't know why I'd do that.]
[It's not fatal.]
[I won't die for now.]
[Yingtian Gate]
[The lightning punishment is coming closer.]
[Now,]
[I've taken your evil bone]
[and returned you with my divine essence.]
[You won't be the Devil God anymore.]
What's going on?
I think I saw you guys
in the Truth Jade Slip.
I…
I've destroyed his evil bone
with the might of the lightning punishment.
He won't be the Devil God.
I've severed the fate
of the destined arrival of the Devil God.
This world
is safe now.
Susu,
so this is the whole truth.
You've returned to 500 years ago alone
and did so much for us.
Since I've extracted his evil bone,
this means the prophecy can be reversed.
We can't choose our birth,
but we can choose between good and evil.
Although Tantai Jin is the devil fetus,
he won't be the Devil God anymore.
Now,
the six soul-slaying spikes
should still be in Tantai Jin's heart.
And there's absolutely
no evil bone inside him.
Go ahead and check
if you don't believe.
Now,
everyone can be rest assured.
I don't care if he's Tantai Jin or Cang Jiumin,
he is the devil fetus!
Even without the evil bone,
he'll be seduced by demons sooner or later.
We can't afford another massacre.
Leaving him alive
will eventually bring disasters!
Being born as the devil fetus
isn't his fault.
Even if he's really born a devil,
we should give him a chance.
Punishing someone for
something he didn't do
is truly the disgrace of immortal sects!
My son died for no reason at all!
And you're still defending him?
It's Si Ying the she devil who killed Cen Mi.
Cang Jiumin forced himself
to activate the God-slaughtering Crossbow
in order to save civilians.
He's also injured for that.
Cang Jiumin used the God-slaughtering Crossbow
for saving the civilians?
Have we really wronged him?
Is… Is this real?
Thankfully we stopped in time.
Cang Jiumin is the devil fetus.
Are we just letting it go like this?
This is the rarest chance to stop
the Devil God from resurrecting again!
Chief Cen,
please be rest assured.
We will try everything we can
to kill Si Ying and Jing Mie
and do your son justice.
As for Cang Jiumin,
it's not his will to be born as the devil.
Not to mention in the emergency,
he chose to get hurt for saving the civilians.
There's no doubt about his kindness.
We cultivators must judge clearly.
Everyone,
the divine energy in our Hengyang Sect
can cleanse the devil energy
and suppress the evil things.
Why don't we put him under house arrest
in our sect
to see if he behaves better?
What do you think of this proposal?
This is a good idea!
Yeah.
With Chief Qu to watching him,
we'll be rest assured.
-Yeah.
-That's right.
Believing in demons
is no different from committing suicide!
I'll put my words in here!
You guys just wait and see!
Get to work!
No wonder the evil bone didn't react
to our devil energy in Jing capital last time.
The words of that little girl
can only fool the stupid cultivators.
No matter what trick they play,
the evil bone can never be destroyed.
Why did His Highness chose him
as the devil fetus anyway?
Not only did he offended His Highness,
he also lost the evil bone for a woman.
What do you know?
His Highness has his plans.
But this time,
we almost killed the devil fetus.
We should be more cautious next time.
Report!
My Lords,
we've found it!
After digging 500 years,
we've finally found it!
We've found the Devil Palace!
See?
His Highness's plan works in mysterious ways.
Devil Palace is where the Devil God was born.
With the palace,
wherever the evil bone is,
he'll return sooner or later.
[Without the evil bone,]
[the devil fetus will be worthless.]
[Let's see what plan can the two demons have]
[to revive the Devil God.]
[But the evil bone is missing now.]
[Where can it be hiding?]
Brother Di,
we have something to ask you.
It's about the things in Demon Subduing Peak?
That day, when I heard that Cang Jiumin
had summoned the God-slaughtering Crossbow,
I knew I couldn't hesitate anymore.
They're only short of the Sky-Slashing Sword
before they can revive the Devil God.
I have to tell the truth.
Otherwise,
if I hesitated a little,
it would be too late.
Then you should discuss with us beforehand
to let us be prepared.
If not for Susu's timely arrival,
Jiumin would've died on the peak.
I knew it's a reckless move,
but do you know how much I hate the Devil God
for sealing me ten thousand years?
Whenever I thought of Chu Huang
who was killed by the Devil God,
I'd lose my sanity out of hatred.
Thanks to this hatred,
I managed to hang on till now.
I'm here
not just to find my daughter whom I'd never met,
but also to help the immortal sects
to stop the Devil God from resurrection.
Please forgive me
if I offended you somewhere.
But after what happened on the peak,
we've given Jiumin
a chance to prove himself.
I won't be against him anymore.
I give you my word.
Forget it.
We're not here to hold you accountable today.
We actually need a favor from you.
Chief Cen,
we've asked from Lord of Evil
the method of sealing the demonic artifacts.
This God-slaughtering Crossbow is too dangerous.
Now let's seal it with the power of us three.
Nobody can open the box alone.
Chief Cen,
now you can be rest assured, huh?
It's already like this.
Anything I say would be pointless.
Cang Jiumin is a disciple of Xiaoyao Sect.
He'll be imprisoned in Hengyang Sect.
For the sake of fairness,
I think it's best
to let you take this crossbow
back to Chixiao Sect.
Mi,
[Memorial tablet of Loving Son Cen Mi]
I'm so useless.
Had I worked harder
and become the leader of all sects,
you wouldn't have died for no reason at all.
But today,
I've obtained this demonic crossbow.
This is a powerful artifact.
If it can be used by me,
Chixiao Sect will not be bullied by others.
Don't worry,
dad won't let you die in vain.
I want them to
pay with their blood!
[Raise your head.]
[Go ahead and pinch me.]
Nothing must be left.
Eat them all.
[It turns out,]
[since then,]
[it's you I've been seeing.]
[You protected me.]
[You're good to me.]
[You wanted to kill me.]
[But you're also afraid of me dying.]
[It's you all along.]
[It's a story lasting for 500 years.]
[And here we are now.]
[You saved me from distresses
despite the risks time and time again.]
[Thank you for doing so much for me.]
[I actually didn't know this until now.]
[Susu,]
why are you so silly?
This time it's my turn to protect you.
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
♪That's about to fall from the edge of the sky♪
♪I wanna hang a glittering butterfly there♪
You're awake.
♪I wanna hang it in a wrong time♪
Tantai Jin.
♪To forget my everything♪
It's okay. I'm okay now.
♪Hearts burn like flames♪
You're also okay now.
Everything's gonna be fine.
♪Why don't we just be like this
for ten thousand years?♪
The evil bone
♪Before we say goodbye♪
will not be destroyed at all.
It's on you,
isn't it?
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
There's no one else here
but you and me.
You don't need to hide anymore.
♪Even when my heart is torn in two♪
♪I won't fly away♪
How do you know?
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
That day in Capital of Jing,
you blocked the devil energy
from Si Ying and Jing Mie.
That black devil energy.
That horrible power.
I'm too familiar with it.
♪It can't be settled♪
I was carrying it since young.
The fire of heart burnt me every day.
Now it's in you.
Susu,
that thing is too dangerous.
I'm afraid…
Don't worry.
I have the dirtless divine body.
It's naturally against the devil energy.
I won't be contaminated by it.
But…
Tantai Jin,
I promise you
I will try to live as long as I can
and turn it into a sleeping secret forever.
Mount Changze is abundant in divine energy.
The evil bone won't wake up
if we stay here.
As for you, just recover your body first.
This way we can face together
any incident that's coming.
Is that okay?
Together.
♪Do you know a wise man♪
♪Does not fall in love?♪
Thank you.
You've been
so good to me all along.
But I didn't know that until today.
You're welcome.
Speaking of which, I must congratulate you.
You won't have to be worried anymore.
You can finally start anew openly.
As long as you're okay,
I don't care how others
treat me at all.
It's okay
even if they won't
accept me forever.
It doesn't matter.
You still have me.
At least I will always stand by your side.
That'll be enough.
♪Always remember before the flowers wither♪
Take a good rest.
♪Tried to change your mind with a kiss♪
♪Let's freeze love before it turns to dust♪
It's a complicated story.
Forgive me for not explaining it to you.
I used to have a friend who helped me a lot.
He looked exactly like you.
[I must find out who I am exactly]
[and who Xiao Lin is.]
[Do Susu and Jiumin]
[care about me or Xiao Lin?]
[What exaclty is real]
[and what exactly is fake?]
[Why are there no records?]
[Gongye Jiwu,]
[you can't be living without knowing the truth.]
Jiwu,
when it comes to life,
we're both trying to cross the river.
You can only have your answers when you
across the river by yourself.
However, you don't have to
turn every stone
in this river.
Master,
I'm not afraid to turn this stone.
I just don't want to be kept in the dark.
Master, please fulfill my wish.
Alright then.
Then I'm gonna tell you
your origin.
[Jiwu,]
[that's why you were born.]
[Good to you to go down the mountain
for a while.]
Just think of it
as a lesson you have to learn.
Just go.
[I believe]
[you will figure it out]
[one day.]
[Splendid Silk Workshop]
[If you get sad again,]
[come to have a meal]
and take some tea here.
I'll always be here for you.
[No.]
[Why do you come here?]
[Take advantage of a woman's kindness]
[to avoid the evil in your heart?]
Sir.
I thought
I'd never see you again.
I just happen to pass by.
You are here.
Why bother to cover it up?
I didn't know I was a doomsayer.
You have sad things so quickly.
Jixu,
can't you tell me about it?
What did you call me?
Jiwu.
Didn't you tell me
you're Gongye Jiwu.
Right,
right.
I'm Gongye Jiwu.
I am myself.
Jiwu,
stay here.
I'll be with you.
Can you be here with me?
Yes.
Jiwu,
I miss you so much.
The two devils of Barren Abyss
just vanished from the scene.
Four Continents and Three Realms
are rare to be calm.
As long as the Sky-Slashing Sword
can be found,
the prediction of the Devil God
being back to life
will have no chance to come true.
God-slaughtering Crossbow
and Bone-refining Seal have been sealed.
But would it really make sure
that everything is safe?
In case…
Two of the top three demonic weapons
have been sealed by far.
Besides,
the devil fetus has no evil bone now
and is under our immortal sect.
He settles down in Mount Changze.
This could be
the greatest achievement of all
for our anti-evil cause
over the five hundred years.
I think Lord of Evil is worrying too much.
Demonic weapons are very powerful.
I'm afraid
that Si Ying and Jing Mie
would get them again.
Then the world will suffer.
The demonic weapons have been sealed.
But Mount Changze is
in plain sight after all.
The enemy can hide but we can't.
It's not safe in the long term.
I'm distressed about it too.
Since Di Mian asks
and you've lurked
around the Devil God for years,
do you think there is a good way
to deal with it?
If any formations or spells
are more solid and extensive
than common guardian barriers…
Guardian barriers?
Zhaoyu,
Xiaoyao sect has a secret treasure,
the Heart-guarding Scale.
Is it available?
My sect has a formation.
We can use the infinite divine power,
refining and enlarging the magic weapon.
With this formation
and the advantage of
the Heaven and Earth as a great furnace
of Xiaoyao Sect,
perhaps the barrier Di Mian suggested
really works.
We indeed have this
Heart-guarding Scale.
But the chief gave it
to an outsider disciple
of the royal family of the Sheng
five hundred years ago.
It was a congratulations gift.
And then somehow
it was brought back by Immortal Buxu.
A few cracks have remained on it
which need to be repaired.
We can try the Formation of Melting.
But who should we send to go?
Let Jiumin go.
Dad,
Heart-guarding Scale
has a deep connection with Jiumin.
He is the best person to refine it.
So please let him go.
Ok.
We'll take your advice.
Jiumin will refine
the Heart-guarding Scale.
Master,
I don't understand.
Why am I the one with such a big job?
JiuMin,
the Heart-guarding Scale was refined
by Ming Ye back then.
You and Susu were in Bo're Life,
having experienced
the life of Ming Ye as a god.
So you're the best choice
to do this.
Yeah.
Me and your master
made the decision together.
We both believe in you.
Jiumin,
I'll leave it to you.
What do I do?
Hold it steady and find a way to melt it.
Listen carefully.
A voice will tell you how to do it.
But I hear nothing.
Not by your ears,
but by your heart.
Ming Ye.
Look, Hongnai Fruits are there.
Thank you, brother.
Look at it.
I get it.
I've been thinking wrong for so long.
I avoided my nature,
scared of the power I was born with,
and dreaded my origin
and the fate awaiting me.
But it's not about others.
It's all about me.
All of it can be used by my heart.
Today I find the answer.
I know
I am what I am.
JiuMin,
you are a devil fetus,
the seed of the Devil God.
But as long as your heart is
pure and bright,
and you believe in the goodness
of this world,
the Devil God won't awaken.
And the Four Continents and Three Realms
can be finally saved.
I've broken it through.
Yes.
You feared to indulge in your powers.
So, you couldn't break through.
What about now?
I'm not afraid anymore.
Jiumin,
Good or evil
has nothing to do
with being an immortal or a devil.
It's up to your heart.
Thank you, master.
Jiumin,
The Mountain Protecting Formation
has been completed.
And the Heart-guarding Scale
has a deep connection with you.
So, I'll leave it to you.
Jiumin,
something I wanna ask you.
Susu has the evil bone,
doesn't she?
What happened in Demon Subduing Peak
isn't obvious to the casual observer.
But how can Qu not know
what his own daughter's thought is?
He just doesn't wanna disclose it either.
If the evil bone could not be removed,
I'm afraid that Susu will have to
stay in Heaven Lake for her lifetime.
And are you willing to
to be here with her
forever?
Master,
the evil bone was in my body.
Susu suffers instead of me.
Even if I must stay in Hengyang Sect
for the rest of my life,
I won't regret it.
From now on,
I will watch over the evil bone with Susu.
All right. Ok.
Since you're willing to do this too,
just be at ease to stay in Hengyang Sect.
I've got a good disciple finally.
But you take advantage of it.
Somehow,
he becomes a live-in son-in-law
of Hengyang Sect.
It's a great loss of me!
Susu,
we just wanna know
if I survived that time.
I don't think so.
Well…
Susu…
Did I survive?
You seemed to be out on patrol
and eaten by a devil.
Eaten by a devil?
Thank you, Susu.
What about me?
Here he comes. Stop asking.
Go, go, go.
-Bye, Susu.
-Go, go!
-Go, go, go.
-Go, go.
Am I disturbing you?
There is nothing important.
Just a little chat.
Talking about the Devil God?
They're afraid of the Devil God, not you.
I know.
But,
only by getting rid of the Demon God,
can they feel at ease.
And only then,
I can be with you in the future.
I'll work with you.
I'll always be there for you.
Take it easy.
Li Susu, Lady of Spirituality,
or Cang Jiumin, a disciple of Xiaoyao Sect,
has plenty of time
to solve these problems later.
There will be ample time for us.
Ok.
Come on,
go with me to Heaven Lake for a walk.
Yes.
So Dad and the others already knew
the evil bone is in me.
So, it's not cleansing my devil energy
with the divine power of Heaven Lake.
This is all for you.
Tantai Jin.
Actually,
it's not too late for you to go away.
Where to go?
The world is so vast.
You can go anywhere.
Stuck in Mount Changze
for the rest of your life,
missing so much good scenery.
What a loss!
Remember you taught me this?
Sketch Spell?
The universe manifests in an inch of land.
The soul follows the mind.
Susu,
even if you stay in the Hengyang Sect
all the time,
I shall stay with you,
enjoying all the mountains and rivers
of this world
and sunsets and mornings.
No scenery is better than
being with you for all eternity.
It's unlikely said by Tantai Jin,
but rather like by Cang Jiumin,
a disciple of Uncle Zhaoyou.
In fact,
I've been looking for you for 500 years.
Every day for these 500 years,
I've been thinking
that if god
has mercy on me
and gives me a chance to meet you again,
then what I can do to make you happy.
So,
I am Tantai,
and I am also Cang Jiumin.
Anything that makes you happy
will be done by me.
Tantai Jin,
what have you learned in Xiaoyao Sect?
I learned a lot.
You have said it.
So don't regret it.
I won't.
If I, Tantai Jin,
betray my words,
Heaven and Earth will slay me.
My body and soul will perish.
Don't say such things!
♪The stars scattered in the sky♪
♪Quietly fall on your brow♪
Ok.
♪As my heart sets its direction
Time passes and deepens♪
♪Let the galaxy be my pillow
and let the moon be my kiss♪
♪I want to enter your dreams♪
♪To explore the spring in your eyes♪
♪We are devout, turning the gears of fate♪
♪Spending a lifetime just to see one person♪
♪From the first glance
to being immersed in passion♪
♪I carefully trace the lines of your palm♪
♪We are devout
opening the door of our hearts♪
♪Wishing to see
only one person in this lifetime♪
♪Only hoping to be moved♪
♪Not to be afraid♪
♪The mark on my heart
don't ask whether it's worth it♪
♪Just believe that it's the right time♪
What are you doing?
I put a mark on you.
A unique spell is used.
You can't get rid of it
even if you want to.
And you can't regret it
My mark is in the shape
of a phoenix feather.
It's very beautiful.
Let me see how it looks.
Susu.
These are all old wounds.
I recovered a long time ago.
Since they won't disappear,
let's cover them.
You can be assured.
As long as it's yours,
I'll have it with me forever.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪