♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 22]
Miss Xiwu, why don't you head back first?
His Majesty is fuming.
If he finds out,
he'll definitely reprimand me.
Then I'll just stand here.
I'll head inside
after he cools down.
Bingchang.
Nian Baiyu,
tell her to leave.
Xiwu, you should head back first.
His Majesty is still angry.
Let me go talk to him.
[Since when did Bingchang
become this close to him?]
This is the white fungus soup
you told me to make.
Please try it and see if you like it.
Miss Xiwu,
why don't you head back first?
His Majesty said
he'd let her accompany him these few days.
Your Majesty, please.
Is it not to your liking?
I'll go and make it again.
That's not it.
Then what's wrong?
Be quiet.
If you don't have anything else to do,
go sit over there.
Grind some ink for me.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[Tantai Jin is really eccentric.]
[He's so hard to predict.]
[Never mind.]
[Nothing in this world comes easy.]
Just accept it.
For a man like that…
Just treat him as if he's dead.
He mustn't die.
I!
Ye Xiwu.
I thought you were just toying with him.
But you actually fell
into the pit yourself
and couldn't get out of it.
I fell into the pit myself?
How do you explain this then?
Look at how listless you are.
You're no different
from a woman who was abandoned.
Actually, I dumped him.
Yeah, yeah. You dumped him.
Let's go. Time to sleep.
[What exactly are you doing?]
Tantai Jin wiped out Sheng Kingdom
and ruined Xiao Lin's homeland and life.
And now, you are betraying him too?
Have you forgotten the vows
you made to him?
Why should I care about Xiao Lin?
He was incapable and broke his promises.
Because of him, I have to become a slave
and serve Tantai Jin.
I'm just trying to survive.
He has no power
to decide state affairs by himself.
Besides, he was deeply in love with you.
He truly loved you with all his heart.
Really? What if that love thread
didn't exist?
Wake up. He wasn't in love with you.
Nobody is in love with you.
Men seem to be attracted to you
simply because you have two love threads.
Is love more important than survival?
[Why would I have such a nightmare?]
[There's no turning back. Don't hesitate.]
Your Majesty.
His Majesty has a fever.
I'll go and get some medicine.
Wrap his forehead with a cold towel.
No one else must know about this.
Or else…
[Even a lowly guard]
[dares to threaten me now.]
Ye Xiwu…
[It's Ye Xiwu again.]
[Ye Xiwu is obnoxious enough.]
[And she abused Tantai Jin like that.]
[Why would he fall for her?]
[Even if he did fall for Ye Xiwu,]
[didn't he used to love me?]
[I'm the one by his side now.]
It's quite late.
Why are you standing here, General Ye?
You helped me. I ought to thank you.
How are you planning to thank me then?
By the way, how is Xiwu?
Lately, she and His Majesty…
They're both your sisters.
But you are partial to Ye Xiwu, huh?
You'll be fine after some time.
As the saying goes,
men can live without love.
But women can't.
But in my opinion,
there are plenty of silly men
in the world.
Right, General Ye?
You're right.
A man can't live without love either.
General Ye.
You're quite agreeable to my eyes.
So I have to make things clear first.
If you intend to seek someone
to spend your life with,
I'm not a good match for you.
However, if you seek momentary pleasures,
I'm always ready.
Why?
You are a human, while I'm a spirit.
What I fancy is nothing but your face.
Besides, foxes are romantic creatures.
Why should I love one man
when I can love many at once?
Think again, and make your decision.
Pian Ran!
Be careful, Your Majesty.
What? Have you never seen anyone
this gorgeous before?
♪Take a look at this world that we love♪
♪Reviewing the past years♪
♪The vivid and splendid dreams are
but a regret that won't fade, it seems♪
There, there.
A scum like him
is a perfect match for a woman like her.
Don't say that. She's my sister.
Seriously, why do you love him so much?
I don't know what's wrong with me either.
♪I'm tired of goodbyes and lingering fondness♪
♪Just send the ashes to the moon♪
There, there.
Stop crying, all right?
It's not shameful
to fall in love with a scum like him.
Right?
♪My emotions ebb and flow like the seasons♪
All right now.
You can ride a horse with me
if you don't have a carriage.
Let's go.
♪I can exchange everything for this life♪
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
♪True love is rare though♪
♪For I still believe in the touching you gave♪
Your Majesty, this sweet soup is chilled.
Your Majesty?
♪While waiting and enduring this bitter sorrow?♪
[Just how much does
Xiwu mean in his heart?]
[Has he forgotten what Xiwu]
[used to do to him?]
Why didn't you let Xiwu
get on the carriage too?
What she did before
was indeed not appropriate.
But she was a woman after all.
Why don't you
have mercy on her, Your Majesty?
No need for that.
Your Majesty, you've
always been like this.
Now that I think about it,
Your Majesty and Bingchang
have known each other for so many years.
Back when you were a hostage
in Sheng Kingdom,
you had a rough life.
Emperor Sheng saw you
as a thorn in his flesh.
I'd feel sorry for you
whenever I witnessed them
making things difficult for you
in the palace.
Now that you've united the world,
this world is your best compensation.
It's all in the past.
Now, Xiao Yi is dead.
I no longer
need any compensation.
Your Majesty,
you're as headstrong as always.
But I can't just pretend
to ignore the truth.
From now on,
let me keep you company.
Compensation?
Compensation is
the most pretentious thing in the world.
Ye Bingchang,
you used to see me as a freak.
What? Are you not afraid of me now?
It's true that I used to fear you.
But now,
we are both loners.
I may understand some of your pain.
You've been in Sheng Kingdom
for over a decade.
And now, I'll spend
the rest of my life in Jing Kingdom.
We will keep each other company.
One day at a time.
I'm a bit tired. You may leave.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Bingchang.
Why are you so nervous?
Let's sit and talk, shall we?
What do you want to tell me?
Xiwu,
I'll cut to the chase.
Tantai Jin was in love with me long ago.
However, he couldn't have me
because of Xiao Lin.
You know that, right?
I know.
Now, I've got nothing left.
I have to depend on Tantai Jin
if I wish to survive.
He's my last straw.
Xiwu,
you won't snatch
this straw from me, will you?
No, I won't. I don't like him anyway.
If so, I can rest at ease.
Xiwu,
what you did to him
was indeed inappropriate.
It's normal that he's holding
a grudge against you.
But I'll ask him not to
put you on the spot
once I'm done coaxing him.
Your Majesty,
these are the nether puppet soldiers
I've cultivated for the past few days.
These puppets do not feel pain or fear.
You can command them with demonic power.
How many nether soldiers do we have now?
Your Majesty,
including the prisoners
sent by Emperor Sheng a few days ago,
we have 4,000 of them.
Tantai Jin has 100,000 Jing soldiers
and tens of thousands of Firewing Army.
Can someone tell me
how can I conquer the Capital of Jing
with just these 4,000 puppets?
Your Majesty, Sheng Kingdom has perished.
Tantai Jin has united Sheng
and is at the peak of his power.
I'm afraid we cannot conquer
the Capital of Jing
in a short period.
Your Majesty,
please gather our forces for now.
Useless fools.
Fu Yu,
don't let them fool me again.
You'll suffer the consequences
if you can't figure something out
in a month.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Tantai Jin.
Ye Xiwu.
You're back?
Tantai Jin, do you love me?
I…
Why aren't you daring enough
to own up to it?
Are you afraid that I'll despise you,
be disappointed in you, and abandon you
when you say that?
Stop that!
See? You're always like this.
Forget it.
I'm going to fall in love
with someone else.
Being with you isn't fun at all.
Ye Xiwu.
Let go of me!
Ye Xiwu, come back!
Were you dreaming just now, Your Majesty?
Please rest early if you're tired.
Dreaming?
You're born without a love thread.
So you can't experience real emotions.
You won't feel happy or scared.
[How could one without
a love thread even dream?]
So, this is what you call a dream.
Speaking of which,
I had fallen in love with you
back in Bo're Life.
I swore to marry nobody but you.
You'd committed all kinds of evil deeds
in Bo're Life.
Are you trying to do the same now?
It was just a dream.
Why did you bring it up
when you knew that was just a dream?
Ye Bingchang, answer me.
Does being with me these days
make you happy?
Staying by your side
was what I desired the most.
Answer my question. Are you happy?
Naturally.
You're lying.
I'm speaking from the bottom of my heart.
Sheng Kingdom just perished,
and Xiao Lin went missing.
You came here from a foreign kingdom
just to keep me company.
Why would you be happy?
After Ye Qingyu surrendered,
he never fawned on me even once.
Although I convinced him to serve me,
he also feared me.
As for you,
you chose to be together
with the ruler who just conquered
your state and destroyed your family
just to seek shelter.
How could I trust you?
Your Majesty, are you despising me?
Have you forgotten
how horribly Ye Xiwu treated you
when you were in Ye Mansion?
Even so, Your Majesty still
took pity on her, right?
I'm just a woman
who's trying to survive
in troubled times like these.
Is one act of survival
nobler than another?
Ye Bingchang,
in my heart,
you're worth nothing compared to Ye Xiwu.
Your nobleness
has nothing to do with me.
[Tantai Jin,
how dare you insult me like this?]
Buttercup.
Come on.
Eat up.
Thank you, Grandma.
Look at you.
How come you became so much thinner?
I think it's because of the heat.
I heard that Tantai Jin
granted Bingchang the title of
Madam Xuancheng as soon as
he brought her back.
Everyone in the capital
is talking about it.
What's going on?
Let's eat.
Tantai Jin had always loved Bingchang.
There's nothing strange about it.
Grandma, I wish to move back.
Just for a few days.
I'll think of something
after I figure things out.
Figure what out? What do you mean?
All right. I'll tell Chuntao
to prepare your room.
From now on,
you'll keep me company every day.
[Ye Xiwu,]
[are you still not appeased]
[after so many days?]
[Never mind.]
[Since you won't come to me,]
[I'll go to you.]
[These are…]
[These letters…]
[Could it be that
she's still in contact with Xiao Lin?]
[Tantai Jin, how are you doing
in Jia Pass?]
[Were you wounded?]
[I found two dandelions]
[in your precious royal garden.]
[The gardeners actually let them live.]
[They're so lucky.]
[I heard that one could
make a wish with dandelions.]
[So I dug them out and brought them back.]
♪My lofty secret is the constraint♪
[I hope they'll remain alive
before your return.]
♪As if my wrist were tied on to♪
[Tantai Jin, when will you be back?]
♪All my life never fades♪
[Today, one of the dandelions
has turned into a white, fluffy ball.]
[I can finally make my wish.]
[I wish my dreams could come true.]
[And I wish that you stay safe and sound.]
♪Who can be spared from the pains?♪
[Never mind.]
[I'll put my blessing for you
over my wish.]
♪I allow no word to escape
But a trickle, flowing deep♪
♪Ripples in my eyes to explain♪
[The other one just bloomed.
I'll keep it for you.]
[You can make a wish when you're back.]
♪May as well be the staffage♪
♪Beyond the deepest depths of our hearts♪
♪Before we go gray
our romance has ended in vain♪
Ye Xiwu.
[Little Meteor.]
[Well, I think…]
You're just like that Little Devil God.
You're black inside out.
You have so many holes on you.
Just as many as his tricks.
Why don't I call you Little Jin?
Is that okay?
♪The surging torrent of love♪
♪Keeps the sound of its murmurs faint♪
♪Even when I know a hug will hurt each other♪
♪I still bet my life on you♪
♪We share this long, long dream♪
♪Love threads twine around the remaining heat♪
♪Our love has taken root long ago♪
[Anyway, you don't need me anymore.]
[I'll return this black lump to you.]
[You can keep him company.]
♪I'll miss you one life after another♪
[Ye Mansion]
Buttercup.
Grandma.
Just let Chuntao clean your room.
Yes, Madam.
Buttercup, would you
help me with something?
What is it?
I heard Qingyu is coming back tonight.
Qingyu is coming back?
Hush. Don't let your father know.
That stubborn kid
doesn't even let us mention his name.
Qingyu has been out there for so long.
I wonder how he's doing.
I made some clothes.
I also told Chuntao
to buy some snacks and tonics.
Deliver them secretly
to your younger brother on my behalf.
Okay?
Sure, just give them to me.
I'll deliver them to him.
Good girl. I'll go and get them now.
Come.
These are all for you.
Tell me if you need anything else.
I'll pass the message on to Grandma.
She's worried that
you can't eat or sleep well.
I don't need anything else.
Xiwu, if you have time,
visit our family on my behalf.
Keep Grandma company.
Rest assured. Grandma's doing well.
I don't believe that Dad
would keep this up forever.
He'll let you in eventually.
Let's talk about my things later.
I went back to the Capital of Sheng
some time ago.
I brought back some books
from our old home.
They're on the horse.
Please send them back on my behalf.
What were you doing in
the Capital of Sheng?
Didn't His Majesty tell you?
Tell me what?
Qingyu, what exactly is it?
It's confidential.
I shouldn't have mentioned it.
Don't tell anyone after hearing this.
The corpse of His Majesty's mother
was stolen by Emperor Sheng.
I brought a few sorcerers there
and did a soul-releasing ritual
in the ruins.
The Empress Dowager's body was gone.
I could only do that to comfort her soul.
There was nothing else I could do.
Xiwu?
Tantai Jin!
Miss Xiwu.
Miss Xiwu, what are you doing?
Where's Tantai Jin?
He…
Where is he? I need to speak with him.
What do you mean by that?
His Majesty forbade me from telling you
or following him.
Tantai Jin.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry.
I had prejudices against you.
I said things that had hurt you
even though I knew nothing.
I was wrong about you.
I'm sorry.
I saw it clearly
when you stared at me.
There were fear, disgust, and hatred
in your eyes.
Anyone could look at me like that.
I'd gotten used to it over the years anyway.
But how could you do the same to me?
I won't do it again. I promise.
Are you willing to keep me company
in the future?
Tantai Jin,
do you love Bingchang?
I brought her back from Sheng Kingdom
because she was your elder sister.
I thought you'd be happy about it.
Once,
I was like
a blind man living in the dark.
I've been trapped in the void
for more than 20 years.
People say that
the sun is bright and warm.
But I didn't know what true brightness
meant.
So,
when I saw how Xiao Lin
treated Ye Bingchang,
I thought that was love.
So I treated her exactly like he did.
Until I met you.
It turned out that it wasn't love at all.
At first, I was wondering
why I had so many strange feelings
when I was together with you.
It was only clear to me after you left me.
I am able to love someone
only because that person is you.
Ye Xiwu,
the one I love
is nobody but you.
Tantai Jin.
That was pretty mushy.
Every single word I said
came from the bottom of my heart.
And it took me a long time
to figure it out.
You're so silly.
Ye Xiwu,
I have learned what is love, expectation,
disappointment, jealousy.
sourness, and sentiment after
spending time with you.
You have taught me all of these feelings.
I'm willing to try to be a good person.
So,
could you please not leave me again?
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
Rest assured. From now on,
I will cling to you every day.
You have no way to get rid of me now.
♪Till the snow falls♪
All right.
♪I wanna hang it in a wrong time♪
♪To forget my everything♪
♪I wanna hang a dream there
and trade you with a drop of tear♪
Tantai Jin,
there's one more thing.
I was angry at you before.
So I threw the star you gave to me
into a pond.
But I couldn't find it no matter what.
I think I lost it. I'm sorry.
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
So, you turned yourself into a mess
because of that stone?
♪Does not fall in love?♪
♪Even when my heart is torn in two♪
♪I won't fly away♪
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
♪Like blessing, like suffering♪
I retrieved it.
♪It can't be settled♪
Tantai Jin,
thank you.
Ye Xiwu, there's one more thing
that I haven't told anyone before.
In the past, I never had any dreams.
However, whenever my life is in danger,
a cold voice
will appear in my dream.
[It's the Devil God]
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
Don't be afraid. I'll stay by your side.
If it appears again,
I'll wake you up from your dream.
♪Even when my heart is torn in two♪
Don't worry.
It hasn't appeared for a long time.
Besides,
you are the only person I dream about.
[Tantai Jin, no matter what happens,]
[I'll stay by your side]
[until that moment arrives.]
Ye Xiwu,
I'm thinking about
giving you a promotion
so that you can enter
and exit the court easily.
And you can also visit your family
whenever you like.
What kind of rank
does Your Majesty desire to grant me?
Tell me.
Why don't I appoint you as my Royal Maid?
You are permitted
to sleep on the floor beside me.
Forget it.
Sleeping on my stiff bed
is much better than
sleeping on the floor.
If so, I'll make a bed on your floor.
All right.
Since you wish to promote me,
I guess I have no choice
but to accept your kindness.
That's more like it.
Your Majesty, it's getting late.
It's time for you to sleep.
I haven't finished my drawing yet.
I'll stay here a little longer.
This is me. That's you.
General Ye,
the hot water for your bath is ready.
Thank you. You may leave.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing here?
Of course, I'm here to take a bath.
I…
Don't you have hot water in your house?
Yes, I have. However…
So, what is your answer
to my previous question?
Ye Qingyu,
are you a man or not?
Pian Ran,
I fell for you
ever since you saved my life.
I don't care if you're a human or a demon
or what you have experienced.
They don't matter to me.
Ye Qingyu.
You are a fool.
Well.
Since you were a dufus
for such a long time,
let me be merciful and tell you one thing.
You trained at Xiaoyao Sect before.
Have you ever heard of love threads?
All intelligent beings have them.
You can't love someone without them.
I was once married to a man.
His name was Jiang Rao.
I gave my love threads to him.
But he went to the battlefield
and died.
Thus, my love threads were lost.
You resemble him so much.
He was also a dumb soldier.
He spent all his days on the battlefield.
So, you…
That's right.
I wouldn't have saved you
with my powers
if you didn't resemble him.
Now, I have no love threads.
I cannot fall in love.
But since you resemble him,
I'll provide you with two options.
What if I insist on
spending my life with you?
Fine.
You might as well change your name.
Why don't you call yourself Jiang Rao?
What? You are not even willing
to change your name?
How dare you say you love me then?
Pian Ran,
if I agree to it,
not only will I humiliate myself,
but I will also taint the relationship
between you and Jiang Rao.
Ye Qingyu,
I thought you were an idiot.
But I didn't expect you to be a lunatic.
Fine. You're not willing to do it, huh?
The world is filled with men
who want to share
this momentary pleasure with me.
Farewell.
Your Majesty.
Little fox, you are being courteous today.
What's the matter?
Do you need a favor from me?
Your Majesty, now that
the Sheng Kingdom has been defeated,
the land is about to be united.
Your ambitions have been achieved.
Since I have always been faithful
in my duties,
at least, I deserve credit
for my diligence.
I would like to ask Your Majesty
for a reward today.
Tell me. What do you desire?
I'm just a wild fox
that came from the hills.
I hate being tied down.
Your Majesty, please give me the cure
and set me free.
You desire to leave?
You got a lot of nerves.
But if you do leave,
Ye Xiwu will be upset.
It's not like I'm going to vanish.
If Miss Xiwu wants to see me,
she can still do so.
It seems like
you're determined to leave.
Pian Ran,
doesn't the Jing Kingdom
have anything worth staying over?
It looks like there is.
Wait a minute…
I have given your antidote
to Ye Qingyu.
Why did you give it to him?
That's my weak point.
He asked for it early in the morning.
Does he know that I'm leaving?
General Ye is honest and hardworking.
He knelt before me
and made a vow this morning.
That's why I gave it to him.
You can ask him for the antidote
if you desire to leave.
You…
Tantai Jin, you scum!
I pray that you stay alone forever!
You…
What a feisty fox.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪