The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till the End of the Moon]
[Episode 26]
Grandma.
Ye Xiwu.
You're awake.
What?
I'm thirsty.
Wait for me.
Come on.
Ye Xiwu.
From now on, whatever you want,
just tell me.
I'll grant your every wish.
Tantai Jin,
marry me.
I wanna be your queen.
Okay.
She's like possessed after she came back.
We sent men to ask her to go home
to pay respects, but she drove them away.
I barely even know her now.
General Ye,
I'd like to ask a favor from you.
It's my pleasure, Your Majesty.
Please just say it.
I'd like to ask you
not to mention this in front of her again.
At least not before our wedding.
Let no one agitate her.
But grandma…
Xiwu loves her no less than you.
You can't imagine how sad she is.
Besides, she loved Xiao Lin for years.
But she watched him die.
These things came one after another.
How can she take it?
But whether father will forgive her or not,
she has to come back to meet us.
Last night Xiwu told me that
she wanted to cut all ties with Ye family.
General Ye, please erase her name
from your genealogy book when you return.
Your Majesty,
the one she wanted to murder was you.
Why do you still make her queen?
Do you really have no ill feelings?
Now, in this world,
only she hasn't abandoned me.
Only she's willing to return to me.
Willing to keep my company.
Willing to love me.
I can ask for nothing more.
Your Majesty,
I've calculated.
The 10th of next month will be an auspicious day.
Nonsense.
It's clearly the last day of this month!
How dare you talk nonsense？
How dare you accuse me of talking nonsense here?
What proof have you got?
From the observation of stars
and from the Five Elements and Eight Trigrams.
So what if you looked into that?
I've even looked into the records of history!
Enough.
The faster the better.
I don't wanna keep her waiting.
Your Majesty, but…
No buts about it.
How soon can we complete?
Your Majesty,
three days at most to arrange everything.
It's August 24 three days later.
It's settled then.
[August 24, Ominous]
Yes.
[August 24]
[August 24, Ominous]
Come on, this way.
Watch it.
Move.
Faster.
Ye xiwu!
Ye Xiwu, come out!
Ye Xiwu!
Come out! You!
Let me go!
Ye Xiwu,
you must be clear with me.
You left Ye family when we've declined.
[Ye Xiwu,]
Do you even have a conscience?
[don't be soft.]
Let me go!
-[Don't be soft.]
-Ye Xiwu!
Come out!
Ye Xiwu!
Drag him away.
You!
Are you even human?
Of all us juniors,
grandma loved you the most!
Are you still a human?
Ye Xiwu, you bastard…
Ye Xiwu…
Stop.
Xiwu,
what's this all about?
You've been hiding from us since you returned.
What exactly is this for?
Ye Qingyu,
you think you can talk to me like this
when you're a general?
If I go talk to Tantai Jin,
and ask him to relieve you of your post,
do you think he'll listen to me?
You're not Ye Xiwu.
You're nothing like my elder sister.
Perfect.
I've officially disowned Ye family.
Is there anything else?
Tantai Jin,
I wanna be your queen.
Okay.
Your Royal Highness, let me explain.
This is a custom of our Jing Kingdom.
The twin lotus flowers on your red bridal veil
should be embroidered personally by the bride.
Only with this sincerity,
can you have good fortune
and grow old together with your loved one.
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly♪
♪While on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing♪
♪Our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
Why is it snowing all of a sudden?
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Let's make it count♪
♪Tears are like fireworks♪
♪Kissing a distressed fairy♪
♪Parting is like a missed encounter♪
♪Nobody cares how much you miss each other♪
♪If not for telling a lie♪
[Your Majesty, you may not know this,]
[but the connected lotus flowers
on the bride's red veil]
[must be embroidered by the new couple,]
[in order for you to live happily ever after.]
"♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪"
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
"♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪"
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
"♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪"
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
[Heavenly gods above,]
[I, Tantai Jin,]
[only wish to spend my whole life]
[with Ye Xiwu, till death do us part.]
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
"♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪"
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
"♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪"
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
[I must get to the things]
[I didn't finish before.]
[This time,]
[I must make it.]
[Xiao Lin,]
[see you.]
[Tantai Jin can also have]
[such vivid expressions.]
[He must be very happy today.]
[I have been waiting]
[for this day for too, too long.]
[All the hard work I've been doing]
[is just for today.]
Thank you.
We are a married couple,
and you are my wife.
You don't need to thank me.
I want to give you a gift.
What gift?
World-overturning Jade.
Ye Xiwu,
what are you doing?
Ye Xiwu.
Ye Xiwu…
Why?
Tantai Jin,
My purpose in the first place
was to kill you.
Don't tell me
that you came back to me
just to kill me?
Yes.
So,
All the things you said to me
were lies.
♪Take a look at this world that we love♪
♪Reviewing the past years♪
♪The vivid and splendid dreams
are but a regret that won't fade, it seems♪
♪Rather than wake from this slumber
I'd prefer the dream to last forever♪
But I still
♪I soothe the reckless face♪
love you.
♪Just send the ashes to the moon♪
♪I'm never heartless♪
♪My emotions ebb
and flow like the seasons♪
♪Even if sorrows never end♪
Do you?
Tantai Jin,
I have never loved you.
♪True love is rare though♪
♪For I still believe in the touching you gave♪
♪While the fireworks of life
are short-lived and easily enjoyed♪
Great.
♪I once thought that joys and sorrows♪
♪were just unfinished preludes♪
Farewell,
Tantai Jin.
♪Have been pushed away
several times by fate♪
The Heart-guarding Scale…
♪Watching the nebulae cycle by,
I've long let go♪
♪But I never forget
your words of "No Regrets"♪
♪I'm never heartless♪
♪My emotions ebb
and flow like the seasons♪
♪Even if sorrows never end♪
♪A fair complexion remains unafraid
of being soaked in tears♪
♪I can exchange everything for this life♪
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
♪True love is rare though♪
♪For I still believe in the touching you gave♪
Ye Xiwu,
♪Only this time, who will be waiting?♪
♪Who is not willing to let go?♪
♪Who doesn't dare to force?♪
Why?
Why would you fool me like this?
♪Looking back again, all grudges
and kindnesses are just fleeting♪
♪No more talk of leaving or staying♪
♪Silence is the best cure♪
♪One who wants to get drunk needs no alcohol♪
♪But I ask, can the commitments
still remain the same?♪
♪Not for heaven and earth,
but only for your heart♪
♪The longing never ends♪
[Go.]
Jiwu,
Dad, my eye hurts.
[What happened to your eye?]
Daddy,
my eye is in so much pain.
It hurts.
[Sorry.]
[I failed.]
[The energy concealed in this jade]
[may be comparable to that of a god,]
[but using it will harm one's karma,]
[causing the user to meet a tragic end,]
[and suffer a violent death.]
[Dad,]
[Jiwu, and Uncle Zhaoyou,]
[I have tried my best.]
I'm truly sorry.
Ye Qingyu,
your sister did that out of no where,
and you really had no idea?
If I knew, I would've stopped her.
I wonder if His Majesty
will blame the Ye family
when he wakes up.
Last night, Xiwu told me
that she wanted to
cut all ties with the Yes.
General Ye,
when you are back,
please scratch out Xiwu's name
from the Ye family's genealogy.
That's what she was doing!
Xiwu had planned
the assassination long ago,
so that's why she wanted to
cut all ties with us.
I didn't realize this sooner.
But what is she doing this for?
Is it for Xiao Lin?
I don't know.
The news of His Majesty's injury
has been blocked
both inside and outside the palace.
I have to go home
and inform my father and the others
to get prepared.
[The incident of Ye Xiwu
drugging His Majesty ]
[has been glossed over so easily.]
[She is indeed lucky.]
[But Tantai Jin clearly knows everything,]
[and kept her alive.]
[No,]
[I can't give Ye Xiwu
the chance to tell the truth.]
Qingyu,
it's so late. Why are you suddenly back?
It's good that you are here, Bingchang.
Let's go to see father together.
Get Zeyu there too.
Yes.
What?
Xiwu tried to assassin Tantai Jin?
The crime of assassinating the king
is punishable by death.
Once the killing order is made,
Xiwu will certainly die.
Well, Qingyu,
What should we do?
I will try to convince His Majesty
turn her over to that three interdependent judicial departments for questioning before the trial.
Being inquired by three departments.
What if she tells us about the drugging?
Now her life is at stake.
I came back today to persuade you to leave home to avoid trouble.
Although Xiwu has severed ties with the Ye family,
His Majesty still may be angry.
Be angry?
So What?
Xiwu is the daughter of the Ye family.
As her gather,
although I cannot exonerate her,
I can't abandon her at this time.
Father, I…
Life and death are decreed by fate.
This time, I won't escape.
General Ye.
Please.
Father, you…
Since you have made up your mind,
I will not persuade you.
Please take care of your health, Father.
Eldest Brother,
please take care of our family.
[Ye Xiwu]
[Since you don't know how to cherish it]
[and want to die,]
[don't blame me.]
Your Majesty.
Hury up. His Majesty is awake.
Your Majesty, you are awake.
Get out, all of you!
Yes.
You Majesty.
What did the doctor say?
He said
he had never seen such a strange concealed weapon before.
It grows in the heart and veins in a few moments
and
it cannot be removed by external force.
Really?
It's OK to keep it in my body.
But Your Majesty,
these nails growing in the flesh
will be painful.
Then let it be painful.
Your Majesty.
How long will I live?
As long as Your Majesty recuperates well,
you will definitely get better.
Nian Baiyu.
You are not good at lying.
The doctor said
Your Majesty's heart and veins are damaged.
Even if he recuperates well,
he will not live more than three years.
So long.
It's really hard to go through.
Where is Ye Xiwu?
She's in the dungeon.
The jailer came to report that
from yesterday to now,
she did not eat or drink.
Dress for me.
But Your Majesty,
Your injuries are still fresh.
Dress for me.
Yes.
[It's because I like you.]
[OK?]
[A couple for one day has a hundred days of kindness.]
[Isn't it natural for me to save you?]
[So you've been lying to me since then.]
[What is love?]
[If you love someone, you don't want him to die,]
[and you want to stay with him.]
[You will be anxious if you can't see him.]
[You will be happy when you see him.]
[Everything is fake.]
[Everything is just a delusion of mine.]
[I was blind]
[to fall in love with you!]
[Tantai Jin.]
[I was supposed to come and kill you.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
[You are really the most heartless person in the world.]
[Almost invisible.]
[This is also the backlash of the World-overturning Jade.]
Ye Xiwu.
Do you think I'm stupid
and ridiculous?
You are locked in here
you can only see a beam of light when you look up.
You feel scared,
right?
I've been in the same mood
day and night these days.
Even when I was embroidering that veil for you,
I was scared.
When people stay in the dark for a long time,
they always look forward to the light of tomorrow.
But once they see it,
they will fear that at any moment they may lose it.
It's really what you're afraid of comes.
Now, in the world,
nobody can save me.
Just like your condition now,
nobody can save you.
Even if no one will save me,
I don't regret it.
Tantai Jin.
I once naively thought that
maybe I could be that light
in your darkness.
And I could make yo become a person.
But I was wrong.
Some darkness does not
deserve light.
It doesn't deserve.
It doesn't deserve?
Ye Xiwu.
Have a look.
I, Tantai Jin, a idiot.
You used to beat him, scold him, torment him.
And you even wanted to kill him.
But even so,
he still can't bear to kill you.
He was even full of joy
to marry you as his queen.
He looks forward to growing old
side by side with you.
He is so foolish.
Until you nailed him with those six nails,
he first came to his senses.
He really has no dignity.
[There is no Soul-slaying spikes.]
[The only chance to change the fate of the Three Realms]
[ was screwed up by me.]
[There is no point for me to live any longer]
[except to be humiliated]
Yes.
You have no dignity.
So I hate you.
Shut up!
I've done this to you!
Why don't you kill me immediately?
Do you have dignity?
Ye Xiwu.
How do you feel, Ye Xiwu?
This heartbreaking feeling is very painful, right?
Let me tell you.
This is not even a fraction of the pain I feel.
Tantai Jin.
Kill me.
Kill me now.
Although it is interesting to make fun with you,
I'm tired of it.
Kill me,
or…
In your dreams.
Did you think I would
let you off the hook so easily?
No.
I will keep your life.
I will take you apart little by little
to see
What kind of heart
do you have in here?
Kill me.
Since
my affection means nothing to you,
have a taste of my hatred.
Your Majesty.
The doctors are outside.
Send them away.
Your Majesty.
No.
Send them to check
if Ye Xiwu is dead in the prison.
If you really hate her so much,
why would you keep her in the palace?
I hate her.
So I won't let her get what she wants.
She wants to run away.
She wants to die.
[Kill me.]
[Kill me now.]
So I'll make sure she's alive.
[I was once naive enough to think]
[that maybe I can]
[be the light in your life of darkness]
[and make you a human.]
[Tantai Jin.]
[It may be tiring,]
[but you must stay alive.]
[You made it. So did I.]
[We both survived.]
[Promise me you'll stay alive.]
[I won't let you die.]
[But I was wrong after all.]
[Some lives in darkness don't deserve lights.]
[Since I'm alive,]
[she has to stay alive, too.]
[Why should I]
[be left alone in such darkness?]
Nian Baiyu.
Summon Ye Qingyu here.
I have things to say.
Understood.
How is His Majesty?
How is he?
He's in great pain
but has to bear with it.
What about Ye Xiwu?
His Majesty told me
that he wouldn't kill her.
She is safe for now.
But the prison
gets humid and suffocating
with pests everywhere in summer.
If she stays without food
or drinks,
she won't make it.
That silly girl is determined to die.
Mr. Nian, can I visit her?
Since His Majesty wants her alive,
go ahead.
Thank you for your kindness.
With my little sister in jail,
the whole family is worried.
That's why they sent me here.
We'll just talk a bit.
It's fine if you're only here to talk.
As long as
you didn't bring any prohibited items.
Sir.
How can a flimsy young lady like me
possibly help her break free?
Fine. Come with me.
Ye Bingchang.
Yes, it's me.
Why did you come?
Xiwu.
You've suffered.
Of course, I have to visit you.
You know.
I've always hated you
for being so condescending.
Since you don't want small talk,
let's get down to business.
My sweet sister.
I would like to know
if Tantai Jin had tasted that bowl of porridge?
Why didn't he die?
You know the porridge…
That's right.
You thought
you were the only one who added things in there.
What did you put in there?
Dry mylabris.
One tiny sip
is lethal.
[Ye Xiwu.]
[Did you]
[make this porridge specifically for me?]
[Tantai Jin thought I wanted to poison him]
[to save Xiao Lin.]
Why would you do that?
Xiao Lin is doomed because of that, you know?
Don't mention that name.
You don't deserve it.
You know?
I had all my hopes up that day.
I thought I would hear about Tantai Jin
and that old woman getting poisoned.
But it never crossed my mind
that Tantai Jin didn't have the porridge.
He didn't die.
You killed Grandma, too.
Ye Xiwu.
You won't be sad for long.
I will do you a favor
and let you get reunited with her
in the underworld.
[Tantai Jin]
[Do you want me to have it?]
[Why?]
[If you feed me,]
[I will force myself to take a few bites.]
[From now on, tell me whatever]
[you want.]
What are you doing?
Xiwu.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪