The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles.
We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 19]
Emperor Jin,
we will arrive at
the Capital of Jing soon.
[Pavilion of Miraculous Mist]
[Ruyi Shop of Rouge]
[So, this is the Capital of Jing?]
[It does look peaceful and prosperous]
[instead of being in great disorder.]
[My feet are worn out.]
[Tantai Jin, you are ruthless indeed.]
Xiwu.
Hold this for me.
[House of Treasures][Tianxiang Inn]
Qingyu, are you here to pick me up?
It has been a few days since we met.
So, you got yourself a job?
It's all because of
that stupid Tantai Jin.
He insisted on making me his maid.
Xiwu, this is Jing Kingdom.
Do not address
the emperor's name in public.
Why is there a wound on your forehead?
Follow me.
Someone prepared a surprise for you.
[Ye Mansion]
The new batch of tea leaves
have already arrived.
Xiwu loved it when she was still at home.
That lass is a picky girl.
She only loves tea leaves
that have just sprouted.
But it has been a long time
since we heard from Miss Xiwu.
When will she come back?
Right now,
I'm picking out the sprouts.
This way, Xiwu can enjoy it
when she comes back.
Father?
Miss Xiwu?
Miss Xiwu, why are you only back now?
Xiwu?
Xiwu!
Grandmother.
You are finally back!
Why have you lost so much weight?
And, you became tanner.
My precious Xiwu,
you must have endured
a lot of hardships out there.
Miss Xiwu, you are finally back.
Grandmother, what's wrong with Father?
Get up!
Look who's back.
Xiwu?
Xiwu! You are finally back!
I missed you so much!
This is great!
Father, what happened to you?
You mean this? It's nothing.
Don't worry. I am doing fine.
I was just putting on an act.
Tantai Jin insisted on making me
come out of retirement.
I told Zeyu to report to him
that I was injured
and that I could only lie on the bed
and drool all day long.
I acted like I was paralyzed.
Anyway, I won't come out of retirement
anytime soon.
I did not need to tell you all of that.
You must be starving.
Come. Let's have our meal.
Wait.
-Come
-Don't forget.
-Come.
-You should tell your grandmother
and me
about what happened these few days.
We need to catch up.
Rebellious son!
[Ye Mansion]
The Ye family would have been massacred
if it were not for His Majesty's help.
Father, you were
a mighty general back then.
But now, you are sitting idly by
in our mansion.
Now, Father,
His Majesty is willing to bestow you
with the Three Armies
so that you can come out of retirement
and defend our kingdom once again.
Do you expect me to draw my sword
against my brethren?
You may be able to do it,
but I cannot do it!
I do not want people to criticize me
after my death.
I, Ye Xiao, cannot accept that!
From now on,
I will break your legs
if you dare to step into this house!
[Xiang's Tavern]
Watch out!
You should not drink
when you have external injuries.
Pian Ran.
You are a grown-up.
And, you're seven-feet tall.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you cannot survive
without your grandmother and father?
My parents chased me out of the house
right after I acquired my form.
There's nothing to cry about.
I didn't cry.
You look even worse than crying.
Enough already.
I have finally returned to
the wonderful capital.
I am in a great mood today.
Why don't we take a walk together?
What do you think? The night market
in the Capital of Jing
is just as good as the ones
in Sheng Kingdom, right?
Let's head there.
Please take a look.
Top-quality fabric for sale.
Mister, what about
buying one for your wife?
She…
He is a dummy.
I shall pick one on his behalf.
I assume these fabrics were woven with
Sheng Kingdom's way of weaving, right?
That's right. Madam,
you have sharp eyes indeed.
Many refugees from Sheng Kingdom
came to our capital.
They wove these fabrics.
Look.
Although His Majesty is decisive,
he is a benevolent ruler.
Some of the refugees lost their homes
because of war.
But more of them came here
as they were unsatisfied with
[Recruitment]
Sheng Kingdom's strict political regiment.
His Majesty has already
[Grain Mill]
issued an order to treat the prisoners of war nicely
and help the refugees out.
They were taught how to read, write, and
weave so that they could make a living.
Excellent!
You are worried that
you have made the wrong choice.
In my opinion,
you do not need to feel this way.
After all, you know better
than anyone else
how tyrannical
the ruler of Sheng Kingdom is.
Once Sheng Kingdom wins the war,
the lives of the people of Sheng Kingdom
will only get better and better.
I only decided to settle down here
because His Majesty wasn't a bad person.
Thank you, mister. Take care.
So, for generals like you who had
surrendered to him,
maybe His Majesty will let you marry
an official's daughter
when you contribute to the kingdom
and make him happy.
Thank you. I have finally seen the light.
I spent a lot of my time
trying to convince you,
yet you always dwell on the same thing.
But you were enlightened right away
when I mentioned someone's daughter, huh?
Wait, I…
Enough. I was just trying to
help you clear your doubts.
Foxes like us are loyal friends.
I heard that a group of acrobats
from Sheng Kingdom is performing in front.
Let's go and take a look.
Okay.
Xiwu,
there are conflicts everywhere.
Men like them have no choices.
Both you and Bingchang
got married to Tantai Jin
and Xiao Lin respectively.
You guys have no choice but to wander.
Your father could not cope with that fact.
Now that I have reached a certain age,
I have straightened out my thoughts.
I just hope that
the younger generations like you all
can stay safe.
I never expected us
to reunite in Jing Kingdom.
Bingchang is the only missing member now.
I hope Xiao Lin can protect her
and not let her suffer any grievances.
Miss Xiwu, you are overthinking it.
Even if Prince Xuancheng is gone,
there are plenty of men who will
protect Miss Bingchang.
Hey, why do you sound so jealous
when we talk about Bingchang?
Did she offend you?
Is it her fault for being likable?
Miss Bingchang wasn't
this popular back then.
However, the number of admirers
had increased considerably
in the past few years.
I just thought it was strange.
Is that so?
Xiwu.
Zeyu. Is Father asleep?
It has been a long time since our family
was this happy.
You had no idea.
Our trip here was hectic.
Aunt and the maids were scattered
as they escaped for their lives.
The soldiers of Sheng Kingdom
were on our tails.
It was excruciating.
However, we were lucky that
Tantai Jin dispatched a group of soldiers
to escort us.
That was how we were able to survive.
He gave us this mansion too.
So, Tantai Jin escorted you guys here?
That's right.
Our family would have been massacred
if we had to rely on that petty Xiao.
He also found physicians
to treat our grandmother and father,
but Dad drove them away.
But in the past,
you used to hit and scold Tantai Jin,
and I often bullied him too.
However, he didn't retaliate against our family.
Why is he being like this?
Yes. Why?
Girl, where are you going?
Taking a stroll in the Palace.
Moreover, on my journey
I have encountered many civilians,
and they don't care about
what the ruler's surname is.
They simply go wherever
there is a livelihood.
You have great governing skills,
not only do I like you
and want to follow you,
but everyone else likes you
and wants to follow you too.
I have also experienced the humiliation
of being dependent on others.
If I can prevent the people
from experiencing such suffering,
as a ruler, I would be
satisfied with my work.
Your Majesty,
Maid Ye is here.
Let her in.
Yes.
Why aren't you bowing
when you come to see the king?
Tantai Jin, thanks.
For what?
Thank you for the surprise you gave me,
for treating my family well,
for providing a way out
for my brother and his subordinates.
Easy for you to say.
What?
Are you just going to
say thank you and move on?
Is that enough?
You…
You asked me to show more gratitude
than just words.
♪Your gaze, a little closer♪
♪Heart beats faster
taking root in the void♪
♪The stars scattered in the sky♪
♪Quietly fall on your brow♪
[The soul-slaying spikes are formed.]
♪As my heart sets its direction
time passes and deepens♪
♪Let the galaxy be my pillow
and let the moon be my kiss♪
♪I want to enter your dreams♪
It's late.
You should go back to go to bed.
What's wrong?
Don't you have to wake up
for duty tomorrow morning?
Yes, Your Majesty.
No problem, Your Majesty.
Leaving now.
♪I carefully trace the lines of your palm♪
♪Just believe that it's the right time♪
Ye Xiwu,
I've never seen you so happy before.
You are happy because of your family,
but not me, aren't you?
I…
I guessed so.
In fact, you don't have to
go to such lengths
to please me by enduring
hardships and humiliations for them.
[My spikes…]
Get back!
Don't bother me anymore.
I said, get back!
Men's hearts are so unpredictable.
[Regardless of whether
Little Devil God can feel love]
[or how guarded he is,]
[I cannot give up.]
[Why did I throw a tantrum last night?]
[Ye Xiwu's reunion
with her family brought her joy,]
[and wasn't that what I wanted to see?]
[Even if the reason for her joy
was not related to me,]
[why would I…]
From Shangyuan City to Kou City.
Did you keep that in mind?
Yes.
Baiyu,
I remember that you have
a mother and a sister
at your home in the Yiyue tribe,
right?
Yes, Your Majesty.
You should go home and visit them.
You Majesty,
do you not need me anymore?
That's not what I mean.
I'm just allowing you to take a leave
and reunite with your family,
or if you prefer,
you can bring them back to Jing Kingdom.
From now on, all Moonshadow Guards
will have the same privilege.
Thank you for your grace, Your Majesty.
I'm just not sure why
you suddenly became
interested in this matter.
[Thank you for treating my family well.]
No reason. You are excused.
Yes.
Family…
Ye Xiwu, you are now a maid to His Majesty.
There are so many rules
and customs in the palace,
have you learned them all?
And how do you have time
to read novels?
I don't want to learn.
I can't remember anything.
What the hell are those rules?
No talking, no moving,
no burping, not farting.
I have more important things to do.
What things?
Making Tantai Jin fall for me, of course.
Don't tell me that
you are reading the romance novels for…
Of course!
I have memorized
all the lines of the stories,
so you can wait
and see me perform perfectly.
What the hell is this?
This is the wishing lantern
I personally made.
Would you like to
release it together tonight?
Wishing lantern?
Is it some kind of psychic sorcery?
Not a sorcery.
It's a romantic gesture.
Just imagine,
two people releasing lanterns together
under the moonlight,
making wishes
and watching the lanterns
slowly disappear into the night sky
while silently hoping for a bright future
and expressing
their feelings for each other.
It's so beautiful.
In other words, it's useless.
Right?
Nian Baiyu,
drag her out.
Yes.
Miss Xiwu, please go.
[Little Devil God,]
[I have been here playing for 6 hours,]
[so please come and talk to me.]
[I can chat so much with you,
from sentimental things]
[to life philosophy.]
[Hurry up.]
What?
His Majesty complains that
this is too noisy,
and you have been constantly playing off-key.
If you still haven't played enough,
I will send you out of the city
so you can play until dawn.
You can come back
after you have enough fun.
No need. I'm done.
Bye.
Your Majesty, the morning drizzle is cold.
Shall we go back?
You've been standing here for a long time.
It will be time for the morning court soon.
What are you smiling about?
Your Majesty.
Nothing.
The music she played was awful.
♪Your gaze, a little closer♪
[According to the novels,]
[the more powerful a man is,]
[the more a girl should
maintain her dignity]
[and not follow his rules.]
[Ideally, she should even
scold him face-to-face]
[in order to get his attention.]
♪Let the galaxy be my pillow
and let the moon be my kiss♪
Miss Xiwu.
Get out of the way!
Tantai Jin, who do you think you are?
Just because you're a ruler of a country
with the power of life and death
and good looks,
you think you can dictate to me?
Although I'm just a maid
I also have my dignity.
♪We are devout
opening the door of our hearts♪
♪Wishing to see only one person
in this lifetime♪
♪Only hoping to be moved♪
♪Not to be afraid♪
♪The mark on my heart
don't ask whether it's worth it♪
♪Just believe that it's the right time♪
Why is it not working?
Tantai Jin is so cruel.
I can't believe he told
the Maid of Discipline about this.
Your Majesty,
Do you really dislike Miss Xiwu?
Are you happy to see her being punished?
Or what else?
I…
I think although Miss Xiwu is silly,
she is quite cute.
Who said she isn't?
Shut your mouth!
This month, the Firewing Army
has consumed 200 stones of rice,
1,300 catties of green grass,
and 500 catties of dry hay.
They have also slaughtered
50 whole oxen and 90 whole pigs.
The army's appearance is improving,
and their discipline is good.
However, there have been
two brawls occurred.
How did you deal with the demon beasts
involved in the brawls?
They refused to change their behavior,
so I ate them.
Great.
This month,
you can forget about having days off.
Tantai Jin,
how are you so inhumane?
What? Do you want to disobey my orders?
Tantai Jin,
you are the ruler of the country,
and the whole Jing is yours.
You don't need to rest,
but we staff need it!
I've been working without rest for 80 days!
It's only 80 days. Calm down.
I have an opportunity just for you.
Go deal with the demons on the west end,
then I'll give you half a day off.
We demons have dignity, too.
You're expecting me, a demon,
to catch other demons?
You're now a leader of Jing
guiding the Firewing Army,
You're responsible of protecting the people.
Understand?
Yes, Tantai Jin. Loud and clear.
I'll be on way.
You better keep your word. Half a day off.
Write your report once you're done.
Run along now.
Just you wait.
I'll escape as soon as I get the antidote.
It's been 80 days?
Miss Fox!
W-Why are you sneaking around?
You scared me!
Pian Ran, my dear friend,
I've tried all the tricks in the book,
can you teach me a couple more?
Those tricks should be enough
for you to deal with His Majesty.
Just repeat them again and again.
It's not! I want him to really like me.
How much more is that?
At least I should impress him nine times.
What a specific number of times.
I just want him to like me more.
Better yet, fall in love with me.
Come on, Pian Ran. Help me out here.
You really want to learn from me?
Then we'll need some real moves!
-General Ye. -Ah!
P-Pian Ran…
There's a bug on your ear.
I'll help you blow it away.
Okay, it can't hurt you now.
You can go.
See? That's how men are like.
You get up close to them,
and their brain freezes.
I'll pass.
Tantai Jin might feed me to the tigers.
You won't take my advice?
Well, it's your loss.
Come on.
Help me come up
with something else, please?
Xiwu, what are you the least good at?
What am I the least good at?
I'm the least good at…
I'm really bad at cooking.
Yes, that's it!
Let me tell you,
the way to a man's heart
is through his stomach.
You can just cook for him.
Even dogs won't eat what I cook.
It's not about the taste, but your heart.
You must feed him with your own hands,
every day, every meal.
That will double the results
with half the work.
And the worse it looks and taste,
the better.
Are you serious?
Have I ever lied to you?
Go on, get to it!
I'm a busy woman you know.
Tantai Jin, I finally found someone
to get back at you.
Wickedness befalls the wicked.
Wait till you get a taste
of Ye Xiwu's awful cooking.
Baiyu.
What does this character mean?
It's pronounced as "tao",
to describe the surging water in rivers.
Baiyu, why don't you go get some rest?
What "Huh?" Just go.
Okay.
What are you reading?
An ancient book of the Yiyue tribe.
No wonder.
I can't read a single character of it.
What are you doing?
This character looks so strange.
It's like a worm crawling out
from the earth.
What does it mean?
It means to sprout.
What about this one?
To smelt.
And this one?
Kill two birds with one stone?
It means…
You don't know either?
Should we get Nian Baiyu to come back?
I think he might know better.
It means "love".
Oh, that's it?
What's there to be shy about?
What are you doing here at night?
Can't I come just to see you?
Are you hungry?
Get out.
Come on, at least take a bite.
I spent so much time
and even burnt my hand.
Ye Xiwu, serves you right.
Don't cook if you can't.
But I wanted you to like me.
Give it to me.
This is the first time
I actually cooked for someone.
I hope you won't mind
my lack of experience.
I'm sure I'll improve with practice.
Does it taste really bad?
Not really…
[Looks like I screwed up again.]
[I need to try something else.]
Just spit it out.
I won't cook anymore.
Why?
Why won't you cook anymore?
Persistence maketh a man.
Besides,
I don't think it tastes that bad.
[Fox was right.]
[The way to a man's heart
is through his stomach.]
[It worked just like magic.]
[He can't even taste how awful it is.]
If you like,
I can cook for you again tomorrow.
Sure.
Here are two more dishes. Try them.
Maybe you'll like them better.
[The Soul-Slaying Teardrop is heating up.]
[Miss Fox wasn't lying after all.]
I'll leave you to it then.
[If there's a will, there's a way!]
[I'm gonna gather all the spikes I need.]
Your Highness, this is the demonic elixir
just crafted by our warlocks.
Your Highness!
Why is it so easy for Tantai Jin
to refine demonic elixir,
yet so difficult for me?
Perhaps we are simply built different to one another.
But Your Highness is as much a mortal
as Tantai Jin is,
you're no different in nature.
So…
If Tantai Jin can master the Firewing Army,
then so can I.
Fu Yu.
Pay a visit to our allies for me.
Allies?
I'm not the only one
who wants Tantai Jin dead.
Don't give yourself away
since Emperor Sheng is already suspicious.
Yes, Your Majesty.
General Ye,
I knew when I was a hostage in Sheng
that Xiao Yi is one to doubt others.
He even distrusts Xiao Lin,
his only son.
The Sheng has suffered heavy casualties
since the beginning of the war.
Xiao Yi must be feeling
extremely anxious by now.
If I push him further now,
he will be determined
to exhaust his troops
and become a burden to Xiao Lin.
Am I despicable for doing so?
All is fair in war.
The sooner we end the war,
the sooner our people can live in peace.
General Ye,
since you grew up in court,
who do you think is the far superior
between the Sheng's princes
and me?
Feel free to speak at ease.
In terms of strategy and wisdom,
Your Majesty is inferior to none.
But since Xiao Lin and his brothers
have been educated well
by knowledgeable scholars,
Your Majesty may be inferior to them
in terms of state affairs.
Nian Baiyu.
At your service.
Summon all great scholars in the nation
to give me lessons starting tomorrow.
Your Majesty,
these old scholars
have served the Jing nation all their lives.
They can be obstinate.
I'm afraid they won't come.
Those who disobey
shall be sentenced to death.
Your Majesty,
are you absolutely certain?
Only to scare them.
Will do.
If there are no objections,
let the lessons begin.
Your Late Majesty!
I've been faithful all my life,
yet I shall lose my loyalty today!
I would rather die than be dishonorable!
Are you okay, sir?
Your head certainly is hard.
You must have mastered the Iron Head.
Nian Baiyu.
Serve the gentlemen some refreshments.
We can start classes
once this gentleman has cried enough.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Tantai Jin!
You vicious monster!
You've oppressed the loyal commoners
murdered your brothers and taken innocent lives!
You are an outrage to the gods and people!
Heaven forbid!
Well said. Well said indeed.
If what you say is true
that I am so unfaithful, unfilial,
ungrateful and unrighteous,
then maybe you should educate me
and make it a great achievement
to pass on to your descendants.
Y-You… you make my blood boil!
What should we do?
I'm so infuriated I could die!
We've let His Late Majesty down.
Y-You're killing me!
From the emperor to the masses,
cultivating ourselves is inevitably the root of everything.
If the root is ungoverned,
all of which that follows shall be chaos.
Resentment by whom respect is shown
and respect by whom resentment is shown
can never cease to exist.
Our ancestors who illustrated virtue
throughout the kingdom,
had to first govern their own states.
In order to govern a state,
they first had to manage well their homes.
In order to manage their homes…
I'm sorry!
Why are you stopping? Go on.
Yes, Your Majesty.
From the emperor
-You too, go on.
-…to the masses,
If the root is ungoverned,
all of which that follows shall be chaos.
Watch it.
His Majesty's work relief policy
is simply wonderful!
Now the government policies
are arried out effectively.
His Majesty merely applies
what he learns immediately.
Before, Tantai Minglang's severe laws
made the people boil with resentment.
Now they've been abolished
by Your Majesty's order.
His Majesty has decreed that
as the neighboring nations of Jing and Sheng
were once unified
with the same streets and same books,
yet due to the tyrannical rule in Sheng today
their people have taken refuge in Jing,
local officials must welcome
the refugees kindly
without exceptions.
Anyone from the Sheng
can settle down in the Jing.
May our kingdom be in peace and stability!
Tantai Jin! You've gone too far!
I will make you pay!
Your Majesty.
A woman has presented a token.
She has a proposition for Your Majesty.
This is a relic of the Jing's royal family.
Let her in.
Your Majesty.
Tantai Minglang has lost his power,
what can he do for me?
Have Your Majesty ever heard
of the puppeteering spell?
My master has mastered the craft
to be build a Puppet Army.
All we need now is men.
What we have most in Sheng is men.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
In time,
I guarantee this Puppet Army
will be the answer to all your troubles.
[These are Yiyue tribe's occult arts,]
[Your Majesty need to practice more]
[to enhance your power.]
Tantai Jin has been working so hard lately.
He toils away from day to night.
Even the clothes on his body
have become loose.
I should make more good food
to keep him fit.
Tantai Jin.
Nian Baiyu,
drag Ye Xiwu out of here.
♪A thousand words♪
♪Are hesitant in my throat♪
♪Like snow flakes sinking in a cup♪
Neither has is shrunk,
nor has it grown.
Should I be spending more time
with the Little Devil God?
When is this going to end?
♪I wear on my wrist♪
♪A bright frost blade♪
Are you going to hang yourself?
♪I decide my life♪
How can I make Tantai Jin admire me more?
I guessed it.
You just showed yourself before him,
that wouldn't work.
From tomorrow on,
you can just stay away from him.
That's man.
If you ignore him,
he will care you more.
Will I seem mean for that?
Are you trying to cheat him
or fall in love with him?
I…
I certainly don't mean it.
But I have to make him admire me.
The more, the better.
So, that's it.
Just take my words.
♪not to die alone♪
When will I gather all nine?
[Or let me try what Pian Ran said.]
[Retrea to advance.]
[Maybe it will work.]
♪How lucky we are♪
♪Since we can meet♪
♪A kiss is more worth than everything♪
♪We are all involved in♪
♪Who can remain unaffected♪
♪My flush of love in heart♪
♪Could you hear it♪
What's the matter
Your Majesty call me here?
And when can I
have that half-a-day off?
I call you here today
to consult you something.
If you well answer it,
you can have a day off tomorrow.
Okay, spit it out.
In this world,
what can make you feel so embarrassed?
Just spit it out.
Ye Xiwu hasn't served me for two days.
Oh? You miss her?
Ye Xiwu is a royal servant
and is fed by the court,
shouldn't she fulfill her duties?
Then you should reach her, not me.
I'm off, I'm busy.
Halt!
She told me a few days ago
that she likes me.
That's why she cooked for me
day after day.
Now since she's been absent,
does that mean
she doesn't like me anymore?
Very likely.
I thought…
I thought she likes being around me.
My God.
You bad men…
You men
are just too self-absorbed, don't you?
Let me ask you,
you want her to be like a mom
who likes you and serves you everyday,
then what have you done for her?
What gifts have you given her?
How many sweet words
have you expressed to her?
See? This is the problem.
But, there is always a way out.
So, what should I do?
If she's absent from you,
you can go to seek her, right?
Don't you really like her?
I…I can…like her.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪