♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 17]
[What's this place?]
[This is the middle of the river,
where the Water-calming Stone is.]
[The divine energy is abundant here.]
[We can use this
to maintain his last shred of hope.]
[Take care of him.]
Divine Water-calming Stone,
our Water Tribe of the Mohe River
suffered from this calamity
because of my fault.
I bear deep hatred
and demand blood for blood.
I'm willing to fall to a devil
if I can kill my foe
[even at the cost of my life]
[or my soul being destructed.]
[I'll never regret it.]
Water-calming Sword,
follow me to get into the Shangqing realm
to slaughter Tian Huan.
[Why am I feeling unsettled?]
[Forget it.]
[Purifying the Seal is perilous.]
[I should get down to it,]
[or I'll spoil it.]
Why are you so upset?
Maid Qingniao in Xuanzhang Palace
was dismissed days ago
and left Shangqing Realm.
So you got lovesickness.
But I heard
many maids in several palaces
have been replaced
by the maids from Flying Serpent Tribe.
I heard Goddess Tian Huan did it.
After the gods fell,
I'm afraid Shangqing Realm
is no longer the same as in the past.
It's you again, little imp.
My honored guest,
you're welcome here.
Where's Tian Huan?
Follow me.
Goddess, have mercy on us.
We had cultivated ourselves
for thousands of years
before getting into Shangqing Realm.
Please don't drive us away.
I know it's hard for you
to get into the Realm.
But you can't blame me for this.
Just blame Sang Jiu.
What does it do with Lady Jiu?
Because you served her before,
I feel annoyed
when seeing you.
So,
is that a good reason?
What if I don't leave?
What?
I came to Yuqing Palace with God Ming Ye.
God Ming Ye
is also the master of Yuqing Palace.
If you want to drive me away,
we should argue this with his presence.
Are you threatening me with Ming Ye?
When the twelve gods were on the thrones,
no one
was dictatorial
or bullying in Shangqing Realm.
Everything should have impartiality.
How dare you offend me!
Goddess, please spare us…
Report.
Goddess,
Sang Jiu from the Mohe River
asks to see you
and says she wants to apologize.
She's putting her head
in the noose before I take action.
Sang Jiu,
don't you think it's too late
to apologize to me?
No.
Tian Huan,
I came here
to take your life.
You…
You fell to a devil.
You dirty and vulgar clam demon.
I'm sorry,
Goddess.
Today, you'll be killed
by a dirty and vulgar clam demon.
[The time has come.]
[Sang Jiu,]
[your divine essence
will soon be reshaped.]
-Lord Immortal.
Lord Immortal, help!
A demon got into Shangqing Realm just now.
[A devil?]
She took Goddess Tian Huan
and went to the southeastern spring.
Sang Jiu.
Are you crazy?
You've become a devil.
Ming Ye.
You finally came to save me.
She took away my divine essence.
Help me.
Sang Jiu.
If you can hear me,
just put down Tian Huan's divine essence.
Come here.
Put it down?
Sang Jiu!
Let go of me.
I must kill her.
Lord Immortal.
Help her out.
Yes.
[Sang Jiu,]
[what exactly happened to you?]
[How did you become a devil?]
That's what happened.
Lord Immortal.
Beryl died in such a grievance.
Believe me.
I'll get justice for you.
Get up.
Since you were scared today,
go back and take a good rest.
Thanks, Lord Immortal.
Has the Water Tribe
in the Mohe River been massacred?
Although being compelled,
you're generals from Shangqing Realm,
who should never be
obsequious or aid villains.
Lord Immortal.
We were wrong.
We were deceived by Tian Huan.
Since we returned from the Mohe River,
we have been feeling guilty.
Lord Immortal,
for the sake of our contribution
to the Realm,
please let us off lightly.
Please spare us.
All of you
will be sent to jail
and be deprived of cultivation.
Wait for your sentences.
Scram!
Take them away.
Yes.
Medicine King,
What's the cure
for Sang Jiu's condition?
I can't always tie her up
with Ruo-River rope.
Her degeneration
is due to her emotional turmoil
and unstable cultivation mind.
Being tormented by the ruination
of the Water Tribe,
Lady Jiu degenerated into a devil.
Mental illness can't be cured by medicine.
Mental illness?
It's not easy.
I'll go see her.
Wait.
Lord Immortal, if you show up now,
I'm afraid you'll remind her
of the painful memories,
and she'll sink deeper.
You'd better leave her alone,
letting the clear energy
dispel some of her devil energy.
You should give her some decoction
to resolve turbidity
and don't see her
until she cools down.
Lord Immortal.
Though this happened because of Tian Huan,
it's a fact that Sang Jiu became a devil,
broke into our gate,
and killed our soldiers.
Shangqing Realm has laws.
Lord Immortal,
you can't be partial to her.
That's right, Lord Immortal.
Shangqing Realm
has been irreconcilable with devils.
Otherwise, the sacrifice
of the Goddess of Space and others
would mean nothing.
Sang Jiu,
have you thought about this?
Ming Ye has been at odds with devils
for many years.
Many of his fellows
were killed by devils.
Since you've become a devil,
how could he tolerate you?
She was right.
There's no turning back for me.
Lord Immortal,
Goddess Tian Huan woke up.
She had lost her divine essence
and had been long soaked in the Ruo River.
She's now bawling.
Has she confessed?
Yes.
This is her statement.
She has a request.
She said her sin was heavy,
but
she wanted to see you anyway.
You tell Tian Huan.
She took the wrong path
and acted like a devil.
No.
She's eviler than a devil,
so we have nothing to talk about.
When she's punished by the thunderbolt,
and her soul is destructed,
I'll be there to supervise the execution.
How's it?
Goddess, don't worry.
I've notified the elders
of our tribe at your orders.
They'll soon go see God Ming Ye.
You give me such a precious gift.
Elders,
what do you want to exchange it for?
Please spare Tian Huan's life.
This crystal can help
Lady Jiu's clansmen come back to life.
Although Tian Huan made a huge mistake,
she's the Goddess of our tribe.
For the sake of the contribution
of the Flying Serpent Tribe,
please spare her life
and reshape her divine essence
before driving her away
from ShangQing Realm.
We promise
we'll put her
under house arrest
and forbid her
to step out of Mist Mountain forever.
I can spare her life.
But I won't reshape her divine essence
and release her.
It's too greedy of you.
God Ming Ye
insists on
not reshaping your divine essence
or releasing you.
Our elders have tried our best.
At least we saved your life.
Saved my life?
I lost my divine essence
and have been trapped in the hellhole.
How much longer can I live?
Even if I wouldn't suffer thunderbolt,
I'm waiting here for death.
Ming Ye,
how cruel you are.
It's ridiculous.
My father has been his benefactor,
and I love him deeply,
but he repaid me with this.
Ming Ye,
if you don't want to save me,
don't think you can save the clam demon.
Yanghe.
Come closer.
Tell the elders
to throw it into Barren Abyss
before telling the news to Sang Jiu.
Lord Immortal.
Has the Flying Serpent gone back?
Yes.
They have left Shangqing Realm.
How did they know
I've purified Bone-refining Seal,
which can reshape divine essence?
Maybe they've heard some rumors.
Keep an eye on Mist Mountain
and let me know the whereabouts
of those elders.
Yes.
Lord Immortal,
you just purified Bone-refining Seal
with the Quadripod,
which cost much of your energy.
And now you're refining
the ten-millennia crystal.
I'm worried about you.
I know how to take care of my body.
Don't be wordy.
[If I turn this crystal
into a spirit container]
[and put the Water Tribe's shells]
[into it.]
[After one thousand years of cultivation,]
[the Water Tribe will come back to life,]
[which will be a comfort to Sang Jiu]
[and bring her back to the right path.]
Have you heard of it?
God Ming Ye has absolved
Goddess Tian Huan.
Flying Serpent Tribe has a long history.
Through generations,
many heroes like Tian Hao
came from the tribe.
At least God Ming Ye
would show some mercy.
That's right.
I think so.
But the poor Water Tribe was killed.
I heard only Sang You survived
with a serious injury.
He was then thrown into Barren Abyss
and was as good as dead.
[Sang You.]
Sang You.
Sang Jiu.
God Ji Ze.
Is that you?
Yes.
You shouldn't have come here.
You're a demon.
Don't step forward,
or you'll be doomed eternally.
Sang Jiu,
leave now.
I won't go
until I find Sang You.
Sang Jiu,
don't be stubborn.
The abyss is full of devils.
You won't make it.
Where's Ming Ye?
Why did he let you come alone?
Now, I have the crystal.
Next,
all I need to do is find all the skeletons
of the Water Tribe.
Lord Immortal.
Our soldier reported
the masters of the Vine Snake Tribe
tended to be suspicious.
They had contact
with the servants
of Yuqing Palace in secret.
Lord Immortal.
Bad news!
Lady Jiu is gone.
A soldier was killed in the palace.
Lord Immortal.
[Sang You, I was being a fool.]
[I should have listened to you.]
[Please be alive.]
[This is…]
Sang You.
It's great that you're alive.
Sorry that I'm late.
I'll take you away.
I was wondering who you are,
you two little clam demons.
Having been trapped for so long,
I'm starving.
You're our full meal.
Get away.
Don't be arrogant, little clam.
Neither of you will leave here alive.
Guys,
take her.
Aren't you God Ming Ye?
You're at odds with us.
Why did you degrade yourself to come here?
The God of War, are you risking your life
for the little clam, your beloved one?
Unfortunately, you came too late.
She's now a mass of bleeding flesh.
All my men, take him.
[Why?]
[Why should we be bullied?]
[Tian Huan has done so many sins]
[but has been forgiven.]
[My clansmen had done nothing bad]
[but had to suffer.]
[Sang Jiu.]
Sang Jiu.
Wake up.
Stop degenerating.
Degenerating?
If you so-called noble and pure gods
and goddesses
do something evil,
that'll be degeneration,
won't it?
Sang Jiu,
go home with me.
I will make up for all the mistakes
that I made in the past.
Go home?
Where is my home?
Tell me where it is!
[She's being very emotional now.]
[Whatever I say,]
[she won't listen to me.]
[I should calm her down first]
[and stop her degenerating.]
Sang Jiu.
Ming Ye, tell me
if the soldiers who massacred
the Water Tribe
are your troops.
How will you punish them?
Kill them?
They're deceived by Tian Huan
owing to my weak discipline.
I'll give them a severe penalty.
Good.
Have you forgiven Tian Huan
and spared her life?
[God Ming Ye, please spare Tian Huan.]
[Our tribe would give the crystal bowl]
[to help regenerate Lady Jiu's tribe.]
Yes.
But Tian Huan lost her divine essence.
Even if I don't kill her,
she doesn't have many years to live.
Ming Ye, you're so kind.
If you spare their lives,
who should pay for the deaths of my father
and my clansmen?
Do you know what I want?
I want them all to die.
When they raised their swords
to kill children and the old
by the Mohe River,
they had no kindness or sympathy at all.
I'll make them
pay for their cruelty
and indifference!
Sang Jiu,
I understand your pain.
But I can't see you become a demon.
You're burying yourself with them.
It's not worth it.
Who are you?
Who do you think you are,
telling me what's worthwhile
and what's not?
Piss off!
Get away!
You…
Sang Jiu.
[I need to figure out
how to take them away first.]
Sang Jiu.
Ming Ye, it has been a long time.
Ji Ze.
Why are you in Barren Abyss?
I thought you were…
Yes.
My body has been destroyed,
but my spirit still exists.
I decide to be imprisoned
and guard Barren Abyss
with my divine body.
I can't move in the formation's center,
but I may help you to leave.
It's perilous in Barren Abyss.
Be sure not to come here again.
Ji Ze.
Ji Ze, wait.
Goddess, forgive us.
We arrived late.
Without God Ming Ye being here,
it's much easier to enter
into the barrier.
Since he took a risk to enter Barren Abyss
to save his girl,
why don't we
get Yuqing Palace back?
Why did you bring me here?
I thought you would bring me back
to Shangqing Realm and imprison me.
You know, I killed someone.
I promised you
I'd stand by your side.
It's not a lie.
Whether you'll be an immortal or a demon,
you're always my Sang Jiu.
Where's my brother?
I've tried my best.
But he's severely injured
and can't recover fully now.
Don't worry.
As long as we cultivate your clansmen
using the crystal bowl,
they will have the chance to regenerate.
Sang You.
Put the remains of the Water Tribe
into the bowl,
and your clansmen will be back
after 1,000 years.
[The divine power in this bowl
is Ming Ye's…]
Sang Jiu,
since you just became a demon,
you're salvageable.
I've refined Bone-refining Seal
and will help you
reshape your divine essence with it.
I've asked Medicine King.
He said if you kept a cultivation mind,
with time,
you could get away from the demonic path
and back to the immortal path.
Sang Jiu, I really enjoyed the life
that I spent with you here.
[For the rest of my life,]
[All I want is to live such a life,]
whatever the cost.
Could you…?
Could you trust me once again?
How did you get
the ten-millennium crystal?
From the Vine Snake Tribe.
Sang Jiu, listen to me.
They said they would
give me the crystal bowl
if I spared Tian Huan's life.
I agreed.
I know you bear deep hatred.
But only with the crystal bowl
can you bring your clansmen back to life.
You care about the lives
of your clansmen
more than that of Tian Huan,
right?
Ming Ye,
you're impartial and lead by example.
You're an excellent god.
But you must understand
this is not a transaction.
Not everything in this world
can be measured fairly
or exchanged equally.
Ming Ye, do you still remember
the story my father
told me?
It's about the king who cut off his flesh
to save the dove.
He chose to do that
just out of his compassion.
The white dove looked so cute.
Anyone would have compassion for it.
As for me,
I had a crush on you
and fell in love with you.
Even if I knew I had to pay for it,
I still took the knife.
I thought
I had enough courage to bear the cost.
But I never expected
such a huge cost.
It's too huge.
The king lost all his flesh
because of his kindness.
And I caused the extinction
of the Water Tribe because of you.
How ridiculous I am.
How sinful I am.
I'm only a clam demon,
not as devout as the king.
He didn't regret it,
so he became immortal.
But I can't.
I regret it.
I'm so regretful
that I want to kill myself.
Since the day Tian Huan slaughtered
my tribe by the Mohe River,
my heart
has been filled
with redemption and revenge.
There's no place for you.
No.
Sang Jiu.
I'll find a way
to save my brother.
I don't want to owe you
a debt.
I'll kill
my foe on my own.
Tian Huan,
Vine Snake Tribe produced many heroes.
How could you enter into collusion
and steal the crown?
Yeah.
Our tribe produced many heroes.
As the daughter of Tian Hao,
why can't I be the leader of the realm?
Ridiculous.
You took credit
for your father's contribution
but made no contribution.
How can you be the leader?
When we followed God Ming Ye
to fight with demons,
where were you?
We will never bow to you.
When God Ming Ye returns,
your tribe will get what you deserve!
Ming Ye.
He degraded himself
to go to the Barren Abyss
to save a demon.
What qualifies him to condemn me?
Besides, it's not certain whether he'll
get out of there.
That's it.
You refuse to take me as your leader.
Soldiers,
throw them into the Quadripod
and burn them.
You…
With enough lives in it,
there will be divine essence for me.
It's a good idea
to refine divine essence
with the Quadripod.
I wonder whether I'll extract
something useful
if I put your tribe into the quadripod.
Sang Jiu,
you're actually alive!
She's a demon.
Arrest and kill her.
No.
Don't kill me.
I didn't expect
that a goddess would be afraid to die.
So you're no different from us,
little imps.
Don't think you're nobler.
Sang Jiu.
Do you think you can get
your clansmen back by killing me?
Do you think you and Ming Ye
can be back together?
Dream on you.
You're still in denial.
I admit
you're much luckier than me
because you're going to reunite
with your tribe.
I thought to myself,
and I don't have anything to say to you.
Goodbye.
Tian Huan.
Here, I take an oath
to the world.
I'll find and kill Vine Snake Tribe
until they've been exterminated.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪