♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 13]
Lianhua,
put away these flowers for me.
Lord Immortal,
where do these flowers come from?
Where else can it be?
From the garden of God of Wood.
Lord Immortal,
you just stole her flowers.
There are countless flowers in her garden.
I only clipped a few tiny branches
just for the sake of the scent.
Take them back and put them in the jade vase.
Remember to change water everyday.
I… I dropped them.
You little brat.
You've been absent-minded and careless
in your cultivation every day.
Now you've lost my flowers.
If this goes on, how can you immortalize?
Lord Immortal, I'm sorry.
Show me your hand.
I have to teach you a lesson today.
Go.
Find my camellias back.
If you can't find them,
don't ever come back.
You get it?
Yes.
Just go.
The gods and demons will eventually have a war.
I can't see through the causes and effects.
You're bound to have a
worldly relationship with these camellias.
Lianhua,
go cultivate and hide in the mortal world.
You've just got happily married.
Why are you willing to
leave your beautiful wife and go out?
Today the twelve gods gathered
to discuss the solution to eliminate demons.
I can't be absent.
You're no fun at all.
My jokes don't work on you.
So boring.
Chu Huang, you came so early.
I'm just getting some air,
in case when you guys arrive later,
you'll nag me to sleep.
Ming Ye suddenly got married at such a young age.
So many fairies are crying their eyes out.
Had I not known
that you're the most descent man there is,
I'd think that you've had
an affair in the Mohe River.
Even you're making fun of me.
No need to explain.
We all know how it is.
The only problem is
how are you gonna treat Goddess Tian Huan?
I've no personal feelings for Tian Huan.
She used to be my subordinate,
and she will remain so.
It's good if you know that.
Now you've married this
clam spirit princess.
Although you're of two races,
you can't give her the cold shoulder.
I understand.
My eyes see through previous and after lives.
How about I take a look for you?
See how this marriage goes?
Little Ji Ze,
quit showing off your abilities.
Even though we're all gods,
our marriages are determined by our own actions.
The innocent have no sorrow.
Just let him live his own life.
Everyone's here.
Let's go.
Without my divine essence,
a large part of my shooting power is lost too.
Watch out!
Who's up there?
It's me.
You…
What are you doing up there?
I saw that these fruits were nice
and no one's here to pick them.
So I wanted to eat some to quench my thirst.
Are…
Are they edible?
Aren't these your fruit trees?
You haven't taste any?
I…
The Xiannai trees have been growing
in Shangqing for 10,000 years.
They were always on their own.
No one has ever picked their fruits.
Gosh.
Don't tell my these fruits are expensive.
I've eaten a lot of them.
But you…
Why do you eat everything you see?
What if they were poisonous?
No, they're not.
I won't pick any.
Why don't you try one?
I…
Just try one. It's super sweet.
I'm going back to my room.
Morning!
They do taste good.
Thank you.
You're so awesome, Madam!
My arm hurts so much.
Be level with the arrow.
Raise your arm a little.
This may save you a little strength.
What do you mean?
Draw the bow one more time.
Raise your arm high.
What did you say?
Nothing. I'm leaving now.
I didn't say anything.
Why was he being shy?
This bow works better.
Ming Ye,
I like the bow you gave me.
A gift for a gift.
I'll take you to see some good stuff.
Be there or be square.
The shooting stars here are so beautiful!
When I was in Mohe River,
I used to look up to the sky.
That's where the most beautiful stars are.
I love this.
I wonder if you love this or not?
What?
Something's not right!
What do you mean?
Normally Ming Ye
would spend 12 hours in the military camp.
He's ready for battle all year round.
But these days,
he keeps heading home.
Aren't all married men like this?
This won't do.
I'm gonna see what kind of beauty
this little clam spirit is.
She change Ming Ye's unchangeable routine?
What are you gonna do?
Let's go.
We haven't been to Yuqing Palace for long.
Let's ask for a cup of tea from Ming Ye.
If anyone doesn't know you,
they'll take you as a thief!
Good heavens!
Is this still the Ming Ye I know?
Did my eyes serve me right?
This move may not only hurt your war mates,
it will also leave you defenseless,
and give your enemies chances to hurt you.
Then let me try again.
Try again.
Raise your arm.
Did you see?
I mean the sword, not me.
Exchange moves with me.
Okay.
I obviously saw this sword
going in that direction.
Why is it here?
Goddess Chu Huang, why are you like Ji Ze?
Coming without appointment.
Because you're hiding your wife from us.
If I notice you in advance,
will I be able to see this harmonious scene?
You scared me.
Your little wife is so good.
One single move and my face is nearly ruined.
I didn't control my move.
It's not Sang Jiu's fault.
Your remarks were just sour grapes.
Sorry.
I was being careless.
Lord Immortal, are you alright?
Did I scare you just now?
I didn't expect that we're connected in a way.
Ji Ze,
what do you mean?
You'll understand when the time comes.
It's just that you and she both know,
but Ming Ye and Sang Jiu don't.
What do you mean?
Sang Jiu, my little friend.
I visited you on a whim.
I didn't bring you any gift.
How about I give you four words?
Remember why you came.
Guess it's something not for us to know.
Miss Sang Jiu,
you don't need to ask in detail.
You just need to remember what Ji Ze said.
It'll be useful someday.
You're Ji Ze,
the God of Time?
That's me.
This is Chu Huang,
the Goddess of Space.
No wonder.
Just now this sword obviously flied forward,
but it fell by my side.
So it's due to your divine power.
Miss Sang Jiu,
I don't know why,
but you seem so familiar to me.
I didn't bring any gift for a sudden visit.
Shall I give you a wisp of divine power?
What's this?
It can connect you and Ming Ye.
As long as you wish,
you may see him across time and space.
But you can only use it once.
Thanks.
It turns out that you're here to send gifts.
Aren't we here for the tea?
Let's go to the tea room.
Since Lord Tian Hao fell
and you took over his palace,
I've never come here once.
Speaking of which, how's Goddess Tian Huan?
She's already recovered.
But she hasn't come to herself yet.
Jiu, what happened?
Brother,
why am I like this?
Jiu,
your demonic energy has started to devour you.
I am a spirit to begin with.
How can I be devoured by demonic energy?
You used to have divine essence.
You practiced immortal arts since young.
Your core and meridians
were the same as immortals'.
Now that your divine essence is lost,
your demonic nature is back after some time.
Foul energy grows inside you.
It's like feeding meat to a rabbit
and feeding grass to a tiger.
If you don't deal with it carefully,
I'm afraid you may lose your sanity.
Then what should I do?
You've been married into Shangqing
for over a hundred days.
Did Ming Ye…
He never tried dual-cultivation with you, right?
No need to lie to me.
If he's willing to do that,
he'll be able to neutralize
your foul energy with his clear energy.
That way, not only will you not be devoured,
you'll be able to maintain your immortal body.
And you can advance your cultivation level.
Back when father
insisted that you be married there,
he did that partly for this reason.
What?
Did that flood dragon treat you badly?
No.
Ming Ye is a good person.
A good person?
He leave you all to yourself for so long.
What's good about this husband?
Jiu, come back.
Father and I will
find a way to suppress your demonic energy.
No, I can't go back yet.
You mustn't tell dad about this.
You'll make him worry for nothing.
Where are you going?
Since you are too shy about it,
as your brother,
I should naturally visit my new brother-in-law.
I'll ask him properly
why he treats you like this.
Why are you so unreasonable?
Since I didn't know about the demonic energy,
Ming Ye must not know it, either.
Now that I knew,
I'll just talk to him.
Why were you so aggressive?
I shouldn't have told you.
I…
I was trying to do you justice!
I pick this path by my self.
I married this man by my decision.
There's no justice to do me.
What's more,
Ming Ye didn't treat me badly.
Instead, he taught me swordsmanship and archery.
I've made great progress.
Swordsmanship and archery?
You won't understand anyway.
It's getting late.
Ming Ye's probably on his way home.
I'm gonna go back to Shangqing
and talk to him about dual-cultivation.
You…
You're just gonna talk to him about it directly?
Otherwise?
Alright.
Then go ahead.
Whatever trouble you have,
remember to come back, back to Mohe.
I don't care who's right or wrong,
I'll always be by your side.
Why aren't you practicing?
Are you willing to try dual-cultivation with me?
What?
My demonic energy is devouring me.
I heard dual-cultivation can neutralize
foul energy with clear energy.
If you mind it,
I'll think of another way.
You do have a lot of foul energy inside.
It's my fault not to realize it sooner.
This place is clear and cool.
It's perfect for dual-cultivation.
Sang Jiu,
close your eyes.
Breathe in and out with me.
So this is dual-cultivation, huh?
Why was Sang You so mysterious about it?
I thought it's gonna be quite embarrassing.
Sang Jiu.
Get closer to me.
The Healing Barrier
cost quite a lot of treasures.
Goddess Tian Huan?
Great. I'm gonna tell Lord Immortal.
Don't bother.
I'll go tell him myself
and thank him for healing me.
But Goddess…
What?
I'm afraid you can't go now.
Lord Immortal is
doing co-cultivation with his wife.
Wife?
Ming Ye isn't married yet.
What wife?
Goddess Tian Huan… Goddess…
Goddess Tian Huan.
I feel much better now.
This is for you.
Thanks for today.
I'm going to sleep.
Sang Jiu.
Anytime you have a negative energy problem,
come to me.
I will.
Good night.
So,
that clam woman married you,
right?
Sang Jiu married me
three months ago.
At that time,
you were still in a coma.
So, my coma was just in time.
Three months ago, it was me who went to war with you.
It was me
who took a walk with you here in Yuqing Palace.
It was also me
who dug out the Ancient Crystal for you!
You got the Ancient Crystal
from the Water-calming Stone?
Yes, but so what?
You were dying.
I had to save your life!
If I had known this,
I wouldn't have saved you that desperately.
Then I wouldn't lose everything
or live under someone else's roof now.
You grew up here.
It's not someone else's roof.
Then tell me, Ming Ye.
You and that woman
stay here every day,
loving each other.
What am I?
A maid for your wife?
Tian Huan,
no one takes you as a maid.
If you really feel bad,
I can leave with Sang Jiu
and we'll live somewhere else.
Ming Ye,
you're the God of War.
And this is your palace.
You'll leave your own palace for her?
Why don't you stop being the God of War, too?
Enough.
I know you're being too emotional now.
When you calm down tomorrow,
I'll talk to you.
Fine.
Very well.
Ming Ye,
that woman is despicable.
She took advantage of your sympathy
and tricked you.
You just can't see that.
How can I make you see her through?
You two
are close to Sang Jiu, right?
Greetings, Goddess.
Lady… Lady Sang
asked us what Lord Immortal loved.
Then, we talked to her.
When Lady Sang first came,
she made every attempt to fawn over Lord Immortal.
But Lord Immortal didn't accept her.
Until…
Continue.
Until one day she saw Lord Immortal
under the Immortal Tree.
Seeing her climb the tree and pick fruit,
Lord Immortal didn't blame her.
Instead…
Instead, he got closer to her.
The Immortal Tree?
Cut the tree down.
-Aye.
Too bad.
So, your name is Sang Jiu?
Goddess Tian Huan?
It's so great to see you're awake.
Yeah.
I finally woke up.
Thank you for taking care of Ming Ye
by the Mohe River.
Or I wouldn't know what to do.
I also want to thank you
for looking after him lately.
I have something to tell you.
I wonder if you're available, Lady Sang.
So, Ming Ye had the tree cut down?
Yes.
For the sake that you married him so young,
I told you secretly.
Don't let anyone else know it.
Thank you.
I heard every day
you put a Hongnai Fruit on his desk.
But haven't you heard about that?
Ming Ye, the God of War,
hates it most when someone gets into his room,
touches his stuff or pesters him.
[Lord Immortal seems to have no preferences.]
[He doesn't like anyone to get close, either.]
I've heard about that.
But I thought…
Thought what?
You thought you were special?
You thought he liked you?
Fine, I'll be the nice one
and tell you something more.
That your father forced Ming Ye
to return his kindness
is known to everyone in Shangqing realm.
Ming Ye helps you remove your negative energy
only because he has to,
in case others gossip behind his back.
Besides, Ming Ye used to be an immortal.
Now, he's a demigod
with the pure elixir.
But…
Your negative demonic energy
is terribly harmful to him,
especially to his elixir.
Every day, Ming Ye leads his army
against the Devil's Army,
risking his life.
If your demonic energy hurts him
so that he gets wounded in the battle,
wouldn't you regret it?
I had co-cultivation because I didn't know this.
If I had known my demonic energy was harmful,
I wouldn't have asked for that.
Now, you know.
I won't do that again.
He should have told me.
He's a man and the God of War.
How could he have the nerve to tell you
even the mere co-cultivation with you
would get him into trouble?
Ming Ye led his army out before dawn.
I wonder how he's doing now.
He had co-cultivation only once.
As the God of War,
he can't be that fragile.
You'd better worry about yourself.
Without his help,
if your negative energy pushes back,
what can you do?
I don't know.
I have to think of another way.
Looks like
I have to help you more.
Now that I disturbed your co-cultivation,
I should find a solution for you.
Huan, you have a solution?
When your demonic power accumulates,
don't bother Ming Ye.
Come to me.
Thank you, Huan.
[Ming Ye was unhappy.]
[But why didn't he tell me?]
[Why did he vent his anger on you?]
Ming Ye.
Thank you.
Leave it there.
[This is for you.]
[Thanks for today.]
[Today is the day for co-cultivation.]
[Yesterday, Sang Jiu should have
come for co-cultivation.]
[ waited the whole day but she didn't come.]
[I wonder if she was in trouble.]
Did your wife elope with someone else?
What?
Then why have you pulled a long face,
as if you wanted to bite people?
Sang Jiu is a girl.
If you ask her directly,
she'll be shy.
[We haven't done co-cultivation for days.]
[Her negative energy must have accumulated.]
[She's supposed to come to me.]
[I must get this straight to her.]
[The pushing back of demonic energy is serious.]
[We agreed to do co-cultivation every three days.]
[It can't be delayed like this.]
[What a beautiful night!]
[Sang Jiu likes stars.]
[I'll collect some starlight
and give it to her.]
[Hope she'll like it.]
Goddess Tian Huan,
I…
Your demonic energy is pushing back, huh?
You don't need to tell me.
I smelt that from far afar.
Don't worry.
Come with me.
Don't disturb anyone else.
This is the Refining Spring.
Your demonic energy will be cleaned
when you bathe in it.
Quite a lot of treasures in this realm.
But this is a place for immortals.
Why is there a spring
for the cleaning of demonic energy?
This realm is for immortals.
But over thousands of years,
a few demons have come occasionally.
The Spring is natural.
Who knows why it is here?
The water temperature is perfect.
Come have a try.
Jiu, what's wrong?
It… It hurts a lot.
No. It feels good.
If I weren't so busy,
I would like to bathe in it with you.
Oh, I know.
The Spring is for cleaning your demonic energy.
Your vigorous energy makes you feel the pain.
But it works very well.
Look, your skin bathed in the water
has recovered, right?
Yes, indeed.
Get down there.
Jiu,
it won't work well unless you bathe for a long time.
I can't hold on.
It hurts too much.
As if my body were burning.
Jiu,
before you suffer enough,
you can't get what you want.
I heard you wanted to join Ming Ye's army.
How could you
before your demonic energy is eliminated?
I wouldn't deceive you.
Bathe in the Spring for a quarter
and then you can leave.
You'll be refreshed
with no more negative energy.
I've got something else to do.
I have to go.
By the way,
when Ming Ye knows your demonic energy pushes back,
he'll ask how you handle it.
You can tell him
someone else helped you out.
But don't tell him I was the one.
Ming Ye hates it when those around him get too close.
I get it.
Don't worry.
It really works.
Give it to me.
No one knew it, huh?
Don't worry, Goddess.
I've killed that man from Yiyue tribe.
No one else knew where his water was.
For so little water,
I did quite a lot.
Anyone, no matter what he is,
can't resist the burning of the water.
Once he touches it,
his energy
will be gone.
Sadly, I could only apply some in the Spring
and it wouldn't kill you.
You…
What's up?
Ming Ye,
are you waiting for someone?
For your wife?
If you're here for the scenery
because you have nothing else to do, fine.
But if you're waiting for her to do co-cultivation,
let me remind you.
She doesn't need you anymore.
What's your point?
Haven't you realized that?
Lately, Sang Jiu has been terribly cool to you.
Today, she should have come for co-cultivation.
But she's nowhere to be seen.
Even I can tell
she's avoiding you.
Why?
Because you were married by force.
It's understandable that you don't love each other.
But don't blame her.
I heard someone else
helped her with co-cultivation.
So,
she probably doesn't need you anymore.
How do you know?
Calm down.
Her demonic energy has increased lately.
You also felt that, right?
Today, she should have had co-cultivation with you.
But she didn't come.
If you don't believe me,
ask her when she's back.
Ye,
you can't force her.
But if you insist,
I'll help you persuade her.
As a woman,
I can talk better with her, anyway.
No need.
All right.
Then, enjoy your time waiting.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪