The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 40]
Li Susu,
pick up your cup.
Do you demons and monsters
also make toasts to heaven and earth?
No.
This cup of wine
is for all the sins in the world.
This one
is for all the death.
They do worth the toast.
This last cup of bridal wine
is to wish us be together forever.
Lady of Spirituality,
today is our wedding day.
Do you have any problem with it?
Should I be overjoyed
to stay in this dark and sunless hellhole?
That was negligent of me.
Mount Changze has towering terrain,
and this Devil Palace is gloomy and dark.
You would certainly
not get used to living here.
However,
it's easy to fix the problem.
It's time to restore this Devil Palace
to its former appearance.
Return of the Devil God,
in chaos are heaven and earth!
When I became the Devil God,
all kinds of karma appeared before my eyes.
I only understood that
good and evil are all caused by karma.
As long as the sins
in the world do not stop,
the Devil God
will never perish.
Only when the All-in-Distress Way is opened,
the world is in chaos,
and all living beings
can truly return to the same place.
What's that?
It's the Devil Palace! It's in the air!
What?
Hurry up, everybody.
- Yes.
- OK.
- Let's go.
Hurry.
My wife,
are you satisfied
with the gift I have given you?
It seems that
the Four Continents and Three Realms
all belong to you now.
Exactly.
when the All-in-Distress Way
completely swallows the world,
the Four Continents and Three Realms
will all belong to me.
And you
will be my caged bird in this life,
as well as the most interesting decoration
in this Devil Palace.
Indeed, you gave me
a generous gift.
I should give you a big gift in return.
Chongyu Harp.
Li Susu,
you should know that
with your current spiritual cultivation,
you can't hurt me in the slightest.
Although I can't deal with you,
the Chongyu Harp is a divine instrument
with divine power contained in it.
You want to burn the Chongyu Harp
and release the divine power?
Yes.
It has accompanied me for many years.
When the divine power is exhausted,
it's time to say goodbye.
You are quite generous with this.
I won't need to use it anyway.
The Devil God is in the air.
What's that red light?
It's the Incarnation-Abandoning Array.
Susu started
the Incarnation-Abandoning Array.
The Incarnation-Abandoning Array?
You know it?
Li Susu,
would you rather die
than be my wife?
No,
if it's possible,
I will bring you to death with me.
Gongye, what should we do?
Li Susu has trapped the Devil God.
It's a great time for us to start the Array.
Susu can't avoid getting hurt.
Today, all sects are
throwing caution to the wind
regardless of cost
in order to eliminate demons,
not to save Li Susu.
Wow,
bring me to death with you. Great words.
Li Susu,
you should indeed hate me,
but you should hate yourself more.
If you could have awakened earlier
that love to me is nothing but illusory.
How could
the Four Continents and Three Realms
become like this today?
Yes,
all immortal sects
it was too foolish of me.
follow my orders!
Get in position!
Yes!
It was my attempt
to bring you into the light
that brought such heavy darkness
to the Three Realms.
Now I can only make up for it with my life
and try my best to remedy this.
Even if you start
the Incarnation-Abandoning Array,
you won't kill me.
Whatever you do
will be in vain.
Back then, the twelve gods
abandoned their incarnation.
Although they failed to
annihilate the Devil God in one fell swoop,
they severely injured him.
Only then did the God of War
execute the devil
and purify the Three Realms.
I am a disciple of Hengyang Sect
and the daughter of Qu Xuan Zi.
Sacrificing my life to
eliminate the devil is my duty.
Even if I die today,
there will be fellow disciples
who will do the same
until you are killed.
Tantai Jin,
farewell.
Go,
stop them.
Guard the array!
Looks like everything has started.
Come on, hurry up!
Li Susu,
your fellow disciples are here.
Since you are so persistent,
then
I will send you and them to be buried
together for the All-in-Distress Way.
Li Susu,
come here.
Let's witness the destruction of the immortal sects.
Gongye,
all sects are ready.
Tantai Jin,
today
is your last day alive.
Celestial Punishment Array,
open!
It's the Celestial Punishment.
Looks like your friends from immortal sects
are giving up on you.
As long as the Devil God can be killed,
I will die without regret.
In this Celestial Punishment,
there are eighty-one thunderbolts.
Even with my Devil God's body,
it is difficult to retreat unscathed.
Abandoning you
in exchange for severely injuring me,
your immortal sects are really cunning.
But you,
you still want to trap me for them
and perish with me.
Being hit by the Celestial Punishment
hurts a lot,
and I don't want to take it.
Since you are bent on dying,
take it for me.
Tantai Jin!
Li Susu,
goodbye.
These eighty-one thunderbolts
are what you deserve.
Enjoy them,
and regard it as your compensation to me!
What? Tantai Jin escaped!
What should we do, Chief Gongye?
Yeah.
Tantai Jin!
Chief Gongye,
you really don't care about
details or old feelings.
when you start the array.
You even have the heart
to kill Susu.
As long as we get rid of you,
Susu's death is glorious and meaningful.
Xiaoyao Sword-play,
break!
Who are these kids?
We are disciples of the Xiaoyao Sect!
Immortal Zhaoyou's students!
Gongye Jiwu,
with your power,
you wouldn't have such abilities.
What have you done?
Everything I did
is just to kill you.
Gongye Jiwu,
you used a forbidden spell
to absorb the power
of your fellow disciples.
Now you have completely changed.
Do you even know who you are now?
So what?
As long as I can kill you,
what's wrong with
borrowing a little of their power?
Once he goes into devilry,
he will be completely beyond salvation.
Gongye Jiwu,
stop it.
you have gone awry.
That was how you treated me too.
Gongye Jiwu,
you shouldn't be like this,
not tyrannical
not filthy,
or twisted.
I will repay
all my various debts to you.
Gongye Jiwu,
don't fall into evilness anymore.
Jiwu,
don't let evil thoughts control you.
This is the sin
that has accumulated
since the beginning of the world,
and also the reason why you want to destroy
the Four Continents and Three Realms.
I am the Devil God
my life and death are related with you,
my prosperity and decline
are connected with you.
The evil bone has left my body
and empowered the All-in-Distress Way.
It is only one step away,
just like the great battle
between gods and demons.
Run!
Get out of here!
Li Susu,
hate me from the bottom of your heart.
Tantai Jin,
What are you doing?
The God-slaughtering Crossbow?
How can we give up
without fighting till the end?
Yeah. Our immortal sects lasted 10,000 years.
Today at the Barren Abyss,
we'd rather die than retreat!
Everyone, sword formation!
We do need to finish this.
Is this 10,000 years ago
[or later?]
[If it's before the war of gods,]
[why is there already the Heaven Lake?]
[If it's after,]
[why are the celestial pillars still here?]
I never knew that
there's such a world in my heart.
That's because
it only exists when you
look at it.
Mother.
We've been waiting for you for too long…
Too long…
Li Susu.
Come with me.
Where is this place?
I don't know.
But this is
the last place that
hasn't been devoured by All-in-distress Way.
It's going to disappear soon.
Tantai Jin,
the reason why it hasn't been devoured
is because it's the place
farthest from All-in-distress Way.
Farthest from the Devil Palace and killing.
Farthest from the demon realm
where there's bloodshed.
Li Susu,
what are you trying to say?
So,
in the last moment,
we still have some time to talk.
Li Susu,
you've broke through the Heartless Way
and immortalized.
Now,
you're the only god in this world
and the only one who can kill the Devil God.
You actually have time to talk with me?
So,
this is what you want.
To let me kill you?
You figured it out.
Yeah, Tantai Jin.
So, you don't have to
wear this false husk anymore.
The moment when I broke through Heartless Way,
I saw every corner of this world
and heard every sound between heaven and earth.
I can sense everything in the world,
including your heart.
[You've absorbed the power of the Devil God,]
[but you were never controlled by him.]
[But you still chose to show up in front of me]
as the Devil God.
You forced me to abandon my love
to let me go through nirvana.
You want to watch me
and end all these.
I'm sorry.
This is the only way.
It should also be the ending of the Devil God.
♪Take a look at this world that we love♪
♪Reviewing the past years♪
♪The vivid and splendid dreams
are but a regret that won't fade, it seems♪
♪Rather than wake from this slumber
I'd prefer the dream to last forever♪
♪A bond of marriage
entwined for thousands of years♪
Tantai Jin,
I wanted to protect you,
but I fooled you time after time.
I wanted to save you,
but I shot six Soul-slaying Spikes
into your heart.
I used to
wish to live a full life with you
until we get old,
but now we can't grow old anyway.
♪I can exchange everything for this life♪
I didn't expect that
the existence of me
is destined
for the death of you.
♪While the fireworks of life
are short-lived and easily enjoyed♪
♪But this time, who will come and go♪
It's okay.
Susu,
This life of mine is so hard.
I'll let you end it for me.
♪I'm never heartless♪
♪My emotions ebb and flow like the seasons♪
♪One who wants to get drunk needs no alcohol♪
Let me take you somewhere.
♪Not for heaven and earth,
but only for your heart♪
♪The longing never ends♪
Why do you bring me here?
I just wanted to show you the views here.
This world looks so small.
But what a shame.
Only you and I can see such views.
Yeah.
Look.
The mountains are like peas.
The rivers are like lines.
Even the All-in-distress Way
looks just like a tiny speck of stain.
Every living soul
is too small to be visible.
This is what the gods see.
The mortals living in it
will never see such scenery
even after exhausting their whole lives.
That's why they can never see through.
That's why they can never break free.
You are different.
You can.
You can save all from disasters.
You can change the fate of
four continents and three realms.
The purpose of the Devil God
was never uniting the three realms.
What he truly wanted to do
is destroy everything
and let it return to chaos.
Susu,
I've connected myself
with the All-in-distress Way.
The All-in-distress Way and the Devil God
live and die together.
Kill me,
and All-in-distress Way will be destroyed too.
The conflicts and fate of the 10,000 years
will eventually come to an end.
Tantai Jin,
I still have a lot…
A lot of words…
That I want to say to you.
I'm listening.
♪I fly in the direction you go♪
♪And look back with my last strength♪
♪You're the only hope♪
♪In my despair♪
♪Life is short, but love is long♪
♪We go separate ways♪
♪Right or wrong, success or failure♪
But you're too bad.
I don't wanna say them to you.
♪Broken, rebuilt♪
♪I don't care about my tears of sadness♪
♪I won't follow the destined path of my life♪
♪When the mystic bird returns
who will it be then?♪
♪Die Bored♪
♪Not Mine♪
♪I've searched endlessly
in hopes of meeting you in this life♪
♪I've become the light traveling in the dark♪
♪A drop of tear, a pinch of dust♪
I'll say these words to you
when we meet again.
♪I've searched endlessly
in hopes of meeting you in this life♪
Okay.
♪A drop of tear♪
♪But a dream lasts forever♪
Susu,
let go.
No.
Just this time,
let me hold you tight.
Without the Devil God existing,
the world won't need a god.
Okay.
Look!
The All-in-distress Way disappeared!
[The All-in-distress Way.]
[I'm sorry, Susu.]
[I'm gonna lie to you again.]
This
will be the ending of you and me.
Look! That thing is gone!
-That's right.
-It's true!
This is great!
We're saved!
-This is great!
-We're saved!
The All-in-distress Way is gone!
Look, the All-in-distress Way is gone!
This is the tomb of the King of Jing.
[I'll give you a chance]
[to pick a parcel of land that you like.]
[Take a look at]
[where you'd like to be buried.]
[Stop showing off.]
[Who said I'm gonna spend my life with you?]
[Tomb of Ye Xiwu, Loving Wife of Tantai Jin]
[Tomb of Tantai Jin, Loving Husband of Ye Xiwu]
[Answer me,]
[do you love me?]
[We've been husband and wife after all.]
[Of course I love you.]
[No.]
[What I want is not the marital relationship.]
[I just want you to love me
with your heart and soul.]
[Tomb of Tantai Jin, Loving Husband of Ye Xiwu]
[Tomb of Ye Xiwu, Loving Wife of Tantai Jin]
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
♪That's about to fall from the edge of the sky♪
♪I wanna hang a glittering butterfly there
till the snow falls♪
♪I wanna hang it in a wrong time♪
♪To forget my everything♪
♪I wanna hang a dream there
and trade you with a drop of tear♪
♪Hearts burn like flames♪
♪Why don't we just be like this♪
♪For ten thousand years?♪
♪Let's freeze time before we say goodbye♪
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
Tantai Jin,
are you leaving?
Yeah, I am.
Alright.
Then I'll be waiting here for you to return.
You must come back early.
Okay.
I'll be back soon.
Tantai Jin,
don't be sad.
You're not the Devil God.
You're not a murderer
nor a monster that brings disasters.
Your name is Tantai Jin.
You're the one I love the most.
♪I miss you like the sands miss the desert♪
♪O, how I suffered inside♪
♪The delusion of having a dream being with you♪
♪A day is like a thousand years♪
♪Because of the cold and lonely nights♪
♪Always remember before the flowers wither♪
[Ye Xiwu,]
[the one I love the most is you.]
[The reason why there's love in me]
[is because that person is you]
[instead of anyone else.]
[Susu,]
[even if we keep staying at Hengyang Sect,]
[I'll be with you.]
[Let's enjoy all the mountain views]
[and all the days we have.]
[No scenery is better]
[than being with you forever.]
Tantai Jin,
you lied to me again.
[If I break my promise,]
[may heaven and earth kill me.]
[May my soul perish with my body.]
[Tomb of Tantai Jin, Loving Husband of Ye Xiwu]
[Tomb of Ye Xiwu, Loving Wife of Tantai Jin]
[This world finally has peace now.]
[Mortals, immortals and demons
can live in peace.]
[Ji Ze,]
[now I finally understand.]
[Five Hundred Years Later]
Mom.
Come on.
Where else is fun to play in the mortal realm?
There's one place
that's quite pretty.
Mom, look!
So many little fish in the water.
[The water of the Mohe River flows on and on.]
[It seems to be changing all the time.]
[But it seems to have never changed too.]
I was thinking
when love perished,
when hatred perished,
[and when our bodies perish,]
[how can we prove that they]
[have truly existed before?]
[Will our story]
[be known to posterity?]
Mom,
what's this place called?
Well, this river is called the Mohe River.
Long ago,
on the banks of the river
are the Sheng Kingdom and the Jing Kingdom.
And long long ago,
there were a lot of little clams living in it.
Deep at the bottom of the river,
there's also a clam princess.
What happened next?
What does the clam princess look like?
Later, one day,
the clam princess saw
the invincible and handsome God of War.
God of War?
Is he as awesome as my dad?
Yeah.
Just like your dad.
Brave, resolute,
and loves everyone in the world.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪