The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 36]
[The Way is Topgallant]
What? You want
to quit practicing the Heartless Way?
It's not like that, Father.
It's just that I'm still attached to him.
I don't think I'll ever
make a breakthrough.
I'm not fated to attain godhood.
I'm sorry that I let you down, Father.
Get up.
Susu,
you sure Jiumin is the one?
Mm. Would that be fine with you,
Father?
Oh, sweet pea, my opinion doesn't matter.
You know better than anyone
if he is a decent guy.
Besides, he was able
to refine the Heart-guarding Scale.
And that's enough to prove that
he has the kindest heart and the purest soul.
He's a reliable man you can count on.
Father…
It doesn't matter if you can't ascend.
Whatever your decision may be,
I just want you
to stay safe and happy.
If you ever find yourself on the wrong path,
just turn around.
I will always be there for you,
cookie.
That means a lot, Father.
And…
don't worry about
the evil bone.
I'll think of something.
Susu.
So you do have the evil bone.
Why didn't you tell me?
Do you have any idea how many
crave its power?
Was it Jiumin's idea to keep us in the dark?
He must be seeking a chance
to retrieve the bone.
That's why he's sticking around.
No. That's not it.
He just found out a while ago.
I didn't want to tell anyone because I thought
the evil bone would cause catastrophic havoc.
How could you have been so careless?
You don't understand the scale of its power.
You may be of a pure spirit body
with the ability to keep out demonic energy,
but it's the evil bone we're talking about.
Even the Heavenly Pillar failed to contain it.
What makes you think you can?
I didn't have a choice.
I removed the evil bone using my divine essence,
only to realize it was indestructible.
So I had to seal it in me.
It was the Devil Sound Spell, again.
Baiyu,
I sent for you
because I've got a little job for you.
What exactly do you want?
Everyone knows
he no longer has the bone.
If anything,
he has no value to you anymore.
That is none of your concern.
Just bring me the devil fetus
and leave the rest to me.
But…
Don't forget
why you're here,
Baiyu.
Unless you want all of them to die,
you will do as you're told.
Understood.
Si Ying and Jing Mie are coming for Jiumin.
They haven't found
out where the bone is, or have they?
I'd better get a move on.
Time is of the essence.
Susu,
after a lengthy discussion, your dad and I
decided to combine our powers to cast an array
for you at 12 midnight the day after tomorrow.
It's called the Yin-Yang Array.
To nullify the evil bone's power.
It's for our peace of mind.
Well, Father,
I know you two have been chewing it over
for the last 24 hours.
I can't describe how thankful I am.
Not to forget Uncle Zhaoyou.
He's been rushing around
making arrangements for my wedding.
This is a peaceful time for all three realms.
To our kind of people,
there's nothing bigger than
you marrying Jiumin.
Just know that we are really happy for you.
For now, put everything else behind you.
Speaking of which,
we owe a debt of gratitude
to your other father here.
We were mistaken about him.
Since the Demon Subduing Peak indicent,
he's been feeling guilty
for wrongly accusing Jiumin.
But being naturally unexpressive,
he left it unsaid.
When he heard the good news,
he offered to suppress the evil bone for you
at the risk of his powers being dried up.
He said that would be the only way
you and Jiumin
could live a carefree life.
"Call it a token of apology," as he said.
It's about time
you showed her the tiger.
This is…
a rooster-shaped stone?
Tiger.
He made it for you,
out of lava from the Barren Abyss.
He always wanted
to give it to you in person.
At the Barren Abyss,
I thought about what to give you every day.
In most cases,
giving kids tigers made of fabrics
is a more popular option.
There was nothing there
but stones.
The lava rocks were hard.
And I was weak.
I had to strike the rock
a little at a time.
Then one day,
it finally looked like the shape I desired.
And you,
my daughter whom I haven't seen in years,
are all grown up.
I did not do enough for you.
Now I just want to do whatever I can
to make amends.
Father,
I'll take good care of the tiger.
I have good news.
Both my fathers
have found a way to negate the evil bone.
They're going to cast a formation
for that in three days
How did you birth father know
the bone was in your body?
He heard me talking to my other father
about it.
He isn't an outsider anyway.
And this may surprise you,
but he's a very gentle man.
Relax, Jiumin.
As long as the evil bone's power is dampened,
you and I will live a long,
peaceful life together.
Don't you want to have
a full wedding ceremony this time?
Right.
Once you've completed your training,
I'll come and pick you up with bride token.
We'll get married again.
What makes you think I'll say yes?
Well,
Chief Qu did.
I have his permission
to be by your side forever.
Too late to back out now.
Aren't you worried
I'll shoot nails into your body again?
So…
that's a yes?
Oh, you.
You only hear what you want to hear.
Now,
according to Mount Changze's tradition,
we're not allowed to
see each other before the wedding.
Make sure you do a lot
of planning and preparation.
Because my fathers just might
call off the wedding
if you fail to meet their standards.
Okay.
I'll wait for you.
I'll bring enough betrothal gift
and pick you up at the pass.
It's your turn.
You old geezer,
what's wrong with you?
You don't play chess or drink.
Your mind
have wandered beyond the horizon.
This is something big.
Here.
Have a cup of tea first.
Wasn't I right about what happened
last time?
[Marriage Proposal]
Don't make me look bad.
After your beloved disciple
joins Hengyang sect,
will you regret it?
Qu, thank you for saving Jiumin.
Even though he is a devil,
he faintly showed the image of god
when he mastered the Heart-guarding Scale.
[This is sufficient proof that
he has a firm mind in cultivation.]
[Given time,]
[he'll be able
to take on the responsibility]
[of protecting the people.]
[You become serious]
[when we talk about him.]
[You're right.]
[Chief Qu, I'll trouble you then.]
[See you in three days.]
[Planning a wedding is a lot of work.]
[But does Lady of Spirituality remember]
[to go to the lake to meditate every day?]
[What about Jiumin?]
[besides coming to Hengyang Sect to peep]
[at Lady of Spirituality every day,]
[does he practice hard?]
Lady Susu.
You ask her.
Lady Susu, have you noticed that
there are always
some strange people around?
[Cang Jiumin, be patient.]
[We'll be together forever]
[after tomorrow.]
Our classes are cancelled tomorrow.
Chief wants to cultivate
in seclusion for a day.
What's happening?
Why does he want to do that?
Do you think
something big is going to happen
in the sect?
Something big?
The devil fetus's power is ruined.
What can happen?
I think
it is mostly related to something joyous.
Yeah.
But Cang Jiumin isn't worthy
of Lady of Spirituality.
He is a devil
who is millions years old.
I don't know what Chief is thinking.
Keep your voice down.
Nian Baiyu is staying somewhere near here.
What do you call this?
Demon King, Devil God and evil cultivator.
Mount Changze has collected the whole set.
Knock it off.
Keeping quiet doesn't make you a mute.
Susu.
You'll lose all senses later.
But don't be afraid.
You just have to trust us.
Thank you, fathers.
Silly girl,
no need to thank me.
Uncle Zhaoyou will come
to propose a marriage
with betrothal gift for Jiumin tomorrow.
We'll have two happy events
to celebrate then.
Let's get started.
Sister,
what are you thinking?
You look happy.
Anything good happening?
We've found the entrance to Devil Palace.
We only need one thing from Hengyang Sect
and His Lordship will be resurrected soon.
It's a make-it or break-it attempt.
Si Ying.
I've been thinking a lot lately
after coming round.
Whether a god, a demon or a human,
we all exist only for a short time.
So the most important thing
is to be good to yourself
and go after what you want.
You've dedicated your everything
to the Devil God.
Have you thought about
what you want?
Sister,
I want
whatever His Lordship wants.
Sister,
don't be silly.
You've given so much for the Devil God.
But what did he do for you?
His Lordship doesn't need
to do anything for me.
I did everything willingly.
Sister, I shall take my leave.
If all goes well,
the next time we meet
will be in the Devil God's presence.
Susu.
Susu?
It's the hour of the Rat
and the formation has ended.
Why hasn't Susu woken up?
She looks bad.
Could something go wrong?
What would go wrong?
Look.
Isn't the evil bone coming out?
What's going on?
No, why is this happening?
Isn't the formation supposed
to suppress the evil bone?
Sky-Slashing Sword.
If only you can judge
a man's character as accurately
as you judge a weapon.
That's right.
It's Sky-Slashing Sword,
the third demonic weapon.
Ten thousand years ago,
I stabbed the Devil God with it
and sealed him in the Barren Abyss.
Everyone thinks that
the Sword is missing
like other demonic weapons.
Actually, it's always been with me.
I've misjudged you.
Unexpectedly,
you've been after the evil bone
from the very beginning.
Chief Qu.
In fact, I admire an upright man
like you very much.
After I met Chu Huang,
I really wanted to be
a faithful good lover.
Unfortunately, the Devil God's power
is too tempting.
In order to obtain that power,
I had no choice but to betray Chu Huang
and went over to the Devil God.
And I ended up meeting this child.
After I reunited
with Susu,
I was determined to make it up to her
and be a good father.
However, fate makes a fool out of people.
You can only blame
this child
for having a close connection
with the devil bone.
No! Don't hurt Susu!
No!
Susu.
She is my daughter.
How could I have the heart to kill her?
After I take out the evil bone,
she only needs to get through the injury
to lead a peaceful life.
As her adoptive father,
you've worked hard for so many years
to bring her up.
Now,
you can rest in peace.
Susu.
you've made me wait
for thousands of years.
Finally, it's my time
to take control of the Devil God's power.
Your spiritual power is almost exhausted
and you're stabbed
by the Sky-Slashing Sword.
Why bother to struggle?
You greedy man.
You covet the power of the Devil God.
You have no right
to talk about karma with me.
Even if I use up my power
and my divine form is shattered,
I won't let you take the evil bone away.
What a fool.
[As long as you are safe and happy,]
[no matter what you choose,]
I will be happy for you.
Even if you make the wrong choice,
don't be afraid,
I'll always be by your side
to catch you
when you look back
Father, thank you.
Susu.
I'm sorry
[I…]
[can't catch you.]
[Sister, something bad happened.]
Let's go.
[Something bad has happened.]
[I need to get His Majesty out of here.]
[Where am I?]
[Tantai Jin, so?]
[You said when the time comes,]
[you will return to the Barren Abyss.]
[I've found the entrance
to the Devil Palace]
[for you.]
[There's no better time than now.]
[Why am I here?]
[What exactly is going on?]
[Your Majesty,
I've bidden farewell to Chief.]
[Before leaving,
I want to catch up with you.]
Bai Yu, why are you leaving suddenly?
I'm worried
about my family.
Your Majesty,
even if the two chiefs
defended you fiercely
at the Demon Subduing Peak,
your situation
hasn't been improved.
Have you thought about leaving here
and go back to the Yiyue tribe with me?
Baiyu,
I'm not a saint.
Honestly speaking,
I don't like to be subjected to criticism
and have my life dictated by others.
But
as long as I can be with Susu,
I can bear with all these.
Your Majesty,
I heard that
you're going to marry
the Lady of Spirituality
and stay here forever.
But do you not care
[about Yiyue tribe anymore?]
My maternal tribe.
Speaking of which, I'm ill-fated.
Whoever related to me
will be struck by disasters.
Perhaps staying away from me
can stay away from trouble.
This is the best way
to protect my maternal tribe.
Your Majesty,
do you ever miss the days
when you could rally multitudes
with just one call as the ruler?
When you were the king,
With your governance,
things were in good order
and people lived in peace.
Don't you want to be back on that position
to protect your maternal tribe?
I don't know if I miss it.
It's been 500 years.
Many things are like dreamy illusions.
Perhaps
only this bright moon
is eternal and unchanging.
[Surprisingly,]
[your sidekick has some skills.]
[He really brought you back]
[without anyone knowing.]
[It's Nian Baiyu.]
[Why?]
[No, now isn't not the time
to think about these things.]
[Susu is waiting for me.]
[I need to find a way to run away.]
Cang Jiumin,
you're finally back here.
Do you feel
familiar?
I've never been here before.
Why would I feel familiar?
This is the gate to the Demon Realm.
The residence
of the Devil God's true form.
You were born with evil bone.
How could you not recognize this gate?
What are you hesitating about?
You are afraid.
You're afraid
that everything will be proven true.
[Since they're able to bring me here,]
[they must be well-prepared.]
[It won't work if I force my way out.]
[Or I'll comply with them first]
[and find a chance to escape.]
[Is this your home? It's so big.]
[Home?]
What is that?
It's like an animal's den.
Mo Nv and I
used to call the cave
by the Chi River home.
But the Divine Realm took us back
for cultivation
We had no home since then.
This will be your home from now on.
Si Ying.
He really is the Devil God.
He's the Devil God we've been looking for.
What nonsense are you talking about?
If he is not the Devil God,
how could he lift
the interdict placed
on the Demon Realm gate?
Forget it. You won't understand.
In short,
there is no Cang Jiumin
or Tantai Jin.
He can only be the Devil God.
[Come.]
[Come to see me now.]
[You'll have the answers
to all the riddles.]
[Who exactly are you?]
I'm asking you now
[I'm asking you now
[I'll ask you again.]
[Who exactly are you?]
[Or just let me tell you]
[who you should be]
[and]
[my birth.]
[I was born out of natural disasters,]
[Kindness Hospital]
Thank you, doctor.
Be careful when you get home.
Do you need treatment?
Come in, please.
[diseases,]
My chest hurts.
Please, sir, give me some medicine.
This isn't a charity.
So you don't have any money. Leave!
[poverty,]
What are you looking at?
Aren't you broke too?
Going to the hospital like others, huh?
Get lost!
Alright, there you go.
[starvation,]
Stop running, you thief!
I'm gonna beat you to death!
[filth,]
Are you blind or what?
What are you doing?
[rage,]
Behave yourself!
You! You!
Don't you know who I am?
[killing,]
[sadness,]
[death,]
[and war.]
Welcome back, Master!
Sins are my responsibilities.
Gods are the light of this world.
But I
am the shadow of this world.
That's why I can't leave this world.
I've been existing alone in the demon realm
for god-knows how long.
Suddenly one day,
I've figured out something.
There are sins in this world
because there's too much pain and happiness,
starvation and satiety,
and chaos and order.
All these are born relatively to each other.
It's been like this since the beginning of time.
If this is the case,
pain won't be eliminated.
Why can't I go the other way around
and let this world have no clarity anymore?
All lives
will be indulged in pain due to the muddiness.
To create a peaceful world
without happiness or sadness,
I've created the All-in-Distress Way.
When the world no longer has the difference
of clarity and muddiness,
there won't be any sins anymore.
When I achieve this goal,
the three realms will return to the chaos
from which I was born,
and I will be free.
In your dreams.
Junior Sect Aunt, you're awake.
Little Yue Ya,
what happened to me?
Cang Jiumin stole your evil bone.
That's why you're injured and in a coma.
Slowly. Are you trying to get up?
Be careful.
What do you
mean by this?
Junior Sect Aunt,
Cang Jiumin killed Sect Leader Qu,
seriously injured Lord of Evil
and took away the evil bone.
Nobody knows where he went.
[You'll soon lose your five senses.]
[But don't be afraid.]
[You just need to trust us.]
Thank you guys.
Silly kid,
there's no need to thank your dad.
Impossible.
Junior Sect Aunt.
[Memorial Tablet of Sect Leader Qu Xuan Zi]
Dad,
how can you be…
Dad!
Susu.
-Dad!
-Susu!
Tantai Jin did this.
No way.
He won't.
Dad!
[Whatever you choose,]
as long as you're safe and happy,
dad will be happy for you.
Dad!
[Junior Sect Aunt,]
[Cang Jiumin killed Sect Leader Qu,]
[seriously injured Lord of Evil]
[and took away the evil bone.]
[Nobody knows where he went.]
What are you
planning to do to Tantai Jin?
All sects will hunt him down.
If he resists,
they'll kill him on the spot.
Don't kill him.
He won't do such things.
Li Susu,
master's body is still warm,
but you're begging for mercy for the murderer?
Shouldn't he pay with his life for killing him?
No. There must be some misunderstanding.
Senior Sect Brother, I know Tantai Jin the best.
I beg you to give him a chance
to tell the truth
before he was killed.
Enough!
The facts can't be more clearer.
You just don't want to believe them.
You were like this on the Demon Subduing Peak.
To protect Tantai Jin,
you actually hide the evil bone's whereabouts.
If not so,
master won't be dead.
Hengyang Sect won't be in disgrace.
I'm ordering you as the leader of Hengyang Sect.
From today on,
you're grounded in your room.
Senior Sect Brother…
[I'm still in the Devil Palace.]
[My mark is shaped like a phoenix's feather.]
[It looks pretty.]
[Susu's phoenix feather mark awoke me.]
Master, you're awake.
Please eat something.
Baiyu, answer me.
Why do you help them?
Master,
I don't understand why you
refuse to be the Devil God.
You used to crave power so much.
Baiyu,
I am not that king in the mortal realm
Tantai Jin anymore.
Now,
I'm Cang Jiumin from an immortal sect.
Then if this is for Yiyue Tribe?
What does this have to do with the tribe?
Five hundred years ago,
soon after you entered the Nether River,
[Si Ying and Jing Mie went to Yiyue Tribe.]
[They said that Yiyue Tribe]
[had signed a covenant with the Devil God]
[to give birth to and raise the devil fetus.]
[If they refused to hand over the fetus,]
they'd have violated the covenant.
Only by finding you
can they be free from the fate of annihilation.
That's why I was forced to work for them.
[I wish that one day,]
[I can help our people regain their freedom.]
Now there's only one way to save them.
And that is you
becoming the Devil God.
Please, Master.
Please save them.
In these people there's my mom
and the Moonshadow Guards
who once served you!
I'm begging you, Master!
Please save our people!
Just be the Devil God like they wanted, Master!
Please, Master!
I know
you want to save them as soon as possible.
But if I did what they asked,
the Devil God will be revived.
What about the lives in the
four continents and three realms?
People of Yiyue do matter,
but the lives of the
four continents and three realms
are just as important.
What a righteous speech.
Cang Jiumin, you're truly something else.
Who'd have thought
the one who least wants to revive the Devil God
is actually his devil fetus.
You've promised me
you won't hurt my master.
Why are you getting worked up?
Take a look at your master.
Does he look like he's worried for his life?
You'd better not lose yours
before you can save anyone else.
Get out.
I'm gonna
have a chat with our Devil God.
Si Ying,
aren't you afraid that I'll kill you first
after I become the Devil God?
As long as Your Highness can resurrect,
my life
is worth nothing.
Take your hand away.
Cang Jiumin,
this flesh of yours
is the Devil God's shell.
I wouldn't damage it for no reason.
After ten thousand years,
I've finally seen this face again.
I'm in a good mood today.
Let me tell you a story.
Have you seen this Yellow-red umbrella?
She's not an artifact spirit,
but my elder sister.
Elder sister?
She's called Mo Nv.
[And I'm called Si Ying.]
[We were born by the Chi River.]
[We depended on each other for living.]
[We lived our life without worries.]
Slow down.
[Until one day,]
[God of War Tian Hao
from the immortal realm took us away.]
[He put my sister into the Fire Cauldron.]
Later, it's His Highness
who killed Tian Hao
[and saved me.]
[My sister's primordial spirit was damaged.]
His Highness sent her spirit
to the mortal realm.
Her body
was fused with this red umbrella
and was always by my side.
[From then on,]
[His Highness had become my benefactor forever.]
[But ten thousand years has passed.]
Even my sister's primordial spirit has returned.
His Highness hasn't resurrected yet.
I feel guilty towards His Highness.
Guilty?
Is this the reason for you to do evil for him?
That's not the whole truth.
Although we do bring draught,
and eat travelers passing by,
that's just our nature.
Everything is for survival.
Just like beasts will hunt,
we are observing the laws of nature.
Why were the two of us alone
punished by the immortal realm?
Was what the gods
did to my sister and me
the truth?
I want the orders of the world to collapse.
Only His Highness's All-in-Distress Way
can rule the world.
How stupid.
Do you know
filial piety and fraternal duty
and proper human relationships
are the foundation of the order of the world.
Your deceptive narrative
is just for covering
your hatred to this world
and confusing its original order.
Your hatred towards this world
was originated from your love for your sister.
The world didn't fail you.
If you do this,
how are you different from Tian Hao
who hurt you and your sister?
You keep looking for a shell that's not him
because you can't let go of your obsession.
What you want
is but an illusion after all.
Your reasoning
is contradictory.
After living ten thousand years,
you're still so foolish.
How pathetic.
Shut up!
I'll pull your tongue out if not for
your use for His Highness.
Are you going to kill me?
How can I kill my master?
You're the devil fetus we've been waiting
for ten thousand years.
Why don't you let me serve you?
Just accept it.
I knew you wouldn't give up
returning to your sect so easily.
How about I show you something good?
While you were sleeping just now,
your subordinates didn't slack.
Jing Mie already sent the good news
that you had returned to the demon realm
to the immortal sects.
What's wrong with him?
He doesn't look right.
I'm presenting a gift to you
on behalf of the two guards of the Devil God.
What's going on?
Yeah, what happened to him?
Trying to play tricks?
[Thank you Hengyang Sect]
[for keeping the devil fetus alive for us.]
[Now Cang Jiumin has returned to Barren Abyss.]
[The Devil Palace is reopened.]
[The Devil God]
[will soon be revived!]
The Devil God is really coming?
So Cang Jiumin did harbor evil designs!
What should we do now?
What should we do?
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪