♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 18]
I'm powerful enough to do anything,
but I still lost to her.
Ye Bingchang, you're awake, finally.
Who are you? Why are you talking to me?
After going through Bo're Life,
have you learned nothing?
You've been jealous
of Ye Xiwu since you were little,
but you couldn't do anything about it.
You could only lie to yourself
over and over again,
convincing yourself that
Ye Xiwu was the noble daughter
of a legitimate wife
while you're just
a lowly concubine's daughter.
You believe
that's why you were inferior to her
and you didn't deserve everything she had.
How pathetic!
Nonsense.
I don't need to compare with her at all.
Really?
But why did you take someone else's
love thread as your own?
Does your husband Xiao Lin
really love you?
What if you don't have
the extra love thread with you?
How did you know that?
Since having this treasure,
you've gained extraordinary charm
that can conquer many men, haven't you?
But good and bad things come in pairs.
The succubus kidnapped you
because she was attracted
by this love thread.
So you're here to kindly remind me?
If you want to defeat Ye Xiwu,
you'll need more than love threads.
When in Bo're Life,
even if you were the goddess
of the Flying Serpent clan,
didn't she take everything from you again?
Tian Huan was born so noble.
If not for loving the wrong man,
how would she end up in dismay?
What exactly are you trying to say?
Life is short.
If you only rely on your good looks,
bet everything on a man,
and fail to seize the chances,
you can only and will always be a loser.
Tian Huan's tragedy
will be your future.
I'm not Tian Huan,
and I have nothing to do with her!
Tian Huan has the power
of the flying serpent,
but all she knows is to be jealous
and try to please Ming Ye.
I'm nothing like her.
What's different about you?
In this world,
nobody is more worthy of my love than me.
Tian Huan is willing to kill for her man,
but I will only do that for myself.
Clever girl.
May you be luckier than Tian Huan.
Tian Huan.
It's the God-slaying Lightning.
Sang Jiu.
Sang Jiu, what's that?
It's a gem
that I forged with the divine essence
of the entire Flying Serpent clan.
This tiny piece
contains the powers of immortals.
It's capable
of overturning heaven and earth.
Why don't I call it
World-overturning Jade?
You want to use it to revive
your father and brother?
So are you here to stop me again?
Sang Jiu, don't use it.
You killed immortals
for their divine essence
and forged this evil object
with demonic fire.
It has harmed the heavenly harmony.
That's why the lightning punishment comes.
Be aware of the consequences.
Once you use its power,
you'll have to repay it someday.
You won't have a good ending.
A good ending?
From the moment
when I drew the Water-calming Sword,
I never thought of any good ending!
Ming Ye,
you mind too many of others' business.
Out of my way!
What?
You want me to pay them with my life?
No.
I just thought of another way.
Sang Jiu,
you don't have to be a demon anymore.
Everything
can still be saved.
What's your way?
With the so-called Bone-refining Seal?
Or did you borrow any treasure
from someone else?
The Bone-refining Seal has been sealed
by me in the Divine Platform.
You're right.
This shouldn't be a trade
or a favor
but compensation.
What are you up to?
Sang Jiu, look.
This is the God-slaying Lightning.
It is powerful enough
to shatter an immortal's soul.
It appeared
because of your breaking
the rules of heaven
and forging the World-overturning Jade.
If it strikes, you may not survive.
Is this lightning punishment for me?
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
♪That's about to fall from the edge of the sky♪
I didn't expect
that I was just one step short
before I could revive everyone.
♪To forget my everything♪
♪I wanna hang a dream there
and trade you with a drop of tear♪
♪Hearts burn like flames♪
♪Why don't we just be like this♪
♪For ten thousand years?♪
What are you doing?
Sang Jiu,
I'll take the punishment for you.
When my immortal body vanishes,
my divine essence
will replace your demon bone.
Ming Ye!
Let go of me!
I didn't agree!
I didn't agree! Let go of me!
♪I won't fly away♪
Sang Jiu, you know what?
I never found a chance
to apologize to you.
It's my first time being a husband.
I didn't know how to love you.
And for such a long time,
I didn't do anything for you.
Now I'm getting it,
but you don't want anything.
It was me who didn't protect you.
I'm sorry.
You did nothing wrong.
As your husband, I'm not good enough.
It was me
who made you a demon.
A devil.
♪For ten thousand years?♪
♪Let's freeze time♪
♪Before saying goodbye♪
I keep thinking of that bamboo forest.
[Thinking of our home]
and the bitter herbal soup.
You kept tricking me into picking leaves.
I'd also think of you.
You were running, jumping,
sleeping,
laughing
and crying.
If I could choose,
I really hope that I can stay with you
in that cottage in the bamboo forest.
I dream
of living the rest of our lives that way.
This won't work.
This won't work!
Ming Ye,
whatever you say or do,
whether you're alive or dead,
I won't forgive you!
Let go of me!
♪Always remember before the flowers wither♪
I know.
Just hate me like this
and live on.
♪Let's freeze love before it turns to dust♪
Ming Ye.
Actually, I should've died long ago.
My physical body
had been devoured
when I was in Barren Abyss.
[I don't understand.]
[Why do they have to suffer]
[for the mistakes I made?]
[Why do we have to be bullied]
[but Tian Huan can be forgiven?]
Due to the hatred within,
I didn't die.
Instead, I transformed into a demon body.
That's why
I won't survive this lightning punishment.
I won't be able
to accept your divine essence.
You can never repay me.
You owe this to me.
Sang Jiu.
Sang Jiu!
Sang Jiu…
Sang Jiu.
Now that you want to devilize,
then I
will devilize together with you.
[Who am I?]
[Am I Li Susu,]
[Ye Xiwu?]
[or Sang Jiu?]
[What's wrong with its eyes?]
[This flood dragon keeps sleeping]
[to experience dreams in Bo're Life.]
[Whether he'll be devil or god,
this is the moment of truth.]
[No.]
[If my soul disintegrates like this,]
[Ming Ye will surely devilize
due to desperation.]
[Ming Ye, you must make up your mind.]
[Since you can't pull Sang Jiu]
[out of her devilizing fate,]
[live on for her.]
[The Ming Ye, whom Sang Jiu deeply loved,]
[isn't someone who bows to fate.]
[He's always been
that God of War in armor.]
[The demon soldiers haven't left,]
[which means I can still see you today.]
[If I cultivate hard]
[and enter Shangqing Realm,]
[I wonder if I'll get to speak with you.]
[Could I tell you there is]
[a little clam demon
who always loved you?]
[She loved the God of War, who protected]
[the Mohe River and the three worlds.]
[She loved the upright
and unyielding you.]
♪Every pair of distant stars♪
♪Were lonely souls in the beginning♪
♪Floating in the stream of time
and entangled in the threads of love♪
♪Fate is unfathomably deep♪
♪And indifferent to meeting and parting♪
♪Blame heaven for breaking us apart♪
♪Love means becoming the one you love♪
Sang Jiu.
♪I don't care about right or wrong♪
♪I just trap my heart in prison♪
♪The dust of the moon is silent♪
I… I didn't devilize.
I know.
You fought with the Devil God
and protected
the Four Continents and Three Realms.
All along,
you're that God of War
who's always protecting others.
But I didn't protect you well.
It's fine.
I'll forgive you this time.
Just this once.
[The thought of devilizing]
[shouldn't be my choice.]
[I'll always be
the God of War loved by Sang Jiu.]
♪For you, I've overturned my body and soul♪
♪Snow falls without traces
And I revive in ruins♪
♪My body is smashed to pieces
Like flowers fall in an instant♪
♪My dreams want more than me to stay♪
[The Soul-slaying Teardrop.]
♪They are all derived from love♪
♪The dust of the moon is silent
Being awake is too cruel♪
♪Have you ever missed my deep kiss♪
Ye Xiwu.
[What is this feeling?]
We're finally out.
Xiao Lin.
Ye Xiwu.
Ye Xiwu!
[Your Majesty,]
[this is the illusion
the flood dragon created.]
It carries its memories.
This flood dragon is so wicked.
I've summoned my army here for nothing.
Your Majesty,
the water-repelling barrier's
about to disappear.
We must go ashore quickly.
[Ming Ye,]
[why did you choose me
to enter your Bo're Life?]
We've finally got out of this damn river
and put our feet on the ground.
Xiwu.
Kill her!
Xiwu, I'm your elder sister.
Big Sister, sorry.
I was just…
It's okay.
It's all gone.
Miss Bingchang, Miss Xiwu,
are you alright?
Where's that sleeping flood dragon?
It's long dead at the bottom of the river.
After ten thousand years,
the only thing left is its bones.
But it left a dream
to attract people to come.
It managed to make you
experience your dreams.
Why would he do that?
[For a prophecy.]
[To destroy the evil bones,]
[you'll need three keys.]
A dream.
[You can only awaken it]
[after entering its dream.]
A teardrop.
A thread.
Ming Ye didn't devilize in the end.
But he was troubled by love.
So he left this illusion after he died.
It's probably
for inspiring the destined ones.
What did you see in there?
How did that inspire you?
[Sang Jiu,]
[I hope that one day]
[somewhere in this world,]
[you and Ming Ye
can meet each other again.]
Luckily, Tantai Jin
didn't get the flood dragon.
Let's go back to the camp first.
I still have some unfinished business.
I'm not going back with you.
Are you kidding, Miss Xiwu?
What are you going to do again?
I'm going to Jing Kingdom.
I'll tell you when I make it.
Miss Xiwu,
do you have a death wish?
You've just ruined Tantai Jin's plan.
Now if you go back and get caught by him,
he'll torture you in every way!
Let her go.
Although I don't know
what you're gonna do,
I believe you'll definitely make it.
Everyone,
we shall meet again someday
in this big world.
Take care.
By the way, Scholar Pang.
This thing is called
the Mirror of the Past.
When you return
to the immortal sect one day,
remember to take it back to Xiaoyao Sect.
[Senior Ji Ze deliberately
adjusted the time]
[for a few months]
[so that I could get out at the same time]
[as Tantai Jin catching the flood dragon.]
[A dream and a teardrop.]
[Now I've experienced them
and acquired them.]
[Next,]
[I'll need Devil God to grow love threads]
[and fall in love with me.]
[Then there's only one thing
I need to do.]
Your Majesty,
you seem a little absent-minded
since you got out of Bo're Life.
Every day you'll wait here
for quite some time.
What exactly happened there?
[Why do I keep reminiscing
about Bo're Life?]
[Sang Jiu.]
♪Gazing up♪
[No.]
[Ye Xiwu.]
♪3,000 flowers♪
[They look so alike.]
[I can't tell them apart for now.]
♪Holding a butterfly♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing♪
♪Our memories in muddy water♪
This cloak looks so ugly.
I don't want it.
It's yours.
Wake up, Tantai Jin.
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
You're finally awake.
I took care of you for a whole night.
I'm exhausted.
Remember to drink your medicine.
I'm going to bed now.
Tantai Jin,
you must live on.
[From now on,]
come and have dinners here.
Chuntao will cook for you.
You'll eat whatever we give you.
Don't eat anything dirty
or strange anymore.
[Smells good.]
[It's really just a bowl of rice.]
I'm gonna escort you
back to the Sheng Kingdom.
And then put you in prison
to keep you away from the outside world.
I'll be watching you
every second of every day.
As long as I'm alive,
don't ever think
of devouring demonic elixirs.
No more killing.
♪Nobody cares how much you miss each other♪
♪If not for telling a lie♪
♪And mentioning forever so rashly♪
♪Why would there be so many unfinished stories♪
♪Carved on stone tablets for people to lament?♪
[The dream has ended.]
[It's already been so many days.]
[Ye Xiwu and Xiao Lin must've left.]
Your Majesty,
General Ye brought reinforcement here.
Let's go back to Jia Pass camp.
Tantai Jin!
Haven't you already left?
Why do you come back?
Good or bad, I have to follow my husband.
What, you don't want me anymore?
Sweet talking.
[Why is he cold to me again?]
Tie her up.
Wh… What are you doing?
I've made up my mind to follow you.
I swam here!
I also walked for days.
My feet were worn.
You swam here?
Give me that.
Chief Pian.
Lead her back.
See if she's possessed by something evil.
Remember to check carefully.
Okay.
Wait…
My little darling,
what the heck are you doing?
Just stay put in here.
Don't play any tricks.
Otherwise, that person
will really peel off my fur.
I'm most willing to follow you.
Why would I run away?
They really treat me like a prisoner.
The first step is always the hardest.
It's true that if you let go of your ego,
you'll be able to say anything.
[What exactly should I do]
[to let Little Devil God love me]
[and grow love threads?]
Just now, when I supported him
by the river,
that teardrop seemed to be warming up.
Guess I'll need to take the initiative.
Miss Xiwu, hold on.
Miss Xiwu.
Who's there?
It's me!
Let her in.
Can I sleep here tonight?
No.
Did Sang Jiu leave you
some kind of trauma that night?
Shut up.
In this case,
didn't you taste anything
after being through Bo're Life?
Taste?
Ye Xiwu,
you're so shameless.
What the hell were you thinking?
It's not that.
Why do you always have weird thoughts?
-I…
-I meant feelings and inspiration.
Feelings and inspirations.
Feelings and inspirations?
Of course I have some.
First,
Ming Ye is such a fool.
He actually gave up
the power of a god for a woman.
Second,
the ancient Devil God is truly mighty.
One day, I'll replace him.
[Oh no!
Why are you admiring the Devil God?]
You know what? Tantai Jin.
For such a sad
and sentimental love story,
don't you have any other thoughts?
Like, I'd think that if I love someone,
I'll never be as humble as Sang Jiu.
I gotta say it out loud.
Say it out loud?
That was why I came for you.
♪Spending a lifetime
just to see one person♪
♪From the first glance
to being immersed in passion♪
Nian Baiyu.
At your service.
Drag her out of here.
♪Opening the door of our hearts♪
Tantai Jin, are you being shy?
Drag her out.
Yes.
-Are… Are you being shy?
-Let's go, Miss Xiwu.
Tantai Jin.
-You're blushing.
-I…
Miss Xiwu.
You're definitely being shy!
That's true. Tantai Jin. You're being shy.
Lock her in the camp.
Don't let her bother me again.
If she keeps wandering,
you punish her with a beating.
[Did Soul-slaying Teardrop warm up again?]
I can even be shy?
[It's strange.
Whenever I think of Ye Xiwu these days,]
[I'll have an itchy feeling in my chest.]
[Like something's about to come out.]
Your Highness, are you tired?
No, my mind just wandered.
Are you still thinking about the things
in Bo're Life?
Your Highness,
I didn't choose to get into that dream.
I never wanted
to do what Tian Huan committed.
That battle I fought with you
at the bottom of the Mohe River
still gives me the chills
when I recall it.
If you're going to blame me for it…
Then I… I'll…
Why would I? You're not Tian Huan.
I'm not Sang You, either.
We both know that it's just a dream.
Your Highness,
I'm a vulnerable woman.
I can only live with your protection.
Bingchang,
now our kingdom is at stake.
Although I'm the crown prince,
I'm also your husband.
No matter how things will end,
I will protect you well.
I won't leave you behind.
Why are you suddenly
saying things like this?
A man's misfortune
is often due to himself.
But a woman's is often due to her husband.
Just like Sang Jiu,
who married the wrong man
and eventually degenerated out of hatred.
Although I'd been her brother
only in the dream,
my heart still aches
when I think of her now.
Your Highness is so kind-hearted.
But my sister has gone to Jing Kingdom.
She'll be the wife of a king,
with wealth and rank as much as there is.
She won't need love from a fake brother.
Yeah.
It's just a dream, after all.
Now the one I'll love and protect is you.
Why did you take someone else's
love thread as your own?
Does your husband Xiao Lin
really love you?
What if you didn't have
that extra love thread on you?
[Yeah, without the love tread,]
[how could he love me so truly like this?]
[Without the love thread,]
[I'll still be that]
[bullied and ignored
concubine's daughter.]
[With no one to care about or pity me.]
[Putting on a smile for others every day.]
[But everything of mine had already been
snatched by them.]
[This dream really lets me see myself]
[and my so-called family.]
[Ye Bingchang,]
[you must think more for yourself.]
[Put this love thread into good use.]
Your Majesty,
I've sent Miss Xiwu back to the camp.
Have some tea.
You…
Drag her out!
-Are… Are you being shy?
-Let's go, Miss Xiwu.
You're definitely being shy.
That's true. Tantai Jin. You're being shy.
[Why am I happy for no reason]
[when I see her?]
[Jia Pass]
Sister Pian Ran,
I can do anything dangerous in the world,
but not this one.
You have no choice.
Sending you here
to clean the poultry house
and look after these military provisions
is the order from His Majesty.
Let's go.
How can Tantai Jin be so cruel?
Why are these geese so big?
I can't do this. My head hurts.
I'm sweating, and I can't catch my breath.
You think I don't know your little plan?
You came back this time
to seduce Tantai Jin, didn't you?
Is that so obvious?
No need to be embarrassed.
However,
His Majesty will be back
in the capital soon.
If you don't want to be
raising geese in the camp by then,
just work hard now.
Seriously?
Don't go yet.
[People Support Kind Rulers]
Where's His Majesty?
He's patrolling the camp.
Why are you bringing luggage?
Where are you headed?
By His Majesty's order, I'm going back
to the capital for family affairs.
Fine.
You don't feel comfortable
staying here, anyway.
It's better that you go back.
We'll also be back in a few days.
I'll leave first.
I'll be waiting for you…
I'll be waiting for you guys to come back.
[I'm here to inform you]
[that your wife's raising geese now.]
[Men are the cruelest creature.]
[Baiyu,]
[go take a look.]
No!
Tantai Jin, you're so bad!
[Why is Little Devil God's smile different?]
[Did I see it wrong?]
Ye Xiwu.
She has a fever. Call the medic.
I'll give her medicine right away.
Get up. Stop faking it.
Want me to find some geese to wake you up?
What happened to me?
You were infected with evil energy
when you were swimming.
Plus, you were horror-struck.
It's all your fault.
So many damn fowls.
They're everywhere.
Get up and eat something.
What do you have?
Boiled goose eggs.
Steamed goose egg custard.
Salted goose meat.
[Seriously?]
[You killed them all for one offense?]
[How horrible.]
Come on, dig in.
But I'm so weak.
I can't raise the chopsticks
or peel an egg.
Could you feed me?
Ye Xiwu,
I'm afraid you not only caught a cold
but also had something illness
in your head.
Medic!
Stop!
Why are you so heartless?
Will I never be able to see you
if I didn't faint?
I'll count to three.
Alright, I'll eat.
Does it taste good?
Not bad.
Tantai Jin,
did you think I was funny
when I was chased by geese just now?
I saw that you're quite happy.
Did you have a tickle in your heart?
And you couldn't help smiling?
I did.
That's how happiness felt like.
What happiness? It's clearly evilness.
You enjoy watching me suffer.
[Little Devil God learned to be happy.]
[Has his love threads started to awaken]
[after being through Bo're Life?]
[Then as long as
I put more effort into it,]
[wouldn't success be in the bag?]
Enjoy your meal.
Where are you going?
Since you're already fine,
take a good rest then. I'm leaving.
You'll go back to the capital
in a few days.
Could you take me along?
You want to go back
to the Jing Kingdom with me?
If not for this,
why would I try so hard
to swim across the river?
Yeah.
I'm also wondering why.
Don't say anything
like "Following your husband everywhere."
On the ship back to the Jing Kingdom,
you made it rather clear.
You didn't want
to have anything to do with me.
Haven't you
left with Xiao Lin yesterday?
Why didn't you
just let him bring you back
to the Sheng Kingdom?
I just wanna go with you.
Ye Xiwu,
you've been weird
since you left Bo're life.
I'm telling you,
I'm not Ming Ye.
I'm not as righteous as he is.
I don't want to save the three worlds
or protect all the people out there.
I know you're not Ming Ye.
And I'm not Sang Jiu, either.
But they're a couple.
We're also a couple.
Sang Jiu and Ming Ye couldn't disentangle
themselves from the painful relationship.
We still have chances.
What's more, on my way here,
I met a lot of civilians.
[They don't care who the king is.]
[They'll go wherever]
they can sustain their lives.
You're a wise ruler.
Not only do I like you
and want to follow you,
everybody else thinks the same.
Ye Xiwu,
you're full of lies.
How can I trust you?
I'm here and at your disposal anyway.
Believe it or not.
At my disposal?
A royal maid?
Yeah.
Didn't you say you're at his disposal?
The royal maid's clothes
look good, though.
Not bad.
A cold monarch versus a mean handmaid.
This feels so right.
Your Highness,
Fu Yu tried so hard
to save you from the brink of death.
Please take good care of your body.
Yeah.
Thanks to you.
I can still live with no dignity
in this dark cave.
Any news about Tantai Jin?
I heard Tantai Jin had conquered Jia Pass.
He'll be back in the capital soon.
Those spineless ministers in court
have all paid allegiance to him.
How is he qualified to be the King of Jing?
Your Highness,
whatever they do,
I'll always be by your side.
Did you find the people
I told you to look for?
Good.
Let them all in.
All of the best sorcerers
of Jing Kingdom are here.
Greetings, Your Highness.
You're all cultivators
who have seen the world.
I'll cut to the chase.
Do you know
how Tantai Jin obtained the ability
to use demonic hexes?
I heard he's been hunting demon creatures
to devour demonic elixirs.
-That's right.
-Devouring demonic elixirs.
It's a forbidden way of cultivation.
It's extremely risky.
How could you put yourself in danger?
Enough!
If Tantai Jin can do this,
why can't I?
I must let him pay for what he did to me.
I can't wait one minute longer.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪