♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 11]
Just a few days apart,
you have become a king.
That's impressive.
The last time I saw you,
you were still as lively as a tiger.
Just a few days later,
you looked worn out.
If I kill you now,
or take you back alive,
my family will have
another military merit.
Then go ahead and try.
See if you'll get a promotion
or if your king will dread you
for being a threat to his throne.
That's irrelevant for now.
If I kill you today,
I would be killing
a malicious man for the world!
Ye Qingyu,
I've been a hostage in the Sheng for years.
We both know how paranoid
Emperor Sheng is.
The Ye family
is on the brink of destruction.
Be it punishment or reward,
I'll thank my king.
Our Ye family is and will be Sheng people.
I won't be incited
by a few words from you.
Fair enough.
Your people owe Sheng Emperor,
thus must paying him back.
That's what you think.
But what about people
with no power to resist,
like me,
when I was married into your family?
Emperor Sheng doesn't care about them.
If your family is satisfied
to take what's given
and indulges this incapable emperor
as he wishes,
people in the Sheng
will only suffer more.
General Ye,
I've checked war records
in Jia Pass over these years.
You always charge into battle
first in front of the troop,
fighting side by side with your men.
You make Jia Pass a banner
that unites the men
and a shield
that guards the Sheng.
What's the point of saying so?
In a game of power,
I'm only a pawn.
Don't belittle yourself.
The game of power
favors brutal force.
But you're more than just a force,
whether in terms of capability
or temperament.
Your benevolence
could disguise the violence of the emperor
that wreaks havoc on people,
while in good use,
it brings peace to the land.
Cling to loyalty,
or serve the people,
it's up to you.
I hope there be no more war
and the whole land be reunited.
[Jia Pass]
General,
the court gives the same order,
that should Jia Pass falls,
then Ye family
will…be wiped out.
[The jade is a gift from Emperor Gaozu]
and a symbol of home supervisor
for generations.
Today, I give it to you now.
[Home Supervisor]
Son.
Do not yield. Die for honor if need be.
If not for your premature wisdom
that stands out in the crowd,
I meant to have you carefree
as your big brother,
wining and dining at home
and being an ordinary man.
A worthy life still,
even if you were not a hero.
Father,
brother has the fortune
to live an easy life.
Now that I'm the home supervisor.
Then all responsibility
shall rest upon my shoulders,
whether it's about the Sheng
or the whole land.
I'll do what I must do.
My personal concern should be the last.
Always trying to be a hero.
A few bumps are what you need.
The army of the Jing
has reached the gate, General.
[Ye Qingyu],
[does the life of tens of thousands men]
mean nothing to you
compared to your reputation.
That's enough!
Cling to loyalty,
or serve the people,
it's up to you.
Should Jia Pass falls,
then Ye family will be wiped out.
If your family is satisfied
to take what's given
and indulges this incapable king
as he wishes,
people in this country,
will only suffer more.
As a warden of Jia Pass,
living off an official salary,
I'm expected
to guard the Sheng at my best.
Yet from the bottom of my heart,
I hope there be no more war
and the whole land be reunited.
What I want to do
is rule the whole land
and end the war.
Deputy General Liu.
Sir.
Open the gate.
Yes, sir.
We yield.
General.
Sorry, father,
I fail you
only to save the people.
[Jia Pass]
You spend years posting in this place.
Never expect your residence
to be so humble.
Emperor Sheng is cruel and paranoid.
When getting the word,
he will probably root out your family.
I've sent people to the capital of Sheng
to bring your family back here.
They'll arrive at Jing in days.
Thank you, your Majesty.
I understand
you had a rough patch in my family.
Yet you do not fault them
but repay with goodwill.
That's mighty generous of you.
Ye Qingyu.
I save your family,
for I don't want to see your talent wasted
nor your life at risk.
Do you understand?
From now on,
I will shield your back
and give my life for yours if need be.
General Ye,
having your sword
is my great honor.
Your Majesty,
is my big sister faring well?
How should I know?
She…
She left months ago.
She's a bit willful.
If she offends you,
I beg you to pardon her negligence.
I take all responsibility.
I'm a little tired.
You shall rest too.
I…
General Ye, this way.
Ye Xiwu,
where are you?
Mr. Yue, Mrs. Yue,
I'll leave her to your care.
Rest assured,
we bear no children,
and she will be our daughter.
Fuya had a miserable childhood.
For safety,
she needs a new name.
The girl is now yours.
She needs a name to start anew.
We are farmers.
You seem more intelligent.
Maybe you can pick a name.
Yeah, that would be better.
Then, how about Yue Ya?
A reminder of the crescent.
Yue Ya.
-Yue Ya.
-Beautiful.
A good name.
When she smiles,
her eyes squint like a crescent.
Here, fuya.
There.
Fuya.
Do you like this place?
Yes.
You're Yue Ya now.
The name, Yue Fuya,
must be kept unknown.
Do you know what I mean?
If you want to learn magic arts,
take this letter to Mount Changze
and ask for Hengyang Sect.
It's Hengyang Sect, remember.
Hengyang Sect, I know.
Hope we'll see each other again.
Fare well.
Sister.
Goodbye.
Jia Pass.
How dare you.
Ye family
runs away overnight,
even before the word arrives.
You think that I'll spare your life?
Guards.
Send a cavalry.
They shall follow me
even into the grave.
Calm down, father.
Jia Pass has fallen.
The urgency now
is to dispatch troops
and reclaim the lost land.
Don't defend them.
Reclaim the lost land?
Ye Xiao has left northward,
and Ye Qingyu has surrendered.
There are no men for the job.
You made an excuse
when I dispatched the troop.
Are you privy to his scheme?
Please calm down, father.
In just a few months,
Tantai Jin employed talent and
reduced punishment and taxes
to regain peace and prosperity.
It's improper to war with him.
We shall…
Stop your nonsense.
You refuse to war
so you can replace me.
Is that your plan?
No, father.
I serve you with heart and soul.
I will lead an army and reclaim Jia Pass.
As you wish.
I have one more wish, father.
Name it.
Bingchang's from Ye family.
But she's my wife now.
I beg you to spare her life.
Very well.
Consider your sincerity,
I'll spare her.
Thank you, father.
I'll not fail you.
Why don't you leave for the Jing
with Ye Xiao and Ye Qingyu?
Are you staying to spy on us?
Yes, you're a spy!
The loyalty of Ye family is a joke.
Shame on you.
Surrender without resistance,
I used to accept her food.
How awful.
Shame on you.
Ye, the traitor.
You don't deserve to marry the prince.
Get out of our country.
Get out of here.
Get out, daughter of Ye, the traitor.
Bah!
Out, out.
I should have come earlier.
What suffering you endured.
I'll allow no more.
But now,
I'm not sure if I should leave you here.
What do you mean?
Leave me here?
I have no family to rely upon.
Your Highness.
Hear me out.
Father has promised me
that he will spare you.
Now that the Sheng has no general.
I've asked for myself.
You're going to fight?
Bingchang.
The trip is treacherous and tough.
You're too gentle.
Your Highness.
People are angry.
Even if His Majesty spares me,
they won't do the same
to a member of Ye family.
But that's my least concern.
What troubles me is that
there's no one to tend to you.
If I must die,
I want to die for you.
Your Highness, please take me with you.
I don't want to stay here alone.
Fine.
The war is unpredictable,
but I'll protect you.
I recall the last time
I drank tea
with General Ye in the capital.
How does it come to be like this?
You can never tell.
In a war between two countries,
the people suffer the most.
If I had a choice…
Junior Martial Uncle,
we have lived in two different worlds.
A matter of this kind
should not trouble you.
You'd better return to Mount Buzhao.
The war is not my concern.
It's you who I'm worried about.
You risk your life on the battlefield.
I'll do the same.
Or if our brothers and sisters ask,
how am I supposed to answer?
Plus,
earthly experience is cultivation, too
I heard people japed
sticking the noses around
is the principle of Xiaoyao Sect.
I used to doubt that.
Never expect that's true.
Xiao Lin comes in person.
Seems your surrender
irritates Emperor Sheng.
But I'm expecting
to meet with Xiao Lin again.
[Jia Pass]
In the old days in the Sheng,
he was the noble prince,
while I was a hostage prince
under his care.
One may say
I owe him.
Prince Lin is benevolent,
and he's helpful when people need him.
Helpful when people need him.
That's who he is.
But I'm afraid
I'll be the man who returns evil for good.
The demon
only dines and sleeps for all days.
Capturing the Sheng with them
might take a while.
Pian Ran,
find me
some powerful demons.
All great demons within our range
are now answering your call.
There's no more to find.
Jia Pass sits near the Mohe River.
The river is said to be ominous.
There might be some demons.
Check it out for me.
At the bottom of the Mohe River,
sleeps a demon ten-thousand-year old.
Gather all sorcerers.
Head for the Mohe River.
This is what I think.
If Junior General Ye didn't surrender
and the court had no one to assign,
it won't be Prince Xuancheng
to lead the army.
I also heard that…
Qingyu is known for loyalty.
How so?
What happened?
Emperor Jing was a hostage prince.
Maybe His Majesty thinks
a hostage prince is unworthy of a throne,
thus calling a war.
Senior General Ye is badly injured
while Junior General Ye surrenders.
Our country has passed its prime.
If not for the greed of His Majesty,
we never need to endure this suffering.
Not of our concern.
The business of emperors
has nothing to do with us.
The Jing might just be
a good place to live.
I heard they garrison along the Mohe River
and treated prisoners and migrants well.
Buddies,
may I ask,
this army of the Jing,
where do they post exactly?
[Bottom of the Mohe River]
We marched day and night.
Now, by the Mohe River,
we can finally take a rest.
What troubles you?
Something wrong?
The scout just reported
There is a contingent from the Jing
reaching the north bank of the Mohe River.
We just settled a camp
and start a war right now?
That's the curious part.
The army of the Jing arrived
only to stay put.
But we've recaptured the land for days.
Men and horses are tired.
Not a good time for war.
Wait,
it's a trap.
A trap?
How so?
Haven't figured out.
But it seems to be akin
to what happened in Mount Buzhao.
You've traveled a long journey.
It's time to get prepared.
Today, you must not fail.
Yes, sir.
I need to patrol.
Please show them the way, General Ye.
Let's go.
This is a treacherous deed.
When the formation begins,
please take care of that girl
if you may.
No problem.
Qingyu.
Long time no see.
Big sister.
I've betrayed the Sheng.
I'm ashamed to see you.
I've heard about it along the way.
I believe
you have your own reasons.
But where have you been all these days?
It's a long story.
I saw a few sorcerers in the camp.
What're their businesses?
What is Tantai Jin
up to this time?
You got him there.
His Majesty asked Pian Ran
to awaken a demon
sleeping at the bottom of the Mohe River
for his command.
His men are now preparing for the ritual.
It means
Pian Ran serves him as well.
If Tantai Jin succeeds,
a calamity will ensue.
I must turn things around.
Big sister.
When will the ritual begin?
At the next sunrise.
Your Highness!
Your Highness.
Yes? Any news?
At the bottom of the Mohe River
lies a sleeping ancient demon.
An army led by Tantai Jin
is already on its way to the Mohe River.
Apparently, they will be making a ritual
to awaken the demon.
An ancient demon, huh?
Well, I won't have Tantai Jin taming it.
Junior Martial Uncle,
we can't sit back and do nothing.
We have to find a way
to break his formation.
With everything that's going on,
sending in troops would be a bad idea.
We wouldn't want to wake a sleeping dog.
You and I will sneak in there.
It has got to be fast.
Let's go.
Your Highness, wait.
M-my cup.
Where could His Highness possibly be going
at this hour?
In haste and alone?
Your Majesty,
we've hired some rogue cultivators
who know all about formations
from the southern border.
This is going to work.
Your Majesty,
I've cast a formation.
The river will split at sunrise.
Walk down the path,
and you should see the demon.
Very well.
It's time.
Start.
This is odd.
I don't sense any demonic energy
coming from this serpent.
It is, however, holding a grudge.
In time,
it will be devoured by a grudge
and turned into a demonic serpent.
Well, that's even better.
What is that?
A clam's shell.
Start the ritual.
Burn the sky and into ashes.
Subdue!
Pian Ran.
Tantai Jin!
The acolytes sent to search for Miss Xiwu
just reported back.
Miss Xiwu is still nowhere to be found.
Keep searching.
I want her back, alive or dead.
Surprise, isn't it?
Bet you didn't see this coming.
You left without saying goodbye.
Now you show your face again
only to work against me.
Oh, well…
So you will remember me your whole life,
won't you?
I see.
Get her.
Miss Xiwu, are you all right?
That was pretty bold of you,
Miss Xiwu.
Scholar Pang.
Your Majesty,
I'll take care of them.
Hang on.
Xiao Lin.
It's been a long time.
Stop all this, Tantai Jin.
Ordering the Firewing Army
to act recklessly
is outrageous and unforgivable.
So what?
And who is to judge, anyway?
I don't see anything wrong
with giving full play to the Army.
Xiao Lin,
I summoned a flock of blood ravens
as a wedding gift
to celebrate your big day.
I hope that you like it.
Little Devil God…
You don't like it?
Why did you do that?
It just so happened that
the people I wanted to get even with
were all in the same place.
Sorry that I ruined your special day.
And I owe it to you.
Xiao Lin,
you have shown me kindness in the past.
For that, I don't want
to make this hard for you.
Leave now…
and I'll let you live.
What? Are you scared?
You know,
I've been learning people skills from you
since I was a kid.
Clearly, you didn't do a good job of that.
Mm.
In fact, you and I are worlds apart.
But we have one thing in common, though.
Do you know what it is?
Tantai Jin,
what are you trying to say?
You…
are an upright and noble man,
but your brothers aren't fond of you.
They even want to have you replaced.
And me… I'm an aloof and lower-class man.
Wanted dead by my own brothers too.
What a waste of a perfect combination, huh?
You see,
without these unwanted people,
maybe
you and I
could be brothers.
It's such a shame
we are fated…
to be enemies.
I couldn't agree more.
This is why I have to stop you today.
Go ahead.
Kill them all.
The formation has been fixed.
Keep going.
That was him stalling for time.
We've been had.
Oh no!
They're going to wake the serpent!
This serpent has been dormant
for ten thousand years.
Stuck in a limbo
called Bo're Life.
It means
reliving the past
in dreams.
Feeling all the feelings you've felt.
And the loop repeats again and again,
leaving you feeling trapped.
So the serpent has had lucid dreams
for ten thousand years?
What happened to its eyes?
There's a fine line between
becoming a demon and a god.
Maybe that's why it's been asleep
for so long.
Waking the sleeping serpent
has triggered a trial meant for it.
We'll find out soon what becomes of it.
Something's off about Tantai Jin.
Is the serpent messing with his head
and trying to lure him
into choosing an evil path?
Guess this is the beginning
of the calamity
setting in 500 years.
How to stop it
from becoming a demonic serpent?
There's only one way.
Enter the serpent's dream and wake it up.
Let me try.
Ye Xiwu!
Miss Xiwu!
Can't she wait a bit?
I haven't finished.
Why does Tantai Jin get in, too?
Once in the Bo're Life,
the invaders will lose their memories.
They may turn into small animals.
Or even an everyday tool.
They are in grave danger.
I'll stop Tantai Jin.
His Majesty just entered.
Is His Majesty going to be okay?
Wise up.
Every man has his own destiny.
I don't think
we should risk our lives for His Majesty.
You have a point,
miss.
Let's be peaceful about this.
Anyway,
no more bursting into the Bo're Life.
Way too many people,
not enough capacity.
His Majesty has entered the Bo're Life.
It may injure His Majesty
if we get into a fight.
We'll sit this one out.
It's three-on-one.
Take down Tantai Jin, guys.
Never born, never died.
In a state of mind without worries.
Now I let all of you
go through the cycle
of birth,
death,
love,
and hate.
Come into my dream.
And be enlightened.
This is
what the Bo're Life is all about.
Sang Jiu, Princess of the Unionid Tribe
of the Mohe River
Ming Ye, the God of War
of the Shangqing Realm
Long live the God of War!
If I cultivate hard enough,
I will attain godhood one day.
And then, will I be able
to fight the Devil's Army
and protect our lands
alongside the God of War?
Jiu.
Where have you been?
You were nowhere to be found.
Father was worried sick.
Jiwu,
I was away for, like, minutes.
I need you to stay home for a few days.
Don't go out.
A war has broken out
between the Gods and the Devils.
When it's all over,
I'll take you out for a breather, alright?
The Mohe River is a small place.
I'm seriously bored to death.
Jiwu.
Alright, that's enough.
You have Father and me
keeping you entertained, no?
It's been days of bloodshed.
And the Devils
haven't crossed the Mohe River?
That's right, Father.
I heard Ming Ye, the God of War
is on the front line
with his men defending the river.
It's been eight days,
and they haven't stepped back.
Oh, he's called Ming Ye.
I've heard of this young man.
He was a serpent inhabiting the East Sea.
After years and years of hard cultivation,
he was promoted to the God of War.
And he has dedicated himself
to fight the Devil's Army.
As part of the Water Tribe,
we clams have also felt the honor
and been proud.
But Father,
he was a serpent,
whereas we are clams.
What's to be proud of?
Aren't you old enough to know better?
Have you no shame?
You have the nerve to say it.
Ming Ye has divine essence.
And you do, too.
He is the God of War.
But you?
You follow Jiwu and me everywhere
and do nothing all day.
You may not be aware,
but it is chaos out there.
A perfect time to cultivate in seclusion.
So
how long have you meditated today?
Fine.
I'm going to meditate right now.
What's gotten into her lately?
She is secretive,
and so distracted all the time.
Where did she go exactly?
Well, there's a war going on.
She snuck out to rubber-neck
when we weren't looking.
She did?
Hmm. If you ask me,
she went to see someone in the battle.
Oh, my baby girl is grown up.
If she does ascend to godhood,
I just might swallow my pride
and try to set her up with that man.
We clams haven't been bothering others
for generations.
Thousands of years worth of good deeds
in exchange for
a descendant with divine essence.
Regrettably, she's lazy and unmotivated.
Only God knows
when she'll gain immortality.
Father,
Jiu is still young.
It does no harm for her to have fun.
There are always two sides to everything.
Now that the Devil God has manifested.
With the future of
Four Continents and Three Realms unclear,
the Mohe River
is the safest place she could possibly be.
That's a fair point.
Nothing matters more than her safety.
Deliver a message to the people
of the Water Tribe in the Mohe River.
They must hole up for the next few days.
Do not get involved
in the clash out there.
As you wish.
It's been less than three months
since the Devil God's arrival
and more than half the Four Continents
and Three Realms have been occupied.
This is a critical moment for us.
One mistake
and it's all over.
Before Tian Hao, the former God of War,
was taken out,
he made me promise
to defend the Eastern Continent.
It's a promise I intend to keep.
The Mohe River will not be lost.
Ming Ye,
my father left both the Eastern Continent
and me to you.
What am I going to do
if something happens to you?
Tian Huan,
thanks for healing me.
I'm going to go for a walk.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪