♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 12]
[Brothers in arms,]
[your heroic souls
will return to the stars.]
Ming Ye,
there you are.
You haven't recovered from your injury.
Beware of the wind, and don't get chilly.
Thanks.
Ming Ye,
no need to be courteous to me.
You're the guardian of Three Realms.
All I can do
is be by your side.
It's getting late.
The demons could strike at any moment.
Let me walk you back to your palace.
No, thanks.
The celestial troops
suffered heavy casualties in the battle.
I need a moment to myself.
[Ming Ye.]
[So your name is Ming Ye.]
[You are the God of War.]
[No wonder you're so good in battle.]
[I wonder how the battle is going on.]
[Will the God of War come today?]
We're raided by the demons.
Go inform the God of War, Ming Ye!
Look, the God of War is here!
Little flood dragon,
you're quite good.
Before you're killed
by the Sky-Slashing Sword,
tell me your name.
Ming Ye.
[I found him. He's here.]
What happened to you?
Wake up.
Ming Ye.
Ming Ye, wake up.
Wake up.
What's up with him?
The Devil God suddenly showed up
and ambushed Ming Ye.
Ming Ye.
Wake up, Ming Ye.
Ming Ye, please don't die.
Ming Ye.
They're coming after us.
What now?
Follow me.
Ming Ye.
Ming Ye, wake up.
Where is this place?
This is the middle of the river,
where the Water-calming Stone is.
The divine energy is abundant here.
We can use this
to maintain his last shred of hope.
I'll leave him to you.
Where are you going?
How can I protect him alone?
Rest assured.
I'll cast a barrier for you
to cover your energy field.
Even if you cover our energy field,
you can't cover their sight.
What if they find us here?
They won't.
I'll lure them away.
After her!
[Ming Ye's life is fading away.]
[If he dies,]
[what about me?]
[The Ancient Crystal.]
[Ming Ye was born in the East Sea.]
[This crystal is
an ultimate aquatic treasure.]
[It might save Ming Ye's life.]
[The spirits in this little river]
[have a lowly status.]
[When I take the crystal]
[and give them a chance to
present the treasure to the God of War,]
[they should feel proud for it.]
[Ming Ye's in really bad shape right now.]
[I have to make some tough calls.]
The Water-calming Crystal
was absorbed by him!
This man is Ming Ye, the God of War.
Immortal Realm relies on him
to counter the demon soldiers.
Whoever they rely on doesn't concern us.
I just know I'm the King of Mohe River.
The Water-calming Crystal is what
keeps ten thousand of Mohe residents alive!
If we want to protect our people,
we must make him return the crystal!
Dad,
please don't kill him!
He absorbed the crystal
because he was dying
after being injured by the Devil God.
He was dying?
What a coincidence!
How did he happen to fall
into my Mohe River
and take the Water-calming Crystal!
I… I brought him here.
Jiu.
What? I'm gonna kill him!
No!
Ming Ye was already breathing his last.
This place has
the most abundant divine energy.
I can only bring him here.
Besides, demon soldiers were after him.
I went to lead them away,
but I didn't expect
he'd absorb the crystal.
Did… Did you kill any
of the Devil God's men?
I did.
You've…
You've brought
a terrible disaster to us today!
Father, please calm down.
Dad,
since I caused the trouble,
I shall take the responsibility.
If the Devil God wants to catch the killer,
just hand me over to him.
You take the responsibility?
Father!
Are you capable of that?
Without the Ancient Crytal,
the Water-calming Stone
loses its energy source.
The Mohe River will be muddy and billowy.
All of our people
will suffer heavy casualties.
So many lives of them…
How… How are you going to repay them?
The people of Mohe River
suffered a catastrophe today
because I failed to discipline my daughter.
Unionid Tribe is always
kind and peace-loving.
Now that we've lost
our ancestors' blessing,
we'll definitely suffer from retribution!
The energy source was lost
all because of me.
I should make up for it.
What are you doing?
Jiu!
Come back!
Jiu, don't be headstrong!
Jiu!
[My divine essence]
[can replace the crystal
to be the energy source.]
[I've made a mistake.]
I've extracted my essence
to atone for my crime.
I only wish that the Mohe River
would be clear and calm.
Jiu!
Father,
all the aquatic residents
have been appeased.
Please go have some rest.
I'll watch her.
Your sister is asleep now.
I can stay with her for a little longer.
If she wakes up and gets angry at me,
she might not want to see me.
You know what,
your sister has been clingy
since she was a kid.
Every night before she went to bed,
she'd ask me to tell her like ten stories.
And she could only sleep
while grabbing my beard.
She was so young back then.
Her hair was short and sparse.
But she kept asking me
to braid her hair every day.
Father.
I shouldn't…
I shouldn't have hit her, should I?
Ever since she was born,
she wasn't wronged for a single bit.
She must've done this
because I hit her.
She wasn't being reckless.
She has grown up.
She's the princess of Mohe River.
She's saving her own people.
But…
She has lost her divine essence.
The path of immortals and demons diverges.
She's been learning
immortal arts since she was young.
Now without her divine essence,
she won't be able to achieve immortality.
This won't do.
I can't just leave it like this.
I'm still alive.
[The Devil God ambushed me.]
Thank you for saving my life.
the God of War,
I don't deserve your gratitude.
I'm not the one to save your life
or mend your immortal soul.
Your savior is the Ancient Crystal
we used to calm the river.
This is the bottom of the Mohe River?
I heard the Unionid Tribe
has lived here for generations
and governs its territory.
I presume that you must be King of Mohe River.
How generous of you
to save my life with your treasure.
I don't know how to repay you.
No need.
We're just a small spirit clan.
How dare we ask for rewards
from the God of War?
I don't think I've offended you ever.
Would you be frank with me?
You're the noble God of War.
We don't deserve to be your friends.
It's all because of my helpful daughter
who brought you back.
That's why you had the chance
to steal the Ancient Crystal!
I've never stolen anything.
Please be careful with your words.
Did you not do it,
or did you forget it?
Could it be that the crystal
just flew from the Water-calming Stone
into your chest all by itself?
Or am I blackmailing you
with ten thousand
of our people's lives?
When I was shot down
by the God-slaughtering Crossbow,
I lost consciousness.
I really don't remember
what happened later.
Whether you admit it or not,
the crystal has been exhausted by you.
I'm afraid you can't deny that.
As for what will happen to Mohe River,
you don't need to worry about it.
My daughter Sang Jiu
invited a fox into the henhouse,
which cost us our most important treasure.
She knew she had made a huge mistake.
So she extracted her divine essence
in replacement of the crystal.
May I have the chance
to meet Miss Sang Jiu?
I want to thank her in person.
Thank her?
Sang Jiu is my only daughter
and the princess of Mohe River.
For you, she lost her divine essence
and gave up her chance
to achieve immortality.
So you're just going to say thank you
and let it go?
Is that all the gratitude
you have for her,
and for the Mohe people?
As long as it's within my capabilities,
I'll do everything I can to compensate her.
I wonder how you would like me
to show my gratitude to the Mohe people?
Sang Jiu is the hope of Mohe River.
Now her future is ruined for you.
If you are willing to marry her,
protect her, and take her
to the immortal realm,
I'll let bygones be bygones.
I've never met Miss Sang Jiu before.
There's no love between us.
This is such a hasty marriage.
Let's not discuss if I'm willing first.
Will she agree?
That's our family business.
I'm asking you now.
What about you? Are you willing or not?
Brother, you're here.
How are you feeling?
Is Father still mad?
How's the river like now?
Don't worry. Everything's fine.
Brother.
Something wrong?
Jiu,
Father let Ming Ye
sign a marriage contract.
Ming Ye will come marry you in three days.
Why?
Dad arranged this?
Did Ming Ye agree?
You sacrificed
your divine essence for the Mohe River.
No matter how hard you train,
you'll never be able to leave this river.
Dad doesn't want to see you like this.
So he convinced Ming Ye
to take you up to the Shangqing Realm
to cleanse your essence and cultivate.
There's nothing bad staying in Mohe River.
Aren't you and dad both here?
Just tell me.
Are you willing to marry into
the Shangqing Realm?
I…
Jiu, listen to me.
Dad is picking a good future for you.
If you're not willing,
no one can force you to do that.
You can stay home forever.
You can be with father and I.
Understand?
It's your own marriage.
I won't urge you.
You think it through properly.
If you're not willing,
I'll convince father to burn this contract.
Take your time.
Just tell me your answer within three days.
Brother,
I'm willing.
Have you ever thought that
Ming Ye has never met you?
He'll naturally not love you.
But I love him.
[Sang Jiu.]
You…
You've really made up your mind?
I wanna be close to him.
I wanna see the God of War whom I admire.
I wanna see
how the Shangqing Realm looks like.
You used to say
that I was a small girl with big ideas.
This time, just let me
make my own decision.
I'm gonna need you to help with my wedding.
Alright.
Take a good rest then.
[Sang Jiu,]
[you only have courage]
[and a heart full of love.]
[Whether it's a right decision or not,]
[you're gonna have to carry on alone.]
Lord Immortal,
the auspicious time is coming.
Please let me help you get changed.
No need to trouble you.
I'll do it myself.
-Yes.
Sister Ruby,
does the God of War hate us?
He doesn't want us to serve him.
No need to take it to heart.
Those servants from the East Sea
told me that
he preferred to be alone
even when he hadn't immortalized.
And he used to be a soldier.
He really can't get used to being served.
Goddess Tian Huan is about to wake up soon.
When she's there, don't get too close.
If she sees you,
you'll probably have trouble.
Does anyone in Shangqing
not know what she desires?
She's been in love
with Lord Immortal for years.
Now with the new bride coming,
what hope does she have?
I used to think you were pretending it,
but it turns out you are really foolish.
This thing is all over the realm.
Haven't you heard how the marriage came?
The so-called bride is actually
a clam spirit in the Mohe River.
They're blackmailing him.
They say that last time
the God of War fell into
the Mohe River and used their…
[Jiu,]
[this is the Reflection Pearl I raised.]
[Whenever you miss dad and I,]
[just use it to look at us.]
Let me give it a try.
See what dad is doing now.
It's the clothes I used to wear.
Dad.
Jiu.
Ming Ye, the God of War.
Before you leave,
a kind reminder from the Mohe River.
Maybe in the eyes of the immortal realm,
the people of Mohe River
are as insignificant as duckweeds.
But Jiu
is my father's only precious daughter.
Jiu isn't born a brave girl.
But she killed four demons to save you.
Mohe River is a barren corner,
but it offered you its crystal to heal you.
From now on,
if you dare neglect or mistreat Jiu,
even if you're the God of War,
I'll hold you accountable for her,
and for Mohe River!
Who are you?
I'm Sang You, Jiu's elder brother.
Okay, I promise you.
[I will have a happy life.]
♪I wanna borrow the moon♪
♪That's about to fall from the edge of the sky♪
♪I wanna hang a glittering butterfly there
till the snow falls♪
♪I wanna hang it in a wrong time
to forget my everything♪
♪I wanna hang a dream there
and trade you with a drop of tear♪
♪Hearts burn like flames♪
♪Why don't we just be like this♪
♪For ten thousand years?♪
♪Let's freeze time before we say goodbye♪
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
♪Do you know a wise man♪
♪Does not fall in love?♪
♪Even when my heart is torn in two♪
♪I won't fly away♪
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
♪Like blessing, like suffering♪
♪It can't be settled♪
Heaven and Earth
congratulate the God of War on his wedding!
♪Why don't we just be like this
for ten thousand years?♪
♪Let's freeze time before we say goodbye♪
♪Let your sweet shallow smile♪
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
♪Do you know a wise man♪
♪Does not fall in love?♪
♪Even when my heart is torn in two♪
♪I won't fly away♪
♪Do you know the look you cast♪
♪Is like a sword piercing through my bone?♪
♪Like blessing, like suffering, it never ends♪
♪I miss you like the sands miss the desert♪
♪O, how I suffered inside♪
Be careful.
♪A day is like a thousand years♪
♪Because of the cold and lonely nights♪
The bride and the bridegroom
have heard about
each other's qualities and virtues for long.
Today they finally meet and have decided
to be husband and wife.
They promise to love each other forever
and write their vows in this contract.
Ming Ye and Sang Jiu are married today.
May Heaven and Earth be informed.
[I'm asking you now.]
[Are you willing or not?]
My poor daughter
lost her divine essence for saving you.
And she killed demon soldiers.
If the Devil God wants to find the killer,
I'm afraid she can't live.
I can promise you
to take Sang Jiu back
to the Immortal Realm.
I will cure her and protect her.
You stole the crystal.
How can I trust you?
You'll probably lie to Jiu
and lie to us all.
I really don't know anything about that.
I hope you won't pursue it any further.
Then sign this marriage contract,
so that we can trust your words.
[Ming Ye.]
Will this do?
You're really a straightforward man.
Our humble home doesn't deserve
to accommodate someone like you.
[Sorry for not walking you out.]
Lord Immortal, it's getting late.
Okay.
You may go back to rest.
Yes.
Beryl,
this clam spirit from the river
really doesn't seem to have seen the world.
She's from a little ditch.
What do you expect anyway?
I'm afraid she has never seen
how our Immortal Realm looks like
after living so many years.
-Lord Immortal.
Why didn't you two remind her?
Your Highness,
we saw Madam was having a good time.
We didn't dare to interrupt her.
That's why we forgot to remind her.
The God of War.
Miss Sang Jiu.
Miss Sang Jiu,
Is there anything?
I…
The God of War…
You can just call me Ming Ye.
Ming Ye,
I was waiting for you last night.
But you didn't come.
So I accidentally fell asleep.
Did you come afterwards?
Did I oversleep?
Sorry.
Actually,
I should be frank with you last night.
We haven't met before.
There's nothing between us.
Although we're married,
it's not out of my own will.
I guess you must think the same.
Since we're not actually husband and wife,
for our future life,
why don't we make three rules?
First,
you may enter or leave
this Yuqing Palace freely.
I won't get into your bedroom.
You and I will act on our own
and not disturb each other.
Second,
you're my wife nominally,
but you can't use your title
to bully others.
Third,
if you have anyone you love in the future,
feel free to marry him.
I can write a letter to Clam King
to divorce you.
I've got military affairs to attend to.
Excuse me for not keeping you company.
Sister Ruby,
you guessed right.
She looks kinda pitiable in this case.
What's pitiable about her?
The Unionid Tribe was blackmailing
our Lord Immortal for saving his life.
They'll reap what they sow.
Otherwise, should we be friendly to her?
Speaking of which,
we still don't know the name
of that little clam spirit.
I'm Sang Jiu.
Mad… Madam Sang.
Madam Sang.
What are your names?
I… I'm Beryl.
She's Ruby.
Two sisters,
actually, I wanna ask you something.
Do you know what the God of War
likes in his daily life?
If I wanna spend more time with him,
what should I do?
Lord Immortal doesn't seem
to have any hobbies.
He doesn't like to be close
to anyone, either.
If he's not training soldiers,
he'll be at war.
His life is quite hard.
So Goddess Tian Huan
often cooks soup with spirit herbs
for Lord Immortal as tonics.
Also…
Madam,
we're just lowly maids.
How are we supposed to know how to do that?
I understand.
So he loves training and war.
Now that I'm married,
I can't be lazy and sleep in anymore.
I'll get up early and practice with weapons.
If I'm admitted as an exception,
wouldn't I be able to get close to him?
Maybe I can even help
in the war.
Madam, you've got
quite a unique way of thinking.
By the way,
that Goddess Tian Huan you just mentioned,
who is she?
Goddess Tian Huan
is the only daughter
of the previous God of War, Tian Hao.
He used to be the owner
of this Yuqing Palace.
Lord Immortal followed Tian Hao
for many years.
For Lord Immortal,
Tian Hao is both his benefactor
and his brother in arms.
Before Tian Hao died,
he entrusted Tian Huan to Lord Immortal.
Therefore, he often looked out for her.
Madam, please don't overthink.
Is she that pretty fairy
with a very tall chignon?
I heard she's still in a coma.
Can I go visit her?
The Goddess is still
in seclusion in the Bihan Hall.
I'm afraid she prefers not to be visited.
Alright then.
When she wakes up,
please remember to tell me.
I'll go see her.
But the God of War
only needs immortal soldiers.
He can't take in
a little spirit without divine essence.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪