The translation team is working hard on the final subtitles. We will replace the previous version ASAP. Thank you for your patience.
♪Dark night, teary moon, and cold blood♪
♪Have given my eyes reasons to fear light♪
♪Brightness and warmth, leaves me♪
♪Judging by intuition♪
♪Ah, love moulds me like the jade♪
♪Ah, entangled by these feelings♪
♪I will never be fazed♪
♪By how the world treats me♪
♪Break through and break free♪
♪How do you tell good from evil♪
♪I was once fragile♪
♪But the kisses of love healed me♪
♪My existence♪
♪Will never quell to the prickles of pain♪
[Till The End of The Moon]
[Episode 29]
Fortunately,
you weren't hurt.
General Ye,
what are you doing?
His Majesty went crazy. Are you crazy too?
If my sister sees
what you've become now,
she will only be disgusted.
That's nonsense.
Why would she marry me
if she found me disgusting?
And why would she treat me well?
In this world,
only she treated me well.
Only she did…
I…
Tantai Jin,
I plead with you
and with you on her behalf.
Please spare her
and let her rest in peace with dignity.
What you gave her, she didn't want.
And what she wanted from you,
you always failed to fulfill.
She just wanted to leave you.
She was even willing to die for it.
Don't you understand?
Heaven above!
I'm willing to give up my body,
spirit, and everything.
I hope that
meeting you again
we will never meet again
in every transmigration.
No…
No!
I don't want to…
I don't want to torture her.
I just want to be nice to her,
just like how she protected,
and guarded me.
These things are not clean.
Eating them will make you sick.
Do you believe that
I can hit you right now?
Why would you hit him?
A day as a couple
brings a hundred days of gratitude.
Isn't it only natural for me
to help you out this time?
♪to forget my everything♪
"♪I wanna hang a dream there
and trade you with a drop of tear♪"
♪Hearts burn like flames♪
Yes,
she wanted to leave me.
She wanted to leave so much
that she would risk everything.
♪Be the salt in my tears♪
♪Let it be your payback and my debt♪
She did it.
Tantai Jin,
your wife,
my sister,
this woman called Ye Xiwu, is dead.
The deceased has passed.
It's time to let her rest in peace.
Hope that you know the right thing to do.
♪Like blessing, like suffering♪
♪It can't be settled♪
General Ye, wait.
General!
His Majesty doesn't
have many close confidants.
You are the only one who can advise him.
You cannot leave like this.
My persuasion will be useless
if he is stubbornly
trapped in his own delusions.
I envy him,
for he can be so crazy.
I also want to mourn
my loved ones as he does.
But how many generals
and civilians have died
in this war-torn country?
Jing is now in dire need
of someone to revive the country,
but he is indulging in his own sorrow
and is unwilling to wake up.
Did Xiwu, my father,
Zeyu,
and Pian Ran all die in vain?
He wants to die with Xiwu,
but what about me?
Why would I want to live miserably alone?
But I cannot let them die in vain.
The broken country and its people
need someone to carry it forward.
Can you understand how I feel?
Yes.
I may never be able to
be as crazy as His Majesty.
This is the consequence
of those who have been
through the horrors of war.
The first thing that comes to my mind
is what to do with those who lived,
and who caused them
to reach this point today.
The culprit, Tantai Minglang,
was killed by His Majesty himself.
General Ye, who are you referring to?
Chief,
they have found Ye Bingchang.
She wanted to leave the city in disguise
but was recognized by the guards.
Should…
should we lock her back in?
Mr. Nian,
can you bring Ye Bingchang here?
I have questions for her.
Why did you escape?
Qingyu,
save me.
I don't want to be locked up again.
The dungeon is an abyss of darkness.
and I have had enough.
I also understand that I was wrong.
That day in the dungeon,
why did you try to kill Xiwu?
If we were one moment late,
she would have died there.
I told you,
I was taking revenge.
Ye Xiwu caused Xiao Lin's death.
Lie!
Ye Bingchang,
Later on, I thought about it
over and over again.
You are her own sister.
If you wanted to kill her,
you had many opportunities to do so.
There was no need to wait
until she was thrown into prison.
Ye Qingyu,
you are indeed the only smart person
in the entire Ye family, except for me.
I am also your sister.
Are you really going to give me no way out
just because of Xiwu?
Don't compare yourself with Xiwu.
What you've been doing
has made you disqualified
from being a member
of the Ye family since long ago.
Is that so, Ye Qingyu?
What right do you have
to criticize me from
a high and mighty position?
Throughout history, the winners
have always been taking it all.
If Xiao Lin had conquered the world,
it would be Ye Xiwu who kneels here today,
being spurned by you.
Alright,
since you want to know the truth so badly,
I will tell you.
I tried to kill Ye Xiwu
because I didn't want the truth
about the poisoned porridge
to be exposed one day.
Poisoned porridge?
Yes.
Ye Xiwu wanted to please Tantai Jin.
She couldn't cook
but insisted on making porridge.
So I decided to
put some poison in the porridge.
What did you say?
What about Grandma?
You knew the porridge was poisoned,
and yet you still gave it to Grandma!
That's right.
I want her
to die with Tantai Jin
and Ye Xiwu.
Ye Bingchang,
you are out of your mind!
Not at all!
I was very clear-headed.
I just didn't want to
tolerate this anymore.
The old lady sided with Ye Xiwu
and only loved her.
Since she liked Ye Xiwu so much,
I could just fulfill her wish.
Then why did you want to
poison Tantai Jin?
Tantai Jin!
It's all because of him,
that Xiao Lin was nothing.
I lost everything.
Later
he even took away the love threads.
Yet he still wanted me to live,
but I didn't want to yield.
I wouldn't have fallen to this point
if it weren't for him.
I see.
If it weren't for you,
Xiao Lin wouldn't have died.
I thought Ye Xiwu wanted to
kill me for Xiao Lin,
so that was why
everything happened afterward.
Open your mouth.
You wanted to kill me,
but you got Xiao Lin killed.
Since then, Ye Xiwu hated me to the bone,
which led to where we are today.
Nonsense!
It wasn't me!
It was you!
You and Ye Xiwu got Xiao Lin killed!
Ye Bingchang,
Xiao Lin entrusted me
to spare your life before his death,
so what should I do now?
I never liked this world,
but Ye Xiwu is different.
She loved this world.
She wanted to give love
even to widows and orphans,
to refugees and the common people.
That's why I wanted to try
to love this world like she did.
But now that
Ye Xiwu is gone,
my heart is dead too.
I want to hate everything,
but Ye Xiwu wouldn't be happy about it.
Ye Bingchang,
If you like porridge so much,
I'll let you have enough of it.
Yes!
Let me out!
Tantai Jin,
Tantai Jin!
You're awake!
Don't sleep here. You'll catch a cold.
I know what I'm doing.
What are you doing?
Once you start reading memorials,
you never take a break.
Even if you want to become a good king
who works hard for the people,
you cannot harm your own body.
Why are you looking at me like that?
I won't run away all of a sudden.
Ye Xiwu,
what do you really want to do
by coming to my side?
Yes,
I should have left.
Ye Xiwu!
Xiao Lin,
why did you die?
Why don't you come and save me?
The one I wanted to kill was Tantai Jin!
Now you are dead.
What is the use of your dying wish?
Tantai Jin still wants to kill me.
Pang Yizhi?
Ye Bingchang.
Why are you here?
Are you here to save me?
You deserve your punishment,
so I won't save you.
However, Xiao Lin left something with me
before his death
and asked me to find an opportunity
to give it to you.
It's a letter from him.
Wife…
he still recognized me as his wife.
But it's a little late.
Xiao Lin was upright and loyal,
but how did you treat him?
Upright
and loyal…
what does that have to do with me?
That's all I can say.
Bingchang,
things have come to this point.
I no longer care about
the letter you wrote
asking me to save you
or whether you ever plotted against me.
We are a married couple,
and there are some things
I still want you to know.
It is said that the closest people
can sometimes be the least close.
In the past, I was constantly distressed,
feeling that no matter how hard I tried,
I could not win your complete trust.
It was not until the day
I learned about the Love Threads incident
that I finally understood
why you always seemed so uneasy.
You were worried
that the love you received was all false,
weren't you?
Bingchang,
actually, whether you had
that strand of Love Threads or not,
there would still be people loving you.
Perhaps you don't remember this:
In the late spring of that year,
you and the women of the Ye family
went outside the city to worship ancestors,
and you got off the carriage alone
to take a walk.
I still remember how happy you were
because of a cluster of blackberry roses
and how beautiful your smile was.
Blackberry roses do not compete with
other flowers during springtime
and bloom the latest in loneliness.
I will remember your look
with flowers in your hair and your smile
in spring for the rest of my life.
Later on, when you distributed porridge
to the people in the city,
I secretly went to watch as well.
I liked you not because of
that strand of Love Threads,
but because of who you are.
Unfortunately, I never got the chance
to tell you these things,
and our fate has come to an end.
Bingchang,
I hope that your wishes may come true.
♪Take a look at this world that we love♪
♪Reviewing the past years♪
Xiao Lin,
♪The vivid and splendid dreams
are but a regret that won't fade, it seems♪
♪Rather than wake from this slumber
I'd prefer the dream to last forever♪
I always thought that
it was the love threads
that made me receive favoritism.
As it turns out,
I'm the one who's been wrong all the time.
I'm sorry.
I was wrong.
♪I'm never heartless♪
♪My emotions ebb and flow like the seasons♪
♪Even if sorrows never end♪
I have got both the blood of enemies
and the tears of lovers.
♪I can exchange everything for this life♪
♪False sweetness is always abundant♪
Aren't you going to
see her for one last time?
No need.
Mr. Nian,
thank you for previously taking care
of the burial of my father and brother.
Your father and elder brother
sacrificed to protect the people.
Chief Pian Ran did the same.
Their acts of righteousness
are truly admirable.
How is His Majesty?
He went to the royal tomb
early this morning,
and he promised
to bury Xiwu with the ceremony
of a queen in a few days.
In a few days?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I hope he doesn't go back on his words.
The courtiers were initially worried
that His Majesty would
abandon the country for one person,
but now they are all relieved.
♪So many lovers can't be together♪
♪The tides are sketched
by the full and crescent moon♪
General Ye,
to be honest,
I wish His Majesty
weren't the king anymore,
so that he could
leave this sad place.
Sad place?
Yes.
His queen died here.
When he sees her,
how can he be happy again?
♪Actually, the sun and the moon
can shine together♪
♪Light and darkness can overlap with each other♪
♪Love and hate have blurred boundaries♪
Yeah.
Someone has lost
the one he loves the most
but still has to be trapped here forever.
Every flower, every leaf,
every blade of grass, and every tree
would feel like sharp blades
slowly cutting into his heart.
♪Do you still remember your silhouette♪
General Ye,
I know that you also
lost someone loved the most.
Whether for you or His Majesty,
this period of time
will be very difficult to endure.
♪The moment we first met♪
♪Just one glance, and my soul was locked♪
You once promised me
to take me home with you.
♪I can't escape the rule of destiny♪
♪I've suffered and loved♪
♪Actually, the sun and the moon
can shine together♪
Now,
there are no others disturbing us here.
I will go back with you,
and you will take me to see the lake
and watch the stars you have seen.
We will never be separated again,
you belong only to me
and I belong only to you.
Despite the changes in the world,
we will remain steadfast.
We will keep our promise
together this time,
so you will belong to me forever.
♪If good and evil were divided by life♪
♪I am willing to use my thoughts♪
♪For just one chance♪
Ye Xiwu,
let's go home together.
Fire! Help!
The palace is on fire! Put it out!
Hurry up! Put out the fire!
Hurry!
Quickly!
Help!
Hurry!
Put out the fire!
Hurry up!
Hurry!
This way!
Get more water!
Hurry!
Sir,
we have searched through the ruins,
but found nothing.
His Majesty must have had a plan
and left the letter
in the study in advance.
A country cannot be
without a ruler for even a day.
His Majesty entrusted in the letter,
instructing you to find a capable member
from a branch of the Tantai family
to inherit the throne.
For the stability of the kingdom,
you must complete His Majesty's request.
Yes.
Too many people have died.
I can't believe it has been
ten thousand years already.
I never thought that you and I
would have a chance to meet again.
Si Ying?
That's right.
We both lived.
But we never get to meet His Lordship.
Don't be sad.
It has been ten thousand years.
It's time
to welcome the new Devil God.
True.
As long as the evil bone remains,
His Lordship will never disappear.
Now that the Barren Abyss Barrier
is unsealed,
from today onwards,
I will travel across
the Four Continents and Three Realms
to find the trail of the new Devil God.
But with such boundless crowds,
where should I start my search?
The bank of Ruo River.
I heard the bank of Ruo River
is where the spirits of the dead gather.
But His Lordship is the Devil God.
Would his spirit be there?
His Lordship certainly would not
mingle with the ordinary.
However, I heard that back then,
His Lordship made a special agreement
with the Yiyue tribe
of the Bank of Ruo River.
Why don't we start our search from there?
Good idea.
Now that we have been revived,
it's time for us to reunite and restore
the Demon Realm for His Lordship.
It's been ten thousand years,
and do you still know us?
I am the Monster of Drought, Si Ying.
Today, under the command of the Devil God,
I order you
to find the Devil God
and restore Barren Abyss.
Those who refuse to obey
shall be killed!
Devil God!
The Ruo River, guarded by the Yiyue tribe,
is also the Nether River.
When the moon turns into
an underworld moon,
The Yiyue tribe
can use their secret spells
to open the Gate of Underworld Moon
and enter the place
where the spirits gather.
Your Majesty!
Ye Xiwu.
Go away!
Your Majesty!
You can't stay here.
Let go!
Your Majesty,
I know that rescuing you
is against your will.
However, I know of a way
for you to see Ye Xiwu again.
Ye Xiwu is right here.
I'm not going anywhere.
Go away!
Your Majesty!
Nian Baiyu!
The Ruo River, guarded by the Yiyue tribe,
is also the Nether River.
I can tell you
where to find Ye Xiwu's spirit.
What did you say?
But, Lord,
are you sure you want to go in?
The Gate of Underworld Moon
has been opened a few times,
but the people who entered
never came back.
Mister,
will you come back?
Lord,
there is no end or way out in there.
How will you come back?
Nian Baiyu,
thank you
for your helping me the whole time.
Ye Xiwu,
where are you?
Lord…
Here,
freshly boiled milk tea.
Thanks, Sister.
Baiyu,
stop feeling sad.
Every man has his destiny.
You have done everything you can.
Sister, Mom,
do you think the Lord
can find who he wants to meet?
This type of thing
is up to how sincere one's heart is.
Who knows?
There are thousands of spirits in there.
Even if he can resist
the erosion of the Ruo Water,
how long will it take for him
to recognize each spirit one by one?
Ye Xiwu, where are you?
Look. It's him again.
He has been here for several months.
Who is he looking for?
I don't know.
Let's ask him
Who are you looking for?
Ye Xiwu.
I'm looking for her.
Can you help me find Ye Xiwu?
Ye Xiwu?
Is the one you are looking for
called Ye Xiwu?
Yes.
Ye Xiwu.
There are so many spirits here,
and we don't know them all.
But perhaps the one you're looking for
is in the depths of the Nether River.
However…
Ye Xiwu,
where is she?
Tantai Jin,
you are here.
Ye Xiwu!
Tantai Jin,
long time no see.
Ye Xiwu,
you are really here!
You finally came.
It's really you!
Ye Xiwu!
Where did you go?
No!
Ye Xiwu!
Mortal bodies will be tempted
by the Ruo Water and see illusions,
and in the end, they will be devoured.
Ye Xiwu,
you must be in the Nether River.
I will find you!
Instead of letting you perish,
let us take you to find her.
Get on the boat.
You won't be hurt
as long as you don't touch the water.
♪Every pair of distant stars♪
♪Were lonely souls in the beginning♪
♪Floating in the stream of time
and entangled in the threads of love♪
♪Fate is unfathomably deep♪
♪And indifferent to meeting and parting♪
Ye Xiwu,
you died because of me,
No matter what it takes,
I will take you home.
♪It's the world
that loves you and loved by you♪
♪I don't care about right or wrong♪
♪I just trap my heart in prison♪
Ye Xiwu!
♪Laughing at the foolish deep affection♪
♪I, alone, search for your lingering soul♪
Ye Xiwu!
Oh no,
he seems to be seeing illusions again.
♪Inscribed in my heart
is the pain of loving you♪
♪With all my heart and strength♪
♪For you, I've overturned my body and soul♪
♪Snow falls without traces
And I revive in ruins♪
♪My body is smashed to pieces
Like flowers fall in an instant♪
♪My dreams want more than me to stay♪
♪Joy, anger, sorrow, fear, desire, hatred♪
Is it worth it to do all this
for a deceased person?
Yes.
I will
keep looking,
and keep doing this,
until my life is over.
Baiyu,
where did you go?
Mom,
I just went to
the Bank of Ruo River to check
if Lord is back or not.
You know very well that
the Gate of Underworld Moon
only opens once every 500 years.
Your Lord entered it
and there's no way he will be back.
Baiyu,
since you are already back here,
just let go of the past,
and live your life well.
Yes, Baiyu.
The girl I talked to you about last time,
do you really not want to meet her?
Maybe I should really forget about Lord.
Yes,
live your own life.
Mom, Sister,
stay home.
I will go and check it out.
Run!
Be careful!
Hurry up!
It's not fun to kill him.
Why don't we just keep him alive,
in case he might
come in handy in the future?
Let's go.
Let's look for the demonic fetus.
I don't know how long it will take
to look through them one by one.
Lord,
I can't live to see you come back.
I found two dandelions
in your precious Royal Garden.
Surprisingly, they have not been removed
by the gardeners.
They are really fortunate.
I heard that you could
make wishes on dandelions,
so I dug them up.
My hands…
Why?
Now I'm taking your evil bone
and paying you back
with the divine essence.
You won't become the Devil God anymore.
Ye Xiwu,
is the divine essence
you gave me healing me?
You let me live,
but also made me suffer
the pain of shredding me in pieces
again and again.
Is this your revenge on me?
It doesn't matter.
As long as it's from you,
I will accept it.
Why are you still not giving up?
No…
She is still somewhere in here.
I will definitely find her.
Who is he?
A pitiful person.
In order to find his deceased lover,
he has been searching
in the Nether River for a hundred years,
but still hasn't found her.
World-overturning Jade…
Can it help me
find Ye Xiwu's spirit?
She bore the curse
of violent death for me.
Please give me a chance to repay her.
Ye Xiwu,
when can I find you?
Today I will tell you a secret story.
It is said that five hundred years ago,
the king was named Tantai Jin.
Legend has it that he was born
by killing his mother,
which was extremely ominous,
but he unified Jing and Sheng
and achieved greatness.
Nobody knows that
he once burned down the Palace of Jing
for a woman,
and was burned so badly
that his face was destroyed.
To commemorate him,
the Tantai family's generations of kings
have all worn masks
Tantai Jin…
to cover their faces.
There is another secret story
that said the Devil God would appear
in the world again
in 500 years, which is now.
There are too many rumors
about the world ending.
Someone also said that
Devil God would end the world last year,
but what happened?
Nothing.
The healing power of divine essence
is getting weaker and weaker.
I'm afraid my body has reached its limit.
Ye Xiwu,
even if I were to die today,
I would still search for you
for another day.
After I die,
my spirit can merge
with this Nether Water,
and I will continue to seek you.
Are you still not giving up?
Sir, why are you still not giving up?
Don't waste your breath with him.
After being washed
by the Ruo Water for 500 years,
he can no longer hear anything.
Tantai Jin,
go back with me.
Don't you get too carried away.
I never said I'd spend
the rest of my life with you.
Ye Xiwu,
I'm coming for you.
[Till The End of The Moon]
♪A mortal's heart is like gazing up
and suddenly the moon has waned♪
♪The earthly life is like 3,000 flowers
covered in a snowstorm of tears♪
♪Pity is like holding a butterfly
while on the brink of death♪
♪Enlightenment is like washing
our memories in muddy water♪
♪Never to be seen again♪
♪I've seen whispers of love
blossom beautifully♪
♪While weeping eyes murmur in their sleep♪
♪Overwhelming affection
leads us to the brink of destruction♪
♪Within an embrace holds endless dread♪
♪I loved you to the end
of the world and back♪
♪I believed in love at first sight♪
♪After plucking all my black feathers♪
♪My faith in love
as flawless as the moonlight♪
♪Listen to how the flowers respire♪
♪Just like the people of this world♪
♪No matter how far I travel
come rain or shine♪
♪The moonlight shines like my armor♪
♪I admire how you came etched with scars♪
♪Determined to live
as gentle as you could♪
♪You got rid of all your black feathers♪
♪And learned to love all you resented♪
♪Frail lives with our heads in the clouds♪
♪Woo-ooh, let's make it count♪